Chapter 1065: Void Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was floating in the sky looking down at Chen Cheng and her family. This was one of the rare occurrences where he met someone by chance. What he gave Chen Cheng was not just one of his dark blue knives, but also one of the most fundamental frost secret technique exercise. If she actually practiced it to its peak level, he would be able to sense it through the ring and come back to pick her up. However, if she did not practice it, perhaps they might never see each other ever again.

Garen took one last peek below at Chen Cheng and her family who were still in shock. He then turned around and flew back into his own flying ship.

A black whirlpool slowly appeared before the flying ship but nobody from the crowd could see what was happening. The streets were still filled with a stream of cars and the entire city was still functioning as usual.

The flying ship slowly entered the black hole and soon disappeared into the sky.

Garen was sitting at a dimly lit area inside the cockpit of the flying ship, staring at the blinking lights on the control panel. He stood up abruptly and searched around for a purple colored fruit wine. He then poured himself a small glass.

After taking a tiny sip, his body shuddered involuntarily. He was frozen for a moment, the wine glass in his hands and the wine itself was instantly covered with a layer of white frost. From Garen’s palm which was in contact with the glass, a layer of thick ice frost started spreading, freezing the entire glass and wine together which then formed a purple gem-like ice block.

He had unconsciously reached Inherited Level.

It took Garen a long time before he finally came around. Looking inside his body, a high amount of energy from the Plasma Bomb was fully absorbed already while there were still a small traces of energy left unabsorbed from the blood red beads which were weakening by the moment.

“Hellfrost Peacock Technique… Indeed a terrifying growth,” he took a deep breath. “So this is the legendary thick and thin, where it finally outbreaks after years of accumulation.”

Entering Inherited Level was a silent move. For outsiders, Garen just seemed to shudder for a moment and the wine of glass in his hands froze. That was all bystanders would see, and perhaps they would think he lost control suddenly, but nobody would ever think that he actually succeeded in advancing to Inherited Level.

“From entering Resonance Level to Inherited Level, how long did I actually take? Not even three years,” Garen exclaimed. “As a Secret Technician, the highest Living Secret Technique is indeed extraordinary. After practicing the Living Secret Technique for such a long time, I really thought I would never succeed, that I would never reach somewhere, but who knew I would experience such a drastic change.”

He recalled Nonosiva’s future that he witnessed back in the Space-Time Print.

Under the cultivation of the lucky remaining resources of Scarlet Snow Sect, he would enter Inherited Level. But after a hundred years, he would still be killed by the White King’s men, the Royal Cavaliers of the Light of Freedom, in the Battle of Ice Age.

This was the original fate of this body. Members of the Light of Freedom were all Perpetual Motion-leveled powerhouses and Chinande the Wild Mutt was the leader who led the Light of Freedom to destroy one of the Three Major Metropolis of the Energy Machinists — the city of Nagadako, which was also the entire Planet Naga.

Turning back from this tiny planet, Garen returned back to his original path.

“I wonder what is the relationship between Carthage and the Light of Freedom? From the looks of it, this guy might possibly a projection or a clone of one of the members of the Light of Freedom,” he remembered the gigantic silver arm full of scales and made a guess of his own.

“Entering Inherited Level in such a short period of time is too sudden. It is better if I hide it first and wait for a while before announcing it. With that, I’d be valued and also hide some unusual features at the same time,” Garen had come to a decision. He was in no rush since Carthage gave him a year’s time to wander around.

The flying ship flew through the rainbow passage, then emerging in front of a huge circular silver-blue gate.

‘Welcome to Willis Star Port, please choose your time to jump.’ An electronic female voice rang.

“Immediately,” Garen responded.

“Entering default coordinates… Begin access track…”

Garen could see the silver metal track outside the windows backtracking. The flying ship was moving rapidly along two metal tracks in space and it was still accelerating, moving faster and faster.

‘Speed has reached the preset level, will proceed to space jump. All crew please get ready.’ The smart system of the flying ship reminded.

Garen walked toward the control panel of the flying ship and swept through the display screen, there were only a few points marked on the map in the flying ship.

Scarlet Snow Planet, Planet Naga, Mother Planet, and the unknown Planet Number 1 that he just visited.

There were only four planets.

“Returning now would be meaningless. Since I’ve just broken through Inherited Level, I should do some training of my own outside. It’s time to test the true powers of my Hellfrost Peacock Technique,” an idea surfaced Garen’s mind and he did not choose any of the planets as his destination.

‘Activate scanner for star maps, search for any planets or non-planets,’ Garen commanded softly.

‘Understood.’

A soft blue light started blinking on the screen and a huge radar ring appeared in the middle with a white pointer rotating non-stop.

Within seconds, the scan results were out.

‘Three hundred and fifty light-years scan is complete, altogether two hundred and fifty thousand non-planets.’ The scanning system gave an answer that made Garen speechless.

“Exclude the planets near the usual tracks, filter within a hundred light years,” he minimized the range to avoid being found out by other flying ships passing by.

‘Minimizing range… Remaining results one hundred and sixty thousand.’

At this moment, the space jump had already started and there were only silver threads pulled from the Milky Way outside the windows of his flying ship zooming past along with a great number of planets. It was beyond magnificent.

Bang!

Suddenly, the flying ship shook as if it crashed into something.

‘Experiencing spaceship anchor interception, chances of meeting Space Pirates is eighty percent.’ The flying ship’s smart system rang immediately.

The flying ship instantly decelerated and recovered from its space jump status.

Garen was worried. Once interjected in the middle of a space jump and one loses his high-speed jump status, it would be highly unlikely to make a far distance jump with a miniature flying ship like his because energy source would be a huge problem.

The distance between the flying ship and its current location was at least between ten to a few thousand light years. A distance this big was as wide as seas and deserts, maybe even further than one could imagine. Once stopped, the time needed to return to one’s destination would be a huge problem.

This was like a normal person who boarded a plane from Asia to America and was suddenly thrown overboard onto a small island in the middle of the Pacific Ocean, then asked to swim to his destination. The challenge was here. If one did not meet a large-scale flying ship, there was the possibility of dying of old age in the middle of nowhere in the universe. This was the greatest risk of long-distance space jumps.

“A one in a thousand chance of being interjected and I had the honor of meeting it, I’m seriously lucky…” Garen mocked himself softly, then swiftly opened the control panel and started operating his ship.

‘Connect Energy Machinist’s Energy Machine Imprint.’

‘Connected. Manual operation activated.’ The smart system responded.

The view outside the windows finally stabilized and what appeared before Garen’s eyes were at least ten humongous fleets of ships. These ships were like pieces of black mainlands with countless red and blue blinking lights on them. Occasionally there were a few Mechs that emerged from within and darted toward the space in front.

The space on the other side was completely blocked by the humongous ship so Garen could not make out what was happening over there. However, from the vague flashes and explosion flames, he could guess that there was a war happening.

‘Public channel signal found, do you wish to connect?’

“Connect,” Garen replied.

A piece of surface popped out from beside the glass window of the flying ship as a display screen and it was displaying an overall radar scan.

“This is Remora Business Alliance’s mothership, Sapphire. To all those flying ships who were interrupted while jumping, listen up. To all those flying ships who were interrupted while jumping, listen up. The ones blocking us in front are the Dragonfly People from the Interstellar Pirates of Silver Blue Starsea. I hope that everyone will send out sufficient combat power so that we can get through this together,” a frantic man spoke up in the public channel.

“Interstellar Pirates?” It was Garen’s first time meeting such an event. Although he had heard of the Interstellar Pirates through magazines and news, this was actually his very first time encountering them.

After all, he had always been living on Mother Planet before joining Scarlet Sect so that he would have the qualifications to get in touch with the universe space sort of things because back in Mother Planet, space had been completely banned.

On the other hand, Planet Naga was opposing space, not even truly existing in the universe space. Besides Planet Naga, a lot of the surrounding areas were just violent anti-spatial particle storms with raging material-energy. It was nearly impossible to travel around.

It was only when he reached Scarlet Snow Planet where he acquired the Interstellar Travel License when he became a Third Hearted Disciple, or else he would have never thought about leaving Scarlet Snow Planet.

Garen cast a glance at the radar. There were hundreds of ships held up, all squeezed together as they welcomed the fleet of yellow battleship. Both sides were releasing a vast amount of Mechs and miniature bombing planes and combat panes. There were also mant pulse airships and even torpedo ships.

The torpedo ships were constantly releasing fish missiles that were pulled along by thin white threads which were very conspicuous in space.

“What about Energy Machinists in space, how are we supposed to battle?” Garen has yet made contact with such information as he was progressing too fast and there were a lot of things he had not caught up with. Luckily for him, he prepared some information before he started his journey.

“An ordinary Energy Machinist relies on his Energy Machine when engaging in a space battle, but I’m an Energy Machinist from Planet Naga so my body plays the most important role while my Energy Machines play the supporting role. This is troublesome… What I really need now is combat power, but that would be a Pilot’s role…” Garen frowned.

He knew that no matter how strong his Energy Machinist physique was, it was still merely a support in such an intense battle in space. Many Pilots have incredibly powerful Mechs, so in a battle like this, even as an Inherited Leveled Energy Machinist, an Energy Machinist from Planet Naga would not mean anything. If he was to wander around the battle in space alone, Inherited Level would certainly do. However, in comparison to a Mech, his abilities were nowhere near.

The Mechs were equipped with weapons of high lethality. A hundred Level-One Pilots who had been through space battle training would be able to trap a single non-equipped Inherited-Leveled Pilot from Planet Naga.

Chapter 1066: Void Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“The Energy Machinists of Planet Naga who focus on their own strength excessively are only suitable for landing operations, or infiltration operations. They are not quick enough for the various activities in space. After all, some of the places are restricted by the limits of the human body which cannot be compared to a mech,” Garen shook his head and sighed. “During times like these, it will be much more convenient to just let the Energy Machineries get into battle.”

“Now that it is being interrupted, the only way to get back to the territory of Planet Scarlet Snow is through the help of a large spaceship, and Remora Business Alliance spaceship is a good choice.”

Garen quickly checked the data of this business alliance. It was a cosmic group engaged in the research of medical biotechnology, and they were obviously the main target of the Interstellar Pirates. Otherwise, they would not use such a costly space anchor to temporarily seal the Stargate.

From the data, the reputation of the Remora Business Alliance was considered passable. Also, Garen had decided to find the largest spaceship and directly request for help.

“This is an Energy Machinist with a private flying ship who wishes to board your spaceship to use the jump portal to return to Planet Scarlet Snow. Please answer.”

Soon, there was a response.

“Dear Energy Machinist, please show some sincerity if you wish to use the jump portal.”

What he meant was very simple and obvious, and that was, he wanted something in return. What will be the best reward on the battlefield? That would be to help fight off the pirates!

Garen understood what they meant, and after thinking for a short while, he answered quickly.

“You will see my sincerity.”

Then, he walked to the middle of his flying ship. At that time, the flying ship was still located behind the business alliance spaceship and there was still a certain distance before they reached the pirates. Therefore, there was no need to worry about safety issues yet.

Garen quickly found a space flying device that he had prepared before his trip as a prevention. It was something that he used to equip on his black wolf. However, Garen only had five of it, as it was very expensive, and he was reluctant to buy more of it.

He picked up a device, summoned the black wolf and equip the device onto the back of the black wolf.

A clashing sound was heard.

The black device automatically snapped on to the back of the black wolf, and then he slowly stretched out his wings. It looked good, as it transformed an ordinary black giant wolf into a black wolf with wings. However, he was not clear on how it would function.

“After all, the black wolf is only suitable for landing operations. It is time for me to choose a new Energy Machine Imprint… it will be best to choose one that can fight in space,” Garen started pondering.

“I have reached Level Six in the Inherited Level, and I can now choose a new Energy Machine Imprint. The previous two that I chose were wolves. This time, I can choose one that can adapt to various environments.”

As an Energy Mechanist, Energy Machinery was essential to him. Even though he did not have the rare types, but he would always carry a commonly used type around with him. This time in particular, after returning from the Blue Frost Sect, he prepared a whole set of basic Energy Machinery from the market beforehand.

Of course, it was too late to train it right now.

After he equipped the five black winter wolves with the space flying devices, Garen carefully tested it. Then, he took out five distorted seeds from his body and pressed it hard on the hidden parts of the abdomen of the five giant wolves. So that it would not be noticeable to others.

Unexpectedly, shortly after he pushed the distorted seed into the five wolves, some sudden changes happened to the five giant wolves that was beyond Garen’s imagination.

The giant wolves started expanding by becoming taller and larger. From a height of roughly a meter tall to more than three meters tall, they almost looked like elephants and they caused the flying ship to shake as they stepped onto the ground. A large amount of transparent stuff were being sucked into their noses and it seemed like those were the stuff that made their body look that horrifying.

But this wasn’t the weirdest thing, what was even more surprising was that the heads of the five giant wolves began to bend slightly and a large bulge appeared on their necks.

The sound of flesh and blood tearing apart was heard, and another similar looking hideous wolf head appeared.

Howl… howl…

All five of the giant wolves were almost completely dissimilated at the same time, and they tilted their heads as they howled. The sound waves instantly shattered most of the inside of the ship into pieces.

Garen was dumbfounded when he saw the changes.

“Could it be that it was necessary for the final evolution of the wolves to be two-headed dogs?” He never understood how genetic mutation works. He had obviously checked the genes when they were made, and there were no genes that would cause them to be a two-headed wolf…

As Energy Machinery that he controlled, Garen immediately knew the special ability of these mutated two-headed wolves. In addition to the unique Level Six Inherited Level force field, there were two other special abilities.

Firstly, their high-strength qualities had exceeded the other Level Six Energy Machineries, in terms of their strength, speed, physical recovery or resistance. The Level Four distorted seed strengthen them by six times as compared to their original strength, and it was a horrifying increase in strength. Originally, it would only increase their strength by three times, but after mastering the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, the distorted seed was able to improve their physical quality by six times.

The six-fold increase did not represent the increase in six number of heads, instead, it represented an increase in their combat strength.

Secondly, the most crucial part was the other head of the two-headed dog, which had a preliminary level of intelligence… Although their intelligence level was extremely crude, without a doubt, it could be considered a certain level of intellectual being.

“Intelligence…” Garen could not believe it. Beings created purely through biotechnology were able to have their own intelligence. It was not something like an intellectually made brain, but a truly intelligent intellectual being!

Garen had an idea. He quickly transferred the language and characters of the mechanical seal, and some basic information into each area of the brains of the five two-headed wolves. Then, he imported some basic logic in it.

He suddenly thought of the Void Creatures and terrifying race during the Ancient Endor war. Could it be that they created their army using this method? The possibility of his speculation was very high. The reason why each Army Level void creatures had their own void army might be because they were using similar methods.

Soon, the data transmission was completed.

As he finished transferring the data, the five two-headed wolves underwent new changes once again.

They tried to stand up, with only their two hind legs, and they actually stood up.

‘Thank you, master for granting me life.’

‘Thank you, master for granting me life…’

The five two-headed wolves adjusted their vocal cords and started speaking straight out. They politely saluted to Garen with a human-like gesture.

Only then Garen recalled that part of the basic information that he imported into their brain were stuff from the education of the nobles. As compared to the basic knowledge of this world, most of the imported information were from the peaceful aristocratic life in the totem world.

That led to such an odd change to these two-headed wolves.

“How do all of you feel?” Garen looked at the five two-headed wolves in a complicated way. This was after all, the first time that he had created biological beings with wisdom, and he had an indescribable feeling.

“I am recalling my ignorant past. If it wasn’t for master, who gave me wisdom, we would continue living ignorantly by relying on our instinct to survive,” the tallest two-headed wolves responded with a low voice. Their other head seemed to not have any effect, as they only used one head to answer and think.

“Perhaps, I should now call all of you two-headed werewolves,” Garen said speechlessly. He found that guy’s tone a little strange, as he looked like an art enthusiast with a sentimental pose as he had his head tilted 45 degrees towards the sky.

“Master, please grant us names, to celebrate our new life,” the strongest two-headed wolf requested respectfully with his head lowered.

All of their strength were at inherited level, but all they got was inherited level force field, extremely brutal physical quality and vitality equivalent to Garen which was 20 points. However, their agility did not really increase much, with only five points. After all, Hellfrost Peacock was never a void creature with quick speed.

Although they cannot be compared to the Energy Machinist in Planet Naga, or even the Resonance Level Energy Machinist, they were still much stronger than many other Energy Machinists.

“Name?” Garen shook his head. “Get into battle… If you can make it back alive, I will grant you names.”

The five giant wolves immediately kneeled down.

“Our victory belongs to master, and we will return with victory!!”

The isolation hatch of the flying ship opened, and the five giant wolves walked out one after the other.

They each grabbed a laser cannon, although the cannons were not a powerful model, they were still way more powerful than ordinary laser cannons. After all, it was better than fighting empty handed. Since there were more than a dozen of it on this flying ship, and there was no need to equip it on the flying ship since it will not be participating in the battle, so why not just give it to the werewolves.

“Ah… for our great master! For love and justice! For the glory of God that will shine on the earth!” The strongest two-headed werewolf roared loudly at the isolation hatch. “Fight!!”

“Oh!!!”

The rest of the werewolves suddenly started roaring loudly, and their blood started boiling with ardor.

Galleon was left speechless inside the ship.

“What kind of information did I put into them? Love and justice? Do you think you are a Saint?”

The five two-headed wolf set off quickly and flew out of the isolation hatch. As though five small battle mechs, and rushed to the front of the battlefield.

Only then Garen had time to check his status after entering the Inherited Level.

‘Nonosiva Lin — Strength 34.1, Agility 22.2, Vitality 40, Intelligence 15.9, Potential 49983%. Soul limit 40.’

His vitality was maxed out!?

Garen was shocked and delighted.

His vitality was originally 24.8 and it skyrocketed after he reached Resonance Level, and now that he reached Inherited Level, it suddenly increased by that much. From what he knew, after the Energy Machinists of Planet Naga reach Inherited Level, their physical fitness would be significantly stunned, and it would be very difficult to increase it. They can only rely on various types of modified and fused rare materials to enhance themselves. However, they could only rely on non-living things to strengthen their bodies, rather strengthening their bodies by themselves. This might be the key to the fact that they had not surpassed the limit of the Perpetual Motioners.

In other words, they simply bypassed the soul limit, ignored the souls, and simply strengthened their body. This resulted in the imbalance, which might be the reason why they were not able to reach the strongest Regent Level.

“As of now, I am afraid that with only my body, I can withstand the attacks of Inherited Level Energy Machinist and not be injured!” Garen clenched his fist, and he felt the terrifying power that felt in the totem world appearing once again.

“The soul limit… It’s reaching soon. What path should I go next…?” Garen’s mood got a little heavy. If he were to take the mech path and merged with foreign objects, he might go on the usual path of the other Energy Machinists. However, this path was not able to break through the limit and reach the Regent Level. Whereas if he took the Ancient Endor route, it will take too long for the soul seed to concentrate. Although this path would enable him to achieve an undying true soul, the progress was way too slow.

The last route was the simulated Void Beast path, which was the Living Secret Hellfrost Peacock Technique path. This path will eventually lead to the formation of void creatures that belonged to secret technicians, and this route might be able to bypass the soul limit.

To form a void army which belonged to you.

“Perhaps, by practicing the Scarlet Snow Technique, I can reach the top, and forcibly concentrate the soul seed?”

Garen suddenly thought of this idea. As of now, he had two soul seeds, the Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique (blue), and the Holy Phoenix Demonic Book (golden-black). They were both secret techniques that he had practiced until he reached the top and formed through condensation.

But in fact, although both of the formed soul seeds were originally secret techniques, both of them were not top level techniques. The Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique itself was formed by the mutation of a fusion between the Hellfrost Peacock Technique and another hot-natured Living Secret Technique. However, due to its negative mutation, its level was actually lower than the Hellfrost Peacock Technique and was almost at the same level as the Scarlet Snow Technique. Whereas the actual Holy Phoenix Demonic Book was mostly originated from the core technique of the civilization where the underground Buddha Mother was located. However, because there were only parts of it and it was not completed, it could not be considered as high level too.

“From what it seems, even if it was not a top-level secret technique, it will still be able to form a soul seed. The key is to achieve a unique spiritual soul realm and make changes according to one’s own soul attribute. If that is really the case, then it will be easy!” Garen speculated.

“If I guessed correctly, then as long as I practice the Scarlet Snow Technique until it reaches the top, I might be able to also condense a soul seed that belongs to the Scarlet Snow Technique!”

Garen was speculating in his heart.

After all, compared to the previous few worlds, his strength had greatly exceeded his previous strength, as he had reached a terrifying 40 points in his vitality, which could be considered as a non-human category. When he was in the totem world, he might be injured only if he fully activated the abilities of the nine-headed dragon, and that was just a possibility. With a horrifying 40 vitality points, and the Inherited Level force field, as compared to the past, right at this moment, Garen might be in his prime!!

Chapter 1067: Civil War 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Flapping the black wings on their backs, the five Werewolves flew passed the merchant ships towards the forefront of the battlefield. They looked like small, inconspicuous dots compared to the few hundreds of battle airship mechs. It was as though five drops of ink dripped into an ink bottle without any noticeable changes.

Garen drove the flying ship and followed them closely behind. He stopped only when he caught up to the business alliance’s mothership.

His gaze was fixed at the five Werewolves, watching how they were going to perform. Soon, they approached a small torpedo ship.

Whoosh!!

Five lasers were being shot out almost concurrently.

The small torpedo ship exploded suddenly, turning into a soundless fireball. The explosion sound was not transmitted over due to the long distance.

However, Garen still felt the momentary shock caused by the explosion of the torpedo ship.

“Nice teamwork. As expected, they have completely changed after having wisdom…” He nodded in satisfaction.

He continued observing as the five Werewolves approached another laser ship. But this time, two mechs had its eyes on them.

The other party’s standard mechs were both red in color. Each of them had a number marking on the top. There was a horn on each of the mech’s head, making them look rather wild. Looking from afar, the two mechs quickly fought with the five Werewolves.

Soon, five lasers flashed several times, and the two mechs were destroyed.

The five Werewolves continued to advance forward, and gradually, the alliance’s mechs around them started working together with the werewolves.

With a Level Six inherited level force field protection, ordinary laser cannons will at most stagger them slightly, and will not be able to do any harm. Therefore, the alliance’s mechs used them as a shield and rushed straight towards their enemies.

They smashed into their opponent’s territory without any difficulties.

Holding laser cannons in their hands, the five Werewolves went around looking for tougher opponents, and soon, the pirate organization was being messed up, and they had no choice but to retreat unwillingly.

“It seems like no matter where he goes, Inherited Level will always be tyrannical…” Garen sighed. Both the Remora Business Alliance and the interstellar pirates only had one Inherited Level expert on their team. The rest of them who were fighting were all Resonance Level generals. Despite their wounding power were not that strong and had to rely on laser cannons, the five Werewolves appearance still made a great impact on the formation of their organization.

Hundreds of pirate ships and mechs were easily destroyed, and they were forced to retreat.

The entire battle was unusually easy, which made Garen realize the strength of Inherited Levels in space.

‘Dear Inherited Level energy machinist, thank you very much for your generous help. I am Lahu, the commanding officer of Remora Business Alliance. The General Manager of the Business Alliance, Miss Sandor wishes to invite you to board the mothership and use the jump portal together. ‘

The other party immediately said through the public channel. As compared to the previous flat tone they sounded much more respectful this time.

“The General Manager? The Inherited Level pilot that made a move just now?” Garen asked.

“Yes, Miss Sandor is also the daughter of the president of the Business Alliance. She is changing now and she has instructed us to prepare a sumptuous dinner for you, Sir. We hope that you will attend the dinner.” That man appealed in a humble tone.

“Okay then. Please get ready to tow my flying ship.” Garen’s original intention was to jump through a long distance with the mothership, as it would be difficult to get back with his small flying ship.

Soon, the mothership was processing the towing procedure and Garen’s entry.

After waiting for the return of the five Werewolves, the flying ships automatically made a half circle along the mothership and got into a small launcher on the side.

After passing through a long, black tunnel, blue spots of light gradually began to appear around the surrounding metal wall.

Flying into the innermost empty room, the isolation hatch behind lowered down. With a slam, a large amount of air flow was blown in to fill up the vacuum.

As the white mist diffused in the air, the air pressure quickly fell to the standard value.

Garen then only opened his flying ship’s hatch, leaving the five Werewolves in the flying ship. They have gotten too big and could no longer fit inside his Space Ring. Moreover, the environment of the Space Ring was extremely boring, and since they have become intellectual beings, Garen felt that it was not right to keep them like an object.

After walking out of the flying ship, Garen immediately saw the people who have arrived and was waiting for him.

The one who stood in front was a high-spirited woman with blonde hair. Her eyebrows were trimmed sharp, like two knives flying diagonally. Her eyes were sharp and cold. She was wearing a white T-shirt and washed-up jeans, which accentuated her perfect body figure. Those who stood behind her seemed to be her subordinates and senior pilots who fought in the battle. There were also a few people at the side dressed in various clothing, looking as if they also wanted to use the jump portal just like him.

As Garen walked out of the flying ship, the blonde hair woman was attracted by his tall, muscular build and rough temperament.

She voluntarily stepped forward to receive him.

“Hi, I’m Sandor, the General Manager of the Business Alliance, an Inherited Level pilot.” She reached out her hand.

Garen looked at her with a sincere look on his face and reached out his hand too.

“Garen, Inherited Level energy machinist.”

“Even though we suffered huge losses this time because of the pirates, it must be fate that brought all of us who are from different star regions and galaxy together. Please come with me, dinner is ready.”

A bald-headed man wearing glasses behind the woman said loudly.

“Please.” Sandor beckoned to Garen.

Only two of them were Inherited Level here, the rest of them were nothing to them. It was as though they were the main characters and the rest only had supporting roles.

Garen nodded and followed her into a tunnel leading to the inner warehouse.

Sandor walked side by side with Garen and introduced the surroundings to him. There was two energy machinist of the business alliance mothership, but both of them were only Middle Level and they have just reached Resonance Full Moon Level. Moreover, they were not in a sect, so they obviously cannot compare to energy machinists in a sect.

Just as Garen expected, all the energy machinists in a sect were all extremely wealthy, and they will not be willing to work for others. After Sandor finished introducing them, a man and a woman who seemed to be a couple walked out and saluted to Garen respectfully.

Dinner was scrumptious, and there were all kinds of basic fresh meats such as chicken, duck, and fish. There were also some rare fruits and some unknown cosmic meats. Sandor and Garen sat at a table by themselves. She was very curious about energy machinists, especially Inherited Level energy machinists, and it seemed as though she was not exposed to this level of information before.

“To be frank, the energy machinist that I came across with, hmm… how should I say this? All they were capable of were playing a supporting role or were in logistics. Their energy machinery control was dull and boring, and they do not have any fighting style which makes them very vulnerable. As such, most of those that I have met were hired for supporting roles. I hope that you are not offended by what I said. I’m a straightforward person, and I say what is on my mind and will not try to hide anything.” Sandor said so.

“No worries, I understand.” Garen nodded and said, “After all, most of us energy machinists are like that as we mainly focus on research behind closed doors. Therefore, it is normal for an energy machinist to be weaker in terms of fighting. It is like comparing an energy machinist and a pilot in terms of maintenance.”

He laughed.

“Most of the people perceived the same too, and that is they can only work in support and in auxiliary operations. But ever since I saw you that day, I have changed my perception. Moreover, the five Werewolves are absolutely not weaker than pilots. Plus, that kind of control is simply amazing,” Sandor said with admiration.

At this time, a small music band at the corner of the mothership restaurant started setting up a small stage. Soon, a melodious music was gradually played from a bagpipe, then, a harp and piano. A beautiful woman with platinum-colored hair and a good figure stood in the corner and began to sing.

‘The world once gave us happiness, but we did not cherish it. The world once gave us hope, but we turned it into disappointment. Peoples’ will are unpredictable and it often lies on their own inability to hold on to anything. Ah… listen to the sound of the wind, listen to the sound of rain falling down from the sky, intangible yet pure…’

The woman’s voice was soft, sweet, and very pleasant to the ear.

Garen lifted his glass and gently sipped on his amber-colored, alcoholic drink.

“Nice lyrics.”

“How is it? I wrote it.” Sandor said somewhat proudly.

Garen smiled and nodded.

“Remora Business Alliance is mainly engaged in the business of the human race biological techniques, so your market should be very wide, right?”

“Of course, our business alliance ranks 43rd among the human race, and we are now in the top 50. An ordinary King of the Planet might not necessarily be richer than us.” Sandor said proudly.

“I wonder if you have heard of a man named Chinande?” Garen asked casually, his heart was racing slightly.

The Wild Mutt Chinande, the Captain of the Light of Justice knights under the White King, who was the culprit who destroyed the entire group of energy machinist.

“Chinande? Are you talking about that Light of Justice Knight, Sir Chinande?” Sandor reacted immediately.

“Light of Justice?” Garen frowned slightly.

“I have heard that his territory is at the frontier of the star region, which almost wiped out the Finite People. He is the Commander-in-Chief of the Special Operations Forces. We are unworthy to have any relations with such a high and mighty man.” Sandor laughed bitterly. “Why are you asking about him?”

“It’s nothing. A friend of mine kept mentioning about this great man, so I asked out of curiosity.” Garen smiled casually.

The Light of Justice?

Haha…

Garen sneered coldly in his heart. The scene in the space diagram did not show that. The guy’s actual nickname should not be called the Light of Justice, but rabies! The greatest lackey of the White King! A loyal dog!

“I have a request here, an acquisition request. I don’t know if you can spare me some help.” He came back to his senses and asked.

“What is it? As long as I’m capable of, there is absolutely no problem!” Sandor laughed and said with alacrity.

Garen held out his hand out and his energy machinery imprint immediately projected a light screen on both of their sides, and soon the influence of the Staff of Absolute Yin appeared on the screen.

“Can you please help me publish a purchasing advertisement for this thing?”

“This? Isn’t it a holy tree branch? This is not something cheap, but we’ve got some stored in the business alliance. There is no need for advertising, how many do you need? Let’s see if we have enough here, and I will gift it to you!” Sandor replied cheerily.

“There is no need for that. The amount that I need might be a little big.” Garen shook his head. “I need one thousand holy tree branches, and they need to be as big as the one in the picture.”

“A thousand of it? That is indeed quite a number, but let me check all the storage, it should be barely enough.” Garen assumed that Sandor would say she did not have enough. But she only frowned and answered him casually, helping him to solve the problem which had long bothered him.

“Really?” Garen was stunned.

“I will not lie to you.” Sandor laughed. “It’s not easy to find these things, but for us, we should still have some in storage. After all, it can be crushed and used as a lubricating powder. It can also be used in the construction of the jump portal and Stargate.”

“If you are able to provide me with this material for a long period of time, I am willing to pay ten percent higher than the market price as a favor to the business alliance,” Garen replied with a low voice. Now that he had a high social status, he naturally need not have to care about money.

“What are you talking about? Do you think you would need to pay for these things?” Sandor could not care less about money. The business alliance was huge, and there were quite a number of Inherited Level subordinates there. However, during a dispute between major sects, even if she was the daughter of the President, she will need to find forces that will support her, and the Inherited Level energy machinist right in front of her might be a good choice. In her point of view, the profit of the tree branches was only worth a few thousand golden crystals, and it was simply not worth mentioning. It was just the price of a medium-sized merchant ship.

Garen understood what she meant and nodded.

Their conversation gradually got more harmonious. Since each of them has their own intentions, they got closer and sealed a deal. Sandor sold half and gifted half of the Staff of Absolute Yin to Garen. And at the same time, Sandor generously gifted a more advanced spaceship to Garen as a ceremonial gift in conjunction with their first meeting.

Garen understood what she meant. He left her his energy machinist signaling number and did a checkup service and maintenance for her personal mech. With that, their preliminary friendship was considered established.

Soon, the business alliance prepared to jump a long distance. Amazingly huge energy concentrated at the jumping engine, and suddenly in a burst, the mothership was launched forward.

Boom!!

The entire business alliance ship started a ripple, quickly penetrating into the invisible water and disappearing into the space of the universe.

Chapter 1068: Civil War 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Planet Scarlet Snow, over north of Sahar City.

A black submarine-like huge spaceship slowly emerged in the air. It was covered with faint silver light, an indication that it had just came back from space.

However, the people from the city below did not notice this ship. There was an invisible barrier above the mortal’s city, as such, they are unable to see anything from the outside world.

The spaceship turned around unwieldy and headed towards the Black Wolf Lair in Planet Scarlet Snow.

In the spaceship’s general control office, Garen was going through the information related to the spaceship.

The entire spaceship was 328 meters long and 189 meters wide. Considered as a small warship, it had an extraordinarily luxurious interior configuration.

The top floor had a restaurant, the general control office, event hall, swimming pool, an area each for logistics and entertainment, a cold storage area among the storage space, and a huge spaceship level engine. It can withstand a Level-Five heavy armor pressure. The Level-Five armor was a self-recirculating armor that cannot be broken by a Level-Five pilot who was controlling a mech. As long as the energy furnace is still running, it will not be destroyed.

This spaceship was still brand new and was extremely costly. Garen did not know exactly how much it would cost, but an ordinary small warship was worth tens of thousands of crystals, and this ship should be worth at least a few hundred thousands of crystals.

The entire spaceship could be used as a mobile living base, which was very convenient.

He had an urge to drive the spaceship and escape from the energy machinists’ reach and bring along his relatives to seek refuge. However, he was aware that the war between the Red King and the White King greatly affected the two huge races and countless star regions. It was impossible to avoid it. As a relative of Baylon, and the most important person to Baylon, the White King will definitely not let him go.

The spaceship landed swiftly on the Black Wolf Lair. Its massive presence attracted the attention of Scarlet Snow disciples and causing a commotion.

Such a big spaceship was rarely owned by anyone from the Scarlet Snow Sect. Everyone was using a miniature spaceship and only the top few disciples were using such a huge vehicle.

When they saw Garen stepping out of it, everyone was at ease. It was not an exaggeration for a tyrannical genius who was second to Carthage to possess such spaceship.

“Garen!”

With a swoosh sound, a slender figure appeared at the entrance of Garen’s spaceship.

It was Third Senior Sister, Eva, who had a furious look on her face.

“Was it you! Was it you who injured Aloran fatally!”

“Aloran?” Garen frowned slightly. “What are you talking about? Third Senior Sister.”

Eva was in a white dress, she had a short sword in her hand. She was trembling with rage.

“Drop the act!”

Swoosh!

A glaring blue light flashed, Eva suddenly struck with the sword. A terrifying energy condensed into a bundle of chill air seemed to have made the short sword look longer, and she swept it towards Garen’s waist.

A crashing sound was heard, but the elongated, blue light sword missed and caught onto nothing. It immediately froze the space where Garen was initially standing and instantly shattered it into innumerable pieces.

Garen’s figure appeared behind Eva.

“Third Senior Sister, I don’t understand what you are talking about. Aloran is fatally injured? But what does that have to do with me?”

“The wounds on her body was caused by a horrifying heat energy. Who else other than you is capable to use that technique in the Scarlet Snow Sect!?” Eva waved her light sword and attacked once again.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

Several bright, blue lights flashed consecutively. With his current physical fitness level alone, Garen would be able to crush Eva completely. She might have reached the Inherited Level, but her physical fitness was far weaker than that of Garen.

“Antlers! Light of Oblivion!!” Eva swerved around suddenly, and her Inherited Level force field quickly condensed into a majestic stag. As the stag lowered its head, dozens of blue light beams burst out of its antlers aiming towards Garen.

Each of these beams was black on the inside and blue on the outside, even the air that it passed through left behind traces of space cracks.

Eva was serious this time, as she was using an Inherited Level Strength of Origin Technique!

Bang!

A beam of light grazed through a withered tree on the Black Wolf Lair. Instantly, the tree exploded turning into countless pieces of crushed ice bullets.

Boom boom boom!!

All the places swept by the light beam exploded into a countless amount of white-blue crushed ice. All the crushed ice blasted violently with an Inherited Level force field and a bullet-like speed.

“Come!”

Eva shouted loudly, and there was a hint of murderous intention in her eyes.

“Since everything started because of me, then I will be the one to end this mistake!!” She seemed desperate and she had made up her mind.

Countless beams of light headed towards Garen, and it seemed like it all gathered around him concurrently.

From the view above, it looked like a large number of blue light beams were lunging extremely fast towards Garen.

Garen was about to dodge when he detected a faint, mysterious breath.

“Dual Prison Lock!”

He decided to not dodge the attack. Taking out the blue sword from its sheath on his waist, he drew a black circle around him with the sword’s black threads.

Chi chi chi chi…

Sounding like leaked air currents, all the blue light beams were destroyed and shattered in the air by Dual Prison Lock.

Chi!

However, a small piece of shattered ice carrying the terrifying Inherited Level force field heavily cut across Garen’s face. If he did not dodge his head in time, that piece will probably pierce through his head.

‘She’s serious in wanting to kill me…’

A trace of scarlet-colored blood flowed out of his wound. Garen reached out his hand to touch the wound, and the look in his eyes gradually got colder.

“Senior Sister, if you do not stop, I might retaliate…” He smiled eerily and coldly.

“You!!” Eva was a little stupefied. How long was he away for? He only left for a short while, and when he came back, he jumped from Resonance Level to Inherited Level! “How… how is it possible?”

“Nothing is impossible. I can’t help it if I’m a genius, can I?” Garen smiled. He covered the wound on his cheeks with his hand for a short moment before letting go. The wound had healed completely and disappeared.

“I don’t believe it!” Eva clenched her teeth. She felt that she had probably not used her full strength just now.

“Light of Oblivion!!” The stag force field appeared once again, and numerous blue light beams sieged towards Garen in the sky.

“It’s useless…” Garen held his sword by its handle.

“Slash!”

The Dual Prison Lock broke out momentarily, and the Black Thread Sword intertwined with the blue light beams, which looked like a mirage beside Garen. Numerous blue light beams shattered and disappeared into the air. The look on Garen’s face did not seem to change slightly, and he looked at Eva with a smile on his face.

“Long time no see, Senior Sister… it seems like you have gotten weaker…”

The cold wind blew towards them and rolled up a subtle cyclone. But the chill in Eva’s heart was colder than the wind.

“I don’t believe it! I don’t believe it!!!”

“Light of Oblivion!!”

A sky full of blue light beams appeared once again and sieged towards Garen from all directions.

This was Eva’s most powerful technique. It was promoted by the Twelve Grade Scarlet Snow Technique, along with a trace of the Strength of Origin, and combined with all her energy machineries’ resonance. This time, she used everything that she had. She even removed the protective Inherited Level force field and used it for the attack.

Boom!!

Suddenly, a figure was being knocked out.

It was not Garen, but Eva.

She did not know when did Garen left from where he was standing to appear before her.

“Senior Sister, do you not understand what I meant? I didn’t say that I’ll be standing still for you to attack…” Garen smiled and looked at Eva from above, who was thrown down leaving a long dragging indentation on the ground.

Burgh.

Eva spat a mouthful of blood and tried to get up, but she could barely move.

“How can you be so rude to your Senior Sister?” Suddenly, a deadly flat voice was heard coming from beside him.

Carthage slowly appeared on Garen and Eva’s left side. He had a sword in his hand, and nobody knew when he appeared standing there.

“Wounding your Senior Sister is a sin, and it is disrespectful. Apologize to her quickly.” Carthage said with an apologetic tone, but there was not a trace of sincerity.

“I’m really sorry, Senior Sister Eva.” Garen suddenly laughed. “I accidentally missed, and wounded you… but who can you blame when you’re so weak? I thought that…”

He did not continue talking and walked to Carthage’s side. He originally intended to secretly send a message to Eva to explain, but then he felt a hint of Carthage’s presence and stopped doing so instantly.

“Let’s go, it’s time to head back.” Carthage glanced at Garen, and a black whirlpool from his eyes instantly appeared. A horrifying invisible presence encircled Garen immediately.

Garen’s shook. This presence… it had exceeded Inherited Level, it was Non-Falling Level!

Although he was not affected by this presence due to his 40 vitality points, Garen quickly adjusted his body and put up an act that he was being slightly suppressed. When it came to disguising his vital energy, there was no one better than him, who had trained secret techniques for many years.

He could not make a move now, as he still did not have any clues about Carthage’s trump card and his level of strength. As such, he absolutely cannot make a move. Even if he was able to defeat him now, Garen still would not make a move, as he intended to get more information regarding the behind-the-scenes contents of the energy machinist extinction.

The perpetual motioners might be involved in the energy machinist extinction, and they were not something that he was able to fight against now.

At that moment, because of the commotion caused by their fierce battle, someone rushed over from a distance.

“It’s Senior Sister Eva’s disturbance! Quick!”

“Hurry up! Senior Sister seems to be injured. Her energy machinery imprint is damaged!”

There was a sound coming from afar.

“Let’s go.”

Carthage turned and strode towards the distance. He seemed to be moving slowly, but in fact, he was walking at a very fast pace.

Garen followed closely behind him, and the two of them came across four to five men who were walking in an opposite direction. Seeing them, the men stopped momentarily with a nervous look on their face.

“Senior Brother, Ca…Carthage!” A boy wearing spectacles stood up reluctantly and greeted.

“All you do is scare these little guys? Carthage.” A woman dressed in a white robe slowly descended from the air. She was the rank number two Second Senior Sister, Alice, who was also Rainy’s sister.

“Alice? I’m just wandering around casually, and to welcome the return of my Junior Brother. As disciples of the sect, how could you say such hurtful words?” Carthage smiled and answered calmly.

Garen could feel how highly tensed the presence around Alice was. It was obvious that she feared Carthage a lot.

“Rainy is dead,” Alice said suddenly, Garen’s heart shivered. “I just found out about it. She was pierced by an iron baton and her blood was drained. She was hung at the entrance of Junior Brother Garen’s Black Wolf Lair.”

Garen’s heart tightened, and his highly concentrated spiritual energy was fixed on Carthage.

He had told Aloran to let Senior Sister Rainy go…! It was him!!

He closed his eyes slightly and slowly tightened his grip on the handle of his sword.

Chapter 1069: Fusion 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The wind blew passed them lightly. Carthage and Alice could vaguely feel the cyclone flowing between them. It was an obscure Qi’s Dynamic battle.

“If there is nothing, I would like to leave now.” Carthage smiled flatly.

“As a former Senior Brother of Rainy, could it be that her death has not affected you at all?” Alice’s voice got colder.

“With the mistakes she made, Rainy herself was a sinner. Her death was for the best.” Carthage replied calmly. He ignored Alice, turned around and walked away.

Garen followed behind him. He stopped for a short while and glanced at Alice, not saying anything. Then, he continued to follow Carthage.

There was a growing sense of urgency in his heart. Garen knew without a doubt that Carthage killed Rainy, but he was not sure if Carthage knew that it was him who released Rainy. If Carthage guessed that he was the one who intercepted him that night, it would be troublesome…

Garen gripped the handle of his sword tightly. He did not know what his chances of winning Carthage were. On the surface, this guy looked like he was only at Inherited Level, but his actual combat strength was at Non-Falling Level, and he might have more hidden secrets!

But one thing for sure was that he absolutely dare not make a move here!

Garen made up his mind and walked faster to keep up with him.

They passed by a vast, plain grassland and entered a dense, pine forest with some scattered snow foam.

The lush green pine forest was quiet. From time to time, some winter squirrels could be seen crouching around and the both of their movements scared the squirrels to scurry around.

Suddenly Carthage stood still in an open space, his back facing Garen.

“Do you know why I came suddenly to see you?” His voice was as flat as usual, as though he was just talking about something as simple as the weather today.

“Why?” Garen stood still and asked in a low voice.

Carthage turned around.

“I can give you a shot, but only once.”

He knew it!

Garen was shocked, even after Aloran had sent Rainy to somewhere as far as the Four-Star Alliance, he was still able to get her.

No! He might just be testing! If he really knew it, he would not say it out loud, he would have just made a move straight!

Garen immediately came back to his senses. Was he trying to cheat him?

“I don’t understand what you are talking about?” He said, frowning with a dubious look on his face.

Carthage did not say a word, only staring at Garen quietly.

Garen looked at him in the eyes without fear. Many people often have the illusion that a person’s eyes will never lie. Carthage also had such a deluded logic, so when he saw Garen’s clear and dubious eyes, it made him question his speculations.

“You should know how to handle stuff by yourself, as there are many things and situations.”

“What are you talking about? I do not understand?” Garen’s brows frowned deeper.

Carthage also started frowning slightly, but he quickly relaxed. A black-red bead appeared in his hands. With a light flick, the beads suddenly shot outwards and accurately floated in the air right in front of Garen.

“This is for you, eat it. This thing played a big role in you being able to break through into Inherited Level.”

This again?

Garen knew that there was something wrong with this bead. Although he did not know what trick was hidden in it, he was confident that his Hellfrost Peacock will be able to handle any tricks. All he needed to do was swallow it directly.

He quickly grabbed the bead and gulped it.

Boom!!

The energy of this bead was much stronger than the previous one!

Garen felt as though he had swallowed a piece of searing iron and it was burning his stomach. A piercing discomfort suddenly erupted from his stomach.

Ugh…

He did not try to hold the pain and grasped his abdomen.

Seeing Garen’s reaction, the doubts in Carthage’s eyes vanished.

“This is a blood bead essence, which can stimulate your body’s maximum potential and is able to increase your overall strength without harm. One of it is equivalent to a year’s worth of hard work.” He paused. “As long as your performance satisfies me, I will consider increasing the supply of the blood bead essence for you.”

Garen felt that the bead once again tried to pollute his body with that strange blood-color, but was being devoured spontaneously by the peacock technique, and in just a short while, it had completely gobbled up the red color.

The discomfort in his stomach disappeared, but Garen continued to act as if he was still in pain.

“When you’re stronger, go and put an end to all your previous grudges,” Carthage concluded, turned around and left.

With his eyes closed, Garen was still holding onto his abdomen as he inhaled deeply. He only straightened himself a few minutes after Carthage left.

“Non-Falling Level… he’s really powerful…”

He recalled the time when Senior Sister Rainy mentioned the Mirror of True Techniques Realm.

Oneness, Water Mirror, Silver Mirror, and lastly the Perpetual Motioner Level board realm. He was now at the Water Mirror Level, but he was sure that Carthage was definitely at a Water Mirror Level, or even a Silver Mirror Level.

Among the Scarlet Snow Sect, there were only a few people who were aware of the Mirror of True Techniques, which was Alice, Rainy, Carthage, and himself. But of course, this was on the disciple level, he did not know if the elders knew about it or not. However, it was unlikely that they do not know about. After all, they have lived for so many years, and regardless of how they trained, they should be able to reach that level by now.

Other than that, he did not have to worry about the rest of them, including Eva.

“That said, however, the Ancient Endor Demon Lord does not have any partition for realms. They were using a pure strength route. Maybe I can try to follow this path?” He recalled some basic knowledge that Black Seth had mentioned, and it was true that the Ancient Endor did not discover this area of knowledge. They focused their energy more on souls. As for their bodies, it was just a vessel to them.

Condense their soul seed to form a true soul! This was the path of the Ancient Endor.

The more souls, the stronger one will be, and the closer they were to immortality. The stronger their talent abilities were, the greater their strength. By using souls to activate life force, one can make changes to all things and even rules. This was how they evolved.

He was feeling the continuous, astonishing surge of energy seeping out of the blood bead into his body. This energy was being consumed insanely and converted into the purest cold energy to be supplied to the Scarlet Snow Technique.

Chi…

The blood bead dissolved completely and disappeared.

According to Carthage’s estimate, it will take a full six months to fully absorb the blood bead, but in just a few minutes, it was being absorbed by Garen in a full energy efficient way. Moreover, as compared to the others, who can only utilize half of its energy, Garen was able to utilize twice the high amount of energy!

He even completely devoured the manipulative blood-color tricks and transformed it into energy supplies for the Scarlet Snow Technique.

Poof!

A rage of cold air diffused out of Garen’s body uncontrollably and instantly froze all the pine trees around him into icicles. The white cold air spread rapidly, but it seemed to have begun to shrink.

It was changing constantly by expanding outwards and contracting inwards as if two forces antagonizing each other.

After a long time, Garen finally opened his eyes slowly. He instantly withdrew all the cold air around him and kept it back into his body.

The origin crystal of the Scarlet Snow Technique in his body became reddish once again.

“I’ve reached the thirteenth grade… that was fast!”

He himself felt that it was unbelievable. According to records, after reaching Inherited Level with Scarlet Snow Technique, it will take graded years to advance onwards from the twelfth grade, and that was using a super quick genius as a benchmark.

And now, how long have Garen reached the Inherited Level? And he actually improved and reached the thirteenth grade.

However, after he sensed his the interior of his body, the blood bead that he swallowed just now was completely gone, and there was only a little residue left of the devoured energy. The sudden breakthrough used up most of his reserved energy.

“No wonder that it takes such a long time to break through a grade, the amount of energy needed is humongous…”

He glanced at his newly changed attribute pane. With the improvement of the Scarlet Snow Technique, his computing power was starting to not be able to keep up, and the energy machinery imprint continuously transmitted a swelling sensation. It was as though something might erupt and explode inside him.

He knew that it was a sign that he was losing control when his computing power could no longer keep up with his power.

At this point, changes were made to the attribute pane once again.

‘Nonosiva Lin – Strength 39.1, Agility 27.2, Vitality 40, Intelligence 16.2, Potential 49983%. Soul limit 40.’

His strength increased by five points, agility increased by five points, his vitality was maxed out, and his intelligence had the least increase, with only a 0.3 points increase.

“According to the normal logic, I should look for foreign objects to be fused together and then absorb it into my body, to improve my vitality, but such a path…” Galleon exhaled slightly.

Finally, he took a look at his soul limit. He will need to implement the condensation of a new soul seed as soon as possible.

He left the pine forest and soon returned to his Black Wolf Lair. He released the Winter Night Wolves to patrol the territory, as he himself sat in the central office and began to pick out new secret techniques he had previously acquired from the Blue Frost sect.

Among all the secret techniques that he got, only two of them might be able to condense into a soul seed. However, it was not a matter of ranking. The peak realm requires a special kind of acknowledgment and realm that was different from that of the previous soul seeds, which was the most critical part.

Garen’s current intelligence had reached 16 points. Due to the rules of this world, it did not derive the Doublecast technique of the Totem World, but the amazing computing power alone was already very strong.

Nine Layers Body Shattering Technique, and Destructive Impact Fist.

Both of them were chosen because it perfectly fit Garen’s current fighting style. The Body Shattering Technique was used for quenching the body and the surrounding force field. After mastering it successfully, it can activate up to nine layers of terrifying powerful defense, and no matter how one’s opponent was to strike, they will not be able to break through it.

The Destructive Impact Fist seemed to be the perfected evolutionary version of the Multiple Speed Fix that Garen once comprehended. It was twice to eighty-eight times of the horrifying fist pressure, and no one had ever trained this type of fist techniques to its highest level, because its practice requires extreme physical support. This was not the fake physique made by fusion of an energy machinist and other stuff, but a true and completely strong physique that belonged to one, which can be perfectly controlled.

The Nine Layers Body Shattering Technique had nine levels, and the Destructive Impact Fist had a total of eight levels. Both of which were secret techniques that were sufficient to be used to create a new sect.

But of course, this type of Secret Technique was the same level as the Scarlet Snow Technique, but because of all kinds of stringent requirements for its practice, many of the Inherited Level energy machinists were destroyed, and in the end, the secret techniques fell into his hands.

But even so, there was no one in the Blue Frost Sect who practiced both of these unpopular secret techniques, because both of its requirements were too high.

Whereas the reason why Garen picked both of them was that they suited him.

Chapter 1070: Fusion 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The requirement for the Nine Layers Body Shattering Technique was accumulation. It had a massive energy accumulation that was even more terrifying than the Scarlet Snow Technique and this secret technique had once used up all the money of a medium-sized sect. This was a case where the owner of the sect was practicing this technique on his own and he only got as far as the fifth grade. Therefore, it was only natural that no one wanted to train in this technique. No matter how rich an Energy Machinist was, they dare not simply practice such an expensive technique.

As for Garen, it was different. The biggest difference between him and an average person was that he could consume close to 100% energy and make use of most of the energy while others could only absorb at most 50% of the energy. This saved him half of the expenses. In addition to that, his peacock technique would not reject anything and was able to eat everything! Even if it was highly toxic, as long as it had energy, it would be absorbed. Therefore, many highly radioactive energy wastes that were useless to others could be used by Garen.

He had decided to choose both of the secret techniques as a foundation to improve his Scarlet Snow Technique and immediately began train all day and night.

The fixed supply of food provided by the sect was way too little. He needed to swallow exactly a thousand units of energy every day. It was the kind of ore that had not been extracted and the residue of the ores that he had digested piled up into a small hill.

Energy ores, all kinds of high-energy crystals, high-energy medicines, and other scraps. As long there was energy, Garen would eat anything with his Devourer Ability.

However, the energy of these things were not even close to the blood bead that Carthage had given him. That blood bead alone enabled him to directly break through a stage of the Scarlet Snow Technique, and that made him miss the time when he swallowed the two blood beads.

Since his computing power could no longer keep up, he could only forcibly promote his exercises so that it would increase his computing power and intelligence. After all, Garen had no other way.

After an attribute reached 10 points, it required more than a 100 potential points to increase the attribute by one point, and he currently had 500 potential points. In fact, he only had 498 points, which was simply not enough to increase his attribute points. Moreover, if he used it all now, what would he do in the future? He might need much more later on.

Therefore, using Superimposition Secret Techniques to forcibly improve his Scarlet Snow Technique was the way to go. It was also the most traditional way of practicing, and all the Energy Machinists in Planet Naga were doing the same.

After all, intelligence was a natural gift, other than Garen, no one was able to directly promote it…

However, just as Garen was concentrating on his training, there was a problem at the Four-Star Alliance.

**********************

Four-Star Alliance, Planet Gideon, night.

On the edge of a broken bridge across the canyon, in the middle of a small piece of open space, Klaibe and Baylon were sitting by a bonfire. They were roasting two small rodents on top of the bonfire and applied oil on it from time to time. The roasted rodents were giving off a faint meaty aroma.

Both of them were drooling as they had their eyes fixed on the roasted rodents.

By this time, they were no longer as clean and tidy as when they first arrived. They were dirty, and many parts of their clothes were torn. Their faces had gotten gray and they looked like beggars who were asking for food.

“This is the last bit of food left,” Klaibe said as he stared at the rodents greedily and his stomach started grumbling.

“There are a lot of rodents on this planet… it’s everywhere…” Klaibe gulped.

“Of course,” Red Moon suddenly popped out of nowhere and said. “The biggest hobby of the Gideon family is to keep rodents! They themselves are the biggest rodent nests, and it will be odd if there aren’t many rats here. That is why they are known as the Gideon Rodents.”

“Oh yeah, where did the sound that we heard previously come from?” Klaibe asked curiously.

“I don’t know, but everything that happens on this planet should be related to the Gideon Family, since this is their planet,” Red Moon explained.

“Now that both of you can’t activate my accessory armor, you will just be killing yourself if you go to another place. All you can do now is to find me a pair of wings in this place, only then you can gain power by using my accessory mech. This is why the Royal Star is so troublesome. The both of you obviously had a mech with an Inherited Level bursting power, but now, the both of you are just two extremely weak ordinary humans. At most, you have greater strength and better imitation ability as compared to ordinary humans…”

“There is no other way. After all, we have reached a level where many pilots cannot reach even after many years of hard work. It is normal to pay this price,” Baylon smiled. “Moreover, didn’t you say that the difference between the both of us compared to ordinary pilots and Energy Machinist, was that they needed to reach Level Seven in Non-Falling Level to be able to fuse mechs, but we only need to reach Level Six, as long as we find the right mech core. Then, we can fuse it into our body and use it for the Reagent Level Resonance when the time comes. This is to enable us to detect and comprehend so that we can make up for this imperfection.”

“Indeed. During my prime, finding a few cores wasn’t a problem, but now… this is my only hope,” Red moon sighed.

“Actually, if you think about it, Royal Star is really scary… All he had to do was follow the training method that Boss Red Moon gave him to continuously improve, and he quickly reached a very high level. Although there is a drawback if he took off his mech, which would dramatically decrease his strength, but after he reached the Inherited Level and fused with a mech core, he was able to make up for this weakness. After fusing his own body with a mech, it substantially increased the strength of his body. This world… is really unfair…” Klaibe sighed.

“No, this is why the world is fair,” Red Moon said calmly. “I am at the Reagent Level and I can help Royal Star grow really quickly because it is based on the level that I am at, which is the Reagent Level. In fact, when Royal Star was leveling up, he mostly depended on the accumulation of the Reagent Level. The previous generation’s hard work resulted in this difference by passing on their accumulation to their next generation. It’s that simple.”

“For example, there are two families. One of them, since their grandfather’s generation, they had worked harder than the other family, and this resulted in the gap. And after that, even their father’s generation worked harder than the other family, which resulted in a bigger gap. Therefore, the third generation naturally have a large gap compared to the other family, because of their previous two generations. This is fair. Otherwise, all the hard work of the previous two generations will go to waste and both families’ third generation will be at the same level which would be truly unfair,” Red Moon explained.

“That makes sense,” Both Klaibe and Baylon nodded. “This is indeed the case. To put it simply, not that it’s unfair, just that your ancestors did not work as hard as other people’s ancestors. Therefore, there’s a gap between the accumulations.”

“And luck is also one of the factors,” Baylon added.

“Yeah, luck is…” Red Moon was hurt. “My luck was really bad that year…”

Klaibe could not help but say, “Actually… to be honest, even if you were not injured that year, you would not withstand one hit… So please just move on.”

“Are you trying to comfort me or start a fight!!?” Red Moon became angry from embarrassment.

“There’s someone!!” Suddenly, the tone of Red Moon changed. “He’s quick! Let’s hide! Quick!!”

Just when Klaibe and Baylon stood up, they heard a ghostly scream from Red Moon, and then he suddenly disappeared.

At the same time, the fire at the bonfire started burning violently. A tall black metal mech appeared right in front of them.

“A mech! Why is there a mech in this place!!?” Klaibe was dumbfounded. Planet Gideon was empty for a few years, and their Planet’s jump portal and wormhole were destroyed. Even their inverse space had a terrifying space storm, so no one was able to enter, and they got in using a special way. How was it possible for people to be in such a huge planet??

However, he did not know that Planet Gideon was not completely sealed. At least the only survivor of the Gideon Family, White Night was able to enter and leave this place through a teleportation array.

The mech that suddenly appeared was four meters tall. Although it was considered short among the five to six-meter tall standard mechs, the unique part of it was that a black huge sword was stuck in the entire body of the mech and black blood marks could be seen around the edge of the sword.

The entire mech looked like a bloated astronaut as it had large and rounded limbs as if oval-shaped balls were being stringed together. It had a black body and a head with faint blue light.

“Discovered humans… begin to arrest,” the mech stood still for a moment, scanned through Klaibe and Baylon and said with a mechanical tone.

“We are just interstellar adventurers that fell into this planet!” Klaibe shouted and raised his hands to show that he was harmless.

But unfortunately, the mech ignored him. With a ‘swoosh’, it instantly appeared right before Klaibe and Baylon and caught the both of them.

The both of them were being held in their hands and they gave up on resisting.

The both of them without their mechs were just a little stronger than an average person. While facing a speed-type mech, it would be foolish to retaliate.

Neither Klaibe nor Baylon were fools. They immediately gave up on resisting and allowed the mech to catch them, one in each hand. Then it jumped into the air and flew towards the distant bridge.

“Spirit number 109 found two humans. Rank determination, ordinary people; unconscious forces and harmless units.”

The black mech continuously produced a mechanical sound while flying mid-air, and it seemed to be communicating.

“Drop them into the mining slavery group,” a woman’s cold voice was heard coming from the other side.

This surprised both Klaibe and Baylon, there was actually someone here!

“Be careful… This is a spirit mech from the ancient times. It is extremely fast and it will nearly negate half of the damage caused by physical attacks. It is very troublesome!” Only then, Red Moon’s voice was heard. “Fortunately it is a broken version, otherwise, even I will be discovered. It seems like someone discovered the remains of a spirit mech, but do not understand how its technology works.”

“Are you all right, Boss Red Moon?” Klaibe asked softly.

“I’m all right, but both of you need to be careful. Without your mechs, you are no different from ordinary people. Just wait for the right opportunity and do not be impatient,” Red Moon warned.

“Understood.”

“As long as you don’t reveal your identities, you are worth nothing to them.”

Garen was quietly sitting at the center of his mansion and his body was emitting a dense white cold air. The cold air was almost like tails that constantly waved around Garen.

Looking from afar, it was as though the cold white air was a living creature which constantly moved around in the center of the mention, as if a spirit, and it was extremely odd.

Garen was dressed in black clothing and he was sitting there with his eyes closed. A dead tree around him was being frozen into a huge icicle, and the walls of the yard around him were covered with a thick layer of ice. The ground was also completely covered by a layer of ice, and the entire mansion had completely become an ice world.

In the sky, a flying white bird accidentally flew slightly lower, and it immediately rushed upwards due to the snow white cold air. The mansion was like a giant bird which accurately caught on the bird by lifting its head slightly and gobbled up the bird. The flying bird quickly turned into a block of ice and dropped onto the ground of the backyard.

A ‘crash’ sound was heard, as though a broken glassware, the flying bird broke into countless pieces of ice shards. But strangely, no blood was found on the ice pieces, as if all the flesh and blood had dried up and turned into a pale white.

All of a sudden, Garen opened his eyes.

“I’ve finally completed….”

After combining the Hellfrost Peacock’s Cold Chaos and Devourer Force Field Ability with the Scarlet Snow Technique’s Cold Inherited Level force field, it formed an extremely strong Cold Territory.

This type of Cold Territory can devourer any living creatures with vital energy through freezing them. At the same time, it can also freeze any foreign object and digest it completely.

A white light flashed in Garen’s eyes, and suddenly, a large stone at the side of the ground that was covered in cold air had a stiff and firm ice layer on the surface. While it was being covered in cold air, the stone began to shrink at a speed that was visible to the naked eye.

In less than half a minute, that piece of meter long white stone completely disintegrated from an ice cube into stone powder. The extremely little organic substances and energy in it were being absorbed by Garen.

“Any living creature that I have frozen will fall into a mental chaos that is twice as strong as the original Cold Chaos. Then, they will be in a complete despair and will lose any will to fight,” Garen himself did not know how strong this new territory was, because there was no reference. However, he knew that within this territory, those who were nearer to him would need to withstand a greater pressure, freezing pressure, chaotic despair pressure, and their vital energy being devoured.

“It is now not appropriate to call it Cold Chaos. Let’s change it into a simpler name, Faded Creation.”

This name was very appropriate. It engulfed, froze and caused despair, which was the exact meaning of Faded Creation.

Chapter 1071: Snatch 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“There is a mission that I require you to head out to.”

As Garen was training on his own, the Elder’s voice traveled around the Black Wolf Mansion.

“First Elder,” Garen stood up and bowed slightly to pay his respect.

“The Blue Frost Sect has perished… I want you to investigate and search for any clues. Furthermore, I want you to kill a renegade of the Dragon Light Sect along the way as a way of lending them a hand,” the first elder’s tone was rather strict and he was clearly shaken by the massacre of the Blue Frost Sect.

Garen lowered his head slowly.

“Understood. When should I leave?”

“The sooner the better and it’s best if you can stay hidden. Once you’ve returned, I will reward you with a piece of Secret Frost Seed’s Inspiration.”

“A Secret Frost Seed? Alright,” Garen replied as he assessed his current situation. He had been absorbing a lot of items but the gap between him and the Fourteenth Grade of Scarlet Snow Technique was still very wide apart. The Fourteenth Grade was the so-called Non-Falling Level.

The biggest obstacle between the Inherited Level and the Non-Falling Level was to form a wheel, a Crystal Wheel. It could be formed by using the Inherited Level’s source and form the crystals in the shape of a wheel. The more crystals one collected, the stronger one’s strength became.

This was the so-called Non-Falling Level, where the wheels kept perpetuating on its own, producing endless energy. It was completely different from the techniques and Willpower from before where it could be exhausted.

The Secret Frost Seed item seemed to contain a very huge amount of energy. Perhaps it could…

“Looks like I’ll be heading out. The supplies given by the Sect aren’t enough for me to absorb and I won’t be able to create the wheel of the Non-Falling Level,” Garen cut off the first elder’s communication as he looked around his garden which was filled with powder debris. They were all useless trash which contained no energy. This was his result for the past few days.

“Fortunately the Nine Layers Body Shattering Technique has been learned, but the skill with the fastest progress is still the Destructive Impact Fist.”

Garen reached out his right hand.

“One Time Fist Pressure.”

Whoosh!!

A strong wind gusted around him with him as the epicenter.

Garen as the epicenter, the surrounding area spanned hundreds of meters away in the mansion had uniformly sunk down at least ten centimeters.

Garen experienced the intense pressure in the area. It was the strength of the static pressure within the vicinity which increased by multiple multitudes. The items within the Pressure Fist’s area of effect would experience an extremely strong pressure. This was the Destructive Impact Fist.

“Two Times Fist Pressure,” Garen said calmly.

Boom!! Boom boom boom!!

In an instant, the items around him started exploding, including the big ice pillar tree which exploded into debris as they landed on the ground.

The air whistled as it seemed to have formed into a solid glue hundreds of meters around Garen.

Garen then quickly put away his Pressure Fist as the pressure which was double its original was almost enough to destroy his entire garden. The Destructive Impact Fist was definitely a fist technique most suited for people with high vitality. With his current physical attribute, it was as if a fish was introduced to the water as he was able to reach the tenth layer, the Ten Times Pressure Fist from the very beginning.

“This Secret Technique is literally tailored for me. Perfect!” Garen said excitedly as he looked at the mess around him. As he was too lazy to clean it up, he walked out of the garden and headed towards the small Flying Ship since he had to go there covertly.

The biggest obstacle to mastering the Destructive Impact Fist was to have enough Vitality. This was only the foundation as the future pieces of training were very similar to self-torture. With every increment in the Fist Pressure, the user’s body would become much denser and at the same time would suffer great injury to the point of near death. Perhaps a typical person wouldn’t dare practice this technique as they might not be able to recover from such heavy injury every time. Even if they were able to recover, there would be many hidden injuries that technology wouldn’t be able to fix. However, this was not the case for Garen.

He had potential points, which could perfect restore his physical body. This was the reason why he stated that this Secret Technique was created for him.

Once one reached the Tenth Grade, the Ten Times Pressure Fist would have ten times more self-destructive power. It was the pure increment of the fist’s strength to the limits. It also represented the practitioner’s strength which had been increased by tenfold.

**************

Garen went on to attend Senior Sister Rainy’s funeral before he departed. The corpse had already been taken off but the face and flesh were in a complete mess as it was obvious that she was tortured to death.

The cold corpse was placed inside an ice coffin which was surrounded with decorative white flower crystals. The coffin was being slowly placed into the ice tomb just behind the Scarlet Snow Sect.

Garen covered his face as he stood among the crowd, looking at Rainy’s coffin being buried. He was at a loss for words.

Although Rainy didn’t give him much guidance, she was also one of the few who didn’t have any ill intention towards him. Her death and funeral made Eva hate him even more as she stared at him to the point where it seemed as if she was about to kill him.

No one dared to go near Garen as they were not willing to interact with someone who was ungrateful. His reputation had really sunk into the abyss.

Garen stood outside of the Ice Cemetary as he looked at Rainy’s burial from afar. He placed his hand softly on his sword without saying a word.

“Despite her being a criminal to my Scarlet Snow Sect, she was still without a doubt who contributed a lot to my Sect when she was still alive,” The Second Elder, who was Rainy’s teacher, was the only elder who attended the funeral.

Carthage and the remaining two elders didn’t attend the funeral.

The other Three Hearted Disciples had fully arrived.

“Go back to the cosmo peacefully,” the master of ceremony sang loudly.

The Second Elder sighed as he turned around and left the area slowly. He patted Eva’s shoulder without saying a word before he left.

Eva’s eyes were red and tears started flowing down as she could not hold it in anymore. Aloran then immediately walked towards her and held onto her hand tightly.

“Why are you here! You ungrateful man! Pfft!!”

Salivas were spat at Garen’s face but they were blocked off by an invisible field. The salivas then turned into ice cubes before landing on the ground.

Garen looked at where the noise came from and saw a few young men and women. The one who spat saliva at him was no other than the golden-haired Hong Guo, who was standing at the front and beside him was Conan and a weak youngster.

All three of them were younger than seventeen years old. They were all staring at him with an unfriendly expression.

Rainy was the most important person to them.

Garen kept quiet for a while before speaking up.

“Are you the one who inherited the Secret Frost Seed?” He looked at Hong Guo, the youngster who didn’t intend to hide his hatred towards him.

According to the intel, he should be Senior Sister Rainy’s grandson.

However, he was currently very weak…

Garen started laughing.

“How can you prove that I am the one who killed Rainy? You can’t simply make up stuff kid. Be wary of what you say…”

Whoom!!

A powerful Energy Field was pressed onto them. In that instant, the sound of bones cracking could be heard from the three of them. Their faces turned red and kneeled down on the ground due to the intense pressure.

“Damn it!! Ahh!!!” Hong Guo shouted in anger as he tried to stand up with all of his might. As he exerted a huge amount of force, his knees exploded and blood started flowing out from them.

However, he did resist Garen’s pressure.

Perhaps the others were inspired by his courage or they were as strong as him. The short golden-haired girl and Conan didn’t kneel down even though her bandages had broken apart and blood started to stain her entire body.

“Interesting,” Garen smiled as he started to increase the energy field.

Pew! A white line suddenly drew across the air and went towards his face.

Clang!!

As the white line was approximately half a meter away from Garen, it completely lost its momentum and dropped to the ground.

It was Garen’s Condensation Energy Field, which was a passive technique that had been greatly enhanced due to his Inherited Level Willpower. If this Defensive Energy Field could only be extended half a meter away from his body, Hong Guo and the other two might not be able to get within a hundred meter range of Garen.

The white line was shot by Aloran from afar. Her gaze was as cold as ice as she walked in big steps and stood in front at Hong Guo and the others.

“What are you doing bullying these kids!?”

As Hong Guo shouted earlier, he had already attracted the attention from Eva and the others. The Second Elder’s pupils were staring at Garen as if he was an enemy.

Garen shrugged as he put away his Energy Field.

“I was only standing here.”

“Get lost!” Eva walked towards him and shouted.

Garen maintained his smile as he looked at the crowd before turning around and leaving the area quietly. He didn’t care whether the others knew the truth or understood him.

Whatever he had done had not betrayed his own conscience. The friendship between him and Eva, her effort in raising him into a Three Hearted Disciple, her care towards him. He would return all of this favor eventually.

He was not able to save Rainy’s life but he might able to return the favor by helping these three kids.

Although he had been isolated by everyone, had he really mixed himself with anybody from the beginning until the end?

He had already gotten used to such a lifestyle.

***************

It was time for him to leave for his mission.

The Dimensional Tunnel was already opened and the teams assigned to this mission had already been arranged beforehand. Garen was in the Frost Hell as he attempted to be inspired by the Secret Frost Seed when he received the notification. Unfortunately, since the distance was rather far away, he was unable to touch the Secret Frost Seed. Hence, he didn’t really obtain any huge reward but instead the only thing he gained was a surface knowledge of the strength and characteristics of the Scarlet Snow Sect’s ancestors. Perhaps this knowledge would be useful to those who had not decided their path. However, this knowledge was completely useless to the current Garen.

Hence, he left the Frost Hell and rode the Flying Ship and went towards the gathering point the moment he received the call.

As he drove the Flying Ship to the Dimensional Tunnel, he analyzed his own body.

Although there were no changes in his Vitality Attribute, he could feel that there were no changes in his defense, toughness and hardness as well. It seemed that his starting point, being having 40 points of Vitality was so overwhelming that he could resist the body’s increasing density caused by the Ten Times Pressure Fist.

This also meant that he had not reached the limits of the Destructive Impact Fist and could still increase the pressure of his Pressure Fist.

The Flying Ship soon arrived at an icy field and there was a black hole swirling slowly on it. There were a few ships of difference sizes parked beside it and at least ten people from the Scarlet Snow Sect were standing on the icy field, waiting for him as they looked at Garen’s ship.

Chapter 1072: Snatch 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“The Tenth Royal Highness,” one of the men shouted. “We are the Special Order and we will be under your command to investigate the Blue Frost Sect’s incident,” this person was tall and wore a pair of spectacles. He looked gentle and harmless. He had a snow-white longsword by his waist and was in a clean white suit.

Garen stood at the driver’s window of the Flying Ship as he looked down at the crowd.

“Are all of you sent by the First Elder?”

“No, we are a group of people sent by the Second Elder and Third Elder,” the man in glasses adjusted his glasses as he replied calmly. “I am the Deputy Minister of the Special Intelligence Department. You can call me Glasses.”

“Am I of the highest command for this mission?” Garen nodded.

“Naturally.”

Garen glanced at the crowd and the male to female distribution was very equal. Although all of them were wearing the Two Hearted Pauldron, they did not seem to be in the age to be training as a Two Hearted Disciples. Hence, the only conclusion was that they had become members of the headquarters when they graduated from being Two Hearted Disciples.

“Let’s get aboard and prepare to head out,” he said calmly.

“However, there are two other royal highness on their way!” The man in glasses shouted.

“There are two others?” Garen squinted his eyes. “Which two?”

As the man in glasses was about to speak, two white lines were drawn across the sky. In an instant, they landed underneath Garen’s Flying Ship at the side of the crowd. They were one male and female each dressed completely in white.

One of them was Eva. her expression was cold as if she was another person. It was obvious that Rainy’s death had a huge impact on her as she looked rather pale.

The other person was a muscular man with a small white cat on his shoulder.

“King Cat?” Garen recognized this man.

Although King Cat looked like a sincere, muscular and tall man, the small and pure white cat made his frightening appearance much softer.

“I represent the Third Elder in this team.”

Eva stared coldly at Garen.

“I represent the Second Elder in this team.”

“It looks like I’m the captain of this team?” Garen laughed. No one disputed it, including Eva as everyone assumed he’s in charge.

This meant that everyone had recognized him as the strongest person around. Only the person who possessed strength had a say in everything in this Sect.

Although the Energy Machinists of Planet Naga were very good in computing power, they had used all their computing power in increasing their strength and they rarely branch out from it. Hence, the Energy Machinists were often viewed as barbarians. One of their characteristics was that they respected people with power.

“Since everyone has arrived, let’s move out,” Garen ordered coldly.

He was the first one who leaped into the vortex with his ship. The rest then went up to their ships and flew into it. Soon, the icy field had returned to its quiet environment.

**************

“According to intel, the traitor of the Dragon Light Sect is called Agathon. He has the strength of an Inherited Level on the surface but we’re unsure if this intel is reliable. The reason he had betrayed the Sect was because he had raped and murdered the Fifth Elder’s granddaughter of the Dragon Light Sect. This is the wanted assistance order we, the Intel Department had received from the Dragon Light Sect.”

Glasses sent information to Garen’s Flying Ship while the Flying Ship was in the middle of a dimensional leap.

“Agathon?” Garen rubbed his chin. The rotating person on the monitor was a thin, tall man. He looked very normal and seemed to be a little bit handsome. He had elegant eyes and eyebrows and didn’t look like a rapist or murderer.

“What’s the overall inside story?” He questioned.

Glasses was slightly stunned as he replied, “Amazing Garen your Highness. You’re able to guess that there’s an inside story without much lead,” he continued after flattering him. “The inside story is that this man and the granddaughter of the Elder are lovers. He was a very talented man with a very bright future but he seemed to be framed by someone. After raping and murdering his lover, his reputation was thrown down the drain and had no choice but to escape. The mastermind is indeed a cruel man.”

“Who else is assisting in this killing other than us?”

“Hmm… There are two other powerhouses from two different sects. They are the Black Dragon Sect and Sky Sword Sect which were from the same planet. There were also other Inherited Level Pilots which were hired as well,” Glasses answered truthfully. “Since this planet is rather far away, our intel isn’t really reliable so we don’t know their actual strength.”

“That’s fine…” Garen said calmly.

The leap soon had reached an end.

In the sky above the gray and white mountains, a black hole appeared among the blue sky and white clouds as a few white Flying Ships suddenly flew out from the black hole.

Although these Flying Ships had been dyed white, its side still had the Scarlet Snow Sect’s red emblem.

“Location confirmed.”

“The Headquarter of the Blue Frost Sect’s old address is approximately one thousand six hundred fifty-three kilometers away.”

“Activating risk factors and surrounding awareness.”

The participating members didn’t even require any orders to act and formed a formation as they put Garen, Eva and King Cat in the middle of it.

Sizzle.

It seemed that one of the member’s scanning device was faulty as it gave off a disturbing noise.

“I’m sorry I’m sorry!!” The young man immediately shouted among the team.

“It’s fine. Is it your first time out for this outstation mission? Stay calm. Everyone has a first and mistakes are bound to happen,” Eva comforted gently.

It was only then when the member gave a sigh of relief and thanked her profusely.

Garen ignored the little drama over there as he sat on his knees inside the flying ship while he kept training his Destructive Impact Fist.

His body and skin were in a continuous vibration. The Destructive Impact Fist was destroying his organs and bones but at the same time, the Potential Points were recovering every injury at lightning speed. Both elements were balancing each other within Garen’s body.

After they had finished scanning the surrounding, they started to check their respective Flying Ships. They set up the setting to hide the Dimensional Tunnel as they required it to go back home later on.

After leaving behind half of the team to guard the Dimensional Tunnel, Garen and the other two brought six men along and went directly towards the ruins of the Blue Frost Sect.

Since the wanted traitor was still on this planet and it would require a long time to track him down, they decided to head out to the Blue Frost Sect’s old address to investigate.

Garen knew much better than anyone how the Blue Frost Sect perished as his space ring contained a pile of original techniques originated from the Blue Frost Sect. He had also obtained a lot of high-grade Gene Strengthening Liquid.

Hence, his so-called investigation was nothing but an act.

Garen ordered everyone to get down from the ship and walk instead when the Blue Frost Sect’s Headquarter was about ten meters away. The Blue Frost Sect was built on the planet’s huge magnetic field and going there via the Flying Ship would require energy multiple times more than normal. Hence, it was better and agiler to move on foot than to fly there.

The group entered a vast golden desert once they left the ship. The scorching hot sand kept inducing the hot steams upwards as it twisted the air.

The sun bathed the entire area without mercy as it released its overwhelming heat.

However, the nine men from the Scarlet Snow Sect weren’t affected by their environment as they moved swiftly forward in the desert.

The group of people looked like a clear white line among the golden desert as they moved towards the Blue Frost Sect’s headquarter at a great pace.

“If I didn’t come here on my own, I would’ve never guessed that the Blue Frost Sect would have built their headquarters on the hottest desert,” The King Cat stood by the Flying Ship as he said.

“Rumor has it that they are trying to use the natural scorching heat to enhance their coolness. Imagine that you are able to release an incredible amount of chill in the hottest environment and how much chill would they have produced if they were placed under a cold environment?” Garen explained softly.

“That makes sense,” King Cat was an ally of the Third Elder. Now that he was on the same team as Garen, he wouldn’t try to disobey Garen even if their relationship wasn’t good.

The group stood on top of the Flying Ship as they glided at great speed. Soon, they could faintly see the ruins of the Blue Frost Sect.

“Who’s there!?” suddenly a shout could be heard at the front.

“We are the investigation team from the Scarlet Snow Sect. This is our assistance permit,” Glasses put out a white badge-like item and a white light shone out into the sky. It was complete silence after that.

“It’s the people from the Energy Machinist Alliance,” Glasses explained softly to Garen and the other two.

“There should be a lot of people investigating, right?” Garen asked softly. “What kind of investigation is this about?”

Glasses then adjusted his spectacles. “Your Royal Highness. The investigation involves in finding out any key traces or presences when the Blue Frost Sect was destroyed. We also plan to collect some samples to do some experiments as well. At the same time, even though the Blue Frost Sect was destroyed, there are a few items that are too heavy to be moved away within a short period of time. Hence, our mission also involves retrieving most of these heavy equipment.”

“In other words, we’re here to snatch these items?” King Cat concluded in a very straightforward manner.

“Don’t be that straightforward… Everyone needs to cover up somehow,” Garen laughed.

“With that being said, it is as King Cat His Royal Highness has stated. We’re here to snatch the items,” Glasses smiled as he responded respectfully.

“No wonder they sent me out here,” Garen finally understood the situation.

Indeed, he was the strongest in the Scarlet Snow Sect excluding Carthage after the battle with Eva. His battle strength far surpassed any typical Inherited Level and he was very close to achieving Non-Falling Level. Hence, the reason he was sent out here was to snatch these items.

They approached the white ruins closer and closer.

“What’s the most important item left behind by the Blue Frost Sect?”

“It’s the Cold Night Pond. However, there will be a lot of people fighting over it.”

“Let’s go to the Cold Night Pond then,” Garen smiled.

***********

Within the ruins of the Blue Frost Sect, three teams of different colors were surrounding the area on top of the diamond-shaped blue crystal.

“Dragon Armor of the Dragon Light Sect, don’t you think you’ve crossed the line that you’ve used the name of a fugitive to snatch items away from us Planet Almanac?”

A cold woman’s voice reverberated at the top of the blue crystal.

The one who spoke was the female leader in a tight yellow suit standing on the left together with the other women.

“What do you mean by snatching? We’re merely here to collect this crystal sample to analyze so that we can find out who’s the murderer perishing the whole Blue Frost Sect. How can you state that this is snatching?” A soft yet villainous tone came from a man.

Among the men in golden attire on top of the right side of the crystal, there stood a handsome man gently rubbing his golden monocle with a mild expression.

“Everybody knows that the Dragon Light Sect is here to snatch the items away instead of retrieving it. Tsk tsk. How embarrassing. It’s definitely considered one of the wonders among the middle sized Sect,” a tall and muscular man laughed out loud weirdly among the group of black men.

“Gatengsi, looks like you’ve reached Grade Nine for your Black Dragon’s Cloud Technique? Since you dare to speak to me in such manner,” the handsome man stared femininely at the muscular man.

“Looks like I’ve been discovered. Heh. I’ll gladly comply if you wish to fight!” Gatengsi of the Black Dragon Sect laughed. “I’ll say it first. If I, Gatengsi is around, none of you will take away the Cold Night Pond away easily! Including you! Fati!”

The two local Sect had teamed up in secret to fight against the Dragon Light Sect.

“Speaking of which, isn’t it bad that word has gotten out that us sects from the same star clusters fight against each other instead of fighting against the people from the Four-star Alliance? I dare you to go against the Floating Light since he has obtained the best Cold Night Pond, which is unlike ours that is so small,” the feminine man smiled coldly at Fati.

“Why didn’t you go then? The Four-star Alliance! Hmpf!” The woman in the yellow shirt was frightened the moment the name Floating Light appeared.

Ever since the Gideon Household had perished, the Four-star Alliance had put in a tremendous amount of effort in strengthening themselves. As the remaining three stars developed at lightning speed, a talented young man who possessed a talent that appeared once a thousand year had appeared. He was no other than Floating Light. Rumor had it that he would leave no one alive when he attacked.

Chapter 1073: Limit 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“So, this is the Cold Night Pond?”

Suddenly, a faint voice came from afar.

A group of people dressed in white on a Flying Ship came in swiftly and stopped nearby the crowd.

A muscular and tall man walked down from the Flying Ship and threw the vehicle to a side.

The man’s expression was calm, yet he was surrounded with a dense aura that no one could overlook. While the people behind him had a strong presence, he simply overshadowed the rest.

“It’s the people from the Scarlet Snow Sect!” The Scarlet Dragon Armor, Fati of the Dragon Light smirked. It was another external sect. He already had his hands full dealing with two allied Sects. Now that another sect had arrived, one could wonder how they planned on handling the situation.

The people from the Scarlet Snow Sect.

The Black Dragon Sect and the Sky Sword Sect could obtain information from the Energy Machine Imprint; they started being on their guard.

“We from the Black Dragon Sect and the Sky Sword Sect had discovered this place first. Friends of the Scarlet Snow Sect, if you wish to obtain the Cold Night Pond, please head off to somewhere else as there are still a few of Cold Night Ponds around!” The woman from the Sky Sword Sect shouted.

Garen’s group got down from the ship and glanced at the situation in front of them.

Two indigenous Sects united together to fight against the Dragon Light Sect. It seemed that this Cold Night Pond was simply the best and largest within the vicinity, otherwise, there wouldn’t be so many people fighting over it.

“How stupid. They’re still fighting against each other even when the sky is about to fall upon them,” Garen shook his head in his mind. It would be natural that these Energy Machinists, who were consumed by greediness, would perish.

Perhaps, in their perspective, the death of the entire sect was the doing of an enemy and an internal conflict between the Energy Machinists. They didn’t believe that any Pilots or outsiders would dare to attack them.

“This Cold Night Pond…” Garen immediately realized the giant blue crystal placed at the center. It contained a huge mass of chill that he himself couldn’t get his eyes off of it.

“What an overwhelming chill it has…”It is at least equivalent to the essence of five Blood Beads that Carthage has given out…” Seeing how there was still dirt around the crystal, it seemed that this item had just been dug out a while ago.

After some calculation, he would require at least three Origin Crystals to form the Crystal Wheel that would allow him to reach the Non-falling Level.

“I’ll be taking this Cold Night Pond.”

Garen was too lazy to argue with these bunch and spoke straightforwardly, “You guys can leave now.”

As soon as he finished speaking, everyone focused their attention on him; there were about tens of red visors set onto the whole Scarlet Snow Sect team, especially on their leader Garen.

“Who does he think he is? How dare he spew such words,” There were a few people who couldn’t hold in their mockery.

The strongest of each team, Dragon Armor Fati of the Dragon Light Sect, Gatengsi of Black Dragon and the woman in yellow shirt from the Sky Sword Sect looked at Garen as if he was an idiot.

“What kind of joke is that? Lame,” Gatengsi of the Black Dragon Sect rubbed his ears as he laughed.

“This is Planet Almanac, something is definitely wrong with him considering he dares to threaten us in our homeland,” The woman in yellow shirt laughed as well.

Even Eva and King Cat looked at Garen in confusion as they didn’t understand why Garen would say such ridiculous words without knowing the strength of his enemies. People would look down on him for saying such big words.

However, Garen smiled as he took a step forward.

“Three Qi is all I need to deal with you people.”

Boom!

An intense, invisible chill went straight toward the crowd like a tidal wave.

The frightening chill instantly froze the scorching hot gravels on the floor, including everyone within a hundred meters in front of him.

Crack crack… Crack…

The solid layer of ice swiftly froze the legs of the all the members from the two sects, propagating upward to their bodies at a great speed.

An Energy Field that could not be seen meant that they couldn’t defend from it at all. Everything they did was in vain as they couldn’t even have the time to feel frightened or shout. In that instant, ninety percent of the crowd had been completely frozen into ice crystal pillars, standing firmly on the sand.

The three leaders tried to use their Energy Field and Strength of Origin, but they could only slow down the propagation.

“You!” They weren’t even able to finish a sentence before they were covered in ice pillars, fear being written all over their faces.

With a slight trick of the hand, the scene which had a crowd had become silent. The three Inherited Level leaders were covered inside the solid ice pillars.

“How boring,” Garen sighed in disappointment. He wanted to test his limits, yet his opponents were frozen by him without putting up any defense at all.

He could faintly hear the sound of teeth trembling from the Scarlet Snow Sect’s disciples behind him. He could also hear the increased blood circulation from Eva and King Cat’s body tensing up the moment the chill was released from his body.

“You… You killed them all?!” King Cat’s tone was rather dry.

“Perhaps…” Garen smiled as he stepped forward and gently placed his hands on the surface of the Cold Night Pond.

Sizzle…

A sizzling noise which sent chills down people’s spine could be heard as the crowd from the Scarlet Snow Sect stared at the Night Cold Pond in front of Garen shrink at a great pace. It was similar to an ice melting as they could see it shrinking with their naked eyes.

As for the surrounding people, he wouldn’t simply kill them off that easily as he had only released his frost Energy Field instead of Faded Creation. He had at most limited their movements and severely injured them due to the frost. Their lives would only be in danger if someone couldn’t get them out of the ice pillars within the span of ten days.

“Your Highness Garen is definitely the number one genius after His Highness Carthage!” Glasses, who was standing behind him, immediately flattered him as soon as he was able to react. However, his tone was rather dry.

The other five normal members could only swallow their saliva when they regained their composure from the shock. They should be proud of their own team, but all they felt was chills sending down their spine.

“Is the Scarlet Snow Technique really this incredible?” King Cat looked at Garen’s back as he was shocked. He, too, was at the Grade Thirteen for the Scarlet Snow Technique, but he couldn’t achieve such destruction even if he went all out. It had completely exceeded the realm of pure technic and was in the realm of disaster.

Eva gritted her teeth as she stared at Garen’s back. She was also shocked to see that Garen had improved so much. If he were to keep moving forward at such an incredible pace, she might not be able to avenge Rainy at this rate!

As the group was still recovering from the shock, Garen had already finished absorbing the Night Cold Pond and returned to the team. However, he seemed to be disappointed and no one dared to ask him why.

“Let’s go, to the next Night Cold Pond.

Garen said coldly. The fight ended before it started; it was such a buzzkill to everyone who was ready to go all out.

“Your Highness Garen is so strong!” A member behind Glasses couldn’t help but to said softly after regaining from the shock.

“The Scarlet Snow Technique can be that strong!?” Another female member muttered.

“Perhaps we, the Scarlet Snow Sect, are about to rise once again…” Another female member looked at Garen with a sense of worship in her eyes.

Worship would naturally form when the strength between two of similar ages was too drastic. They would then draw a line between the two and categorize the other party into another realm so that they wouldn’t compare themselves to the other party. This way, they could protect their own dignity. This was the nature of human being.

The Two Hearted members were in this exact situation.

Eva stared at him as she held the dagger in her arms tightly.

Garen rushed toward the next location where the Night Cold Pond was located. Glasses instructed a member to use the detecting device to locate more Night Cold Ponds.

Although the first Night Cold Pond Crystal was huge, Garen was only able to fill up the first Origin Crystal after refining it, he couldn’t even see the second crystal sprouting.

This made him have a firmer grasp on the difficulty of achieving the Non-Falling Level.

The people were already fighting around the second Cold Night Pond. Golden sparks were everywhere, and herds of purple-black birds covered the entire sky. A few large Mechs were mixed among these birds in the sky As they dyed the sky in red and green. It seemed that they were of the Inherited Level as well.

Garen couldn’t care less which Sect they were from since he had Carthage as the final line of defense. That person’s strength was endless, and he was definitely the strongest person in the Scarlet Snow Sect. The three Elders weren’t able to restrict him, and the Guardians had not shown themselves until even today. Half of the current Scarlet Snow Sect had been controlled by him and even though there were a few Three Hearted Disciples who viewed him as a threat, the majority of them were proud to have him. They didn’t care who was the owner, but they cared who could bring them glory and power.

Carthage was able to meet those criteria.

“Absolute Freeze.”

Garen didn’t even need to unsheathe his sword as he walked directly toward the blue Night Cold Pond Crystal, ignoring the battles surrounding him.

The birds froze into ice and fell onto the ground wherever he walked by. The people who were fighting were instantly frozen before they could react. All of them were frozen within an ice pillar, defenseless against the attack.

It was the same towards the Resonance Level or Inherited Level.

It was almost as though the Scarlet Snow Sect was walking in an environment without any human presence as they walked directly toward the Night Cold Pond. Garen reached out his hand and placed tightly on the surface of the Night Cold Pond.

The people behind him didn’t know what he was doing, neither did they dare to ask him as well. Garen’s invincibility had carved deeply in their memories. No one was able to stand against him as his enemies were instantly sealed within ice pillars in an instant. This Scarlet Snow Technique was out of everyone’s imagination!

After a while, Garen put away his hand as he looked at the Night Cold Pond that had been greatly shrunk.

“I’ve absorbed the Cold Energy inside it, but there are still traces of Cold Energy left that could be used for research. It seems to contain some secrets from the Blue Frost Sect. You can bring it back to the Technical Department for them to do their research. Keep it safe.”

“Yes!”

Glasses immediately went forward and kept the Cold Night Pond Crystal, which was as tall as a human, with the Space Ring that he had prepared earlier.

“Let’s go to the next one,” Garen turned around and went towards the third one.

Chapter 1074: Limit 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Glasses glanced at the Energy Machinists and Mech Pilots within the icicles around him as a hint of greed flashed in his eyes.

“If I were able to remove the items from these people…” He knocked the icicles briefly when he walked past them silently.

However, the thing that shocked him was the intense and terrifying chills that suddenly spread throughout his fingers the moment he touched the icicles. He triggered the Scarlet Snow Technique and he continued to resist it desperately. Unfortunately, the chills that were only as thin as strands of hair consumed more than half of all his skills. Its purity was simply unimaginable!

While fear continued to linger in his heart, he glanced at Garen who was strolling in front of him. As he was too afraid to overthink this, Glasses followed Garen closely behind instead.

The third, the fourth, the fifth…

Garen absorbed numerous Cold Night Ponds one after another. He froze everyone who tried to resist or fight him for it.

The terrifying chills caused the temperature of the surrounding area to be reduced by more than ten degrees gradually. When the weather was scorchingly hot, abnormal occurrences like this would gradually attract the attention of the powerhouses from other regions.

A few scattered Mech Pilots and Energy Machinists who came to make a profit looked at the members of Scarlet Snow Sect from afar before fleeing quickly to avoid becoming casualties.

Therefore, Garen and his group were able to absorb the Cold Night Ponds even faster.

There were more than twenty Cold Night Ponds and most of them were completely absorbed by Garen now. He finally began to solidify his second Origin Crystal. He could freeze Cold Energy within a range of a hundred thousand square kilometers into frozen snowscapes by absorbing all of this energy into his body. However, he had merely started to freeze the second Origin Crystal. This gave him some new insight regarding the Non-falling Level’s terrifying accumulated energy.

The others did not possess such a convenient absorption and purification ability. From the past to this present, he was probably the only one who could enjoy the perfect purification abilities from his Ice Coffin Secret Technique. After all, he had spent more than a thousand years practicing this skill wearily in order to perfect it. This was not a price that merely anyone could accept.

Moreover, the Heart of Ice that was produced by the perfected Ice Coffin was not just used to purify Cold Energy. It could also strengthen and amplify the efficiency of the chills that Garen released. This allowed him to have a perfect command of these chills.

When they noticed that the crowds of frozen people had increased, Garen’s reputation grew as well.

Some people tried to smash the solid icicles open and save those inside but their efforts were futile. The frozen layers that were attacked or smashed would restore themselves to their original states on their own as if they were alive.

Moreover, they were afraid of hurting the people inside if they exerted too much force. Hence, it was impossible for the powerhouses, who rushed over later, to undo Garen’s frozen chills.

They collected all of the Cold Night Ponds that were nearby quickly. The group even overturned some of the ruins to find some good things that were concealed in deeper places. They had obtained considerably great gains.

Garen’s second crystal had successfully solidified now. He was able to fully absorb its Cold Energy to a perfect stage, allowing him to release even more terrifying chills.

He lowered his hand and placed it on a Cold Night Pond in front of him slowly.

Shh!

Suddenly, a golden light pillar rose up in the distance into the sky. This gigantic light pillar was blindingly bright, resembling a gold rod that shot itself into the sky directly. Shrouds of golden air currents revolved around it.

The enormous Energy Field pressed onto and enveloped the entire Blue Frost Sect and the ruins around it instantly.

“So powerful! This is the Lord of Gold, the ultimate move as well as a skill that is specialized by the Gold Clan of the Four-Star Alliance!” said King Cat sincerely and subconsciously. “It’s probably Floating Light.”

Along the way, they did not have any opportunities to do anything. While feeling astonished towards Garen’s powers, he also felt extremely bored. However, once he saw the light pillar now, a hint of frustration rose in his heart suddenly. His initial fighting intentions instantly and completely disappeared. He had previously assumed that Garen was already a rare deviant, before another deviant appeared before his eyes, making him feel powerless.

“Floating Light?” Garen raised his eyebrows. “Let’s go take a look.”

“This trip simply feels like a vacation,” said another one of his group members while smiling.

“With His Highness Garen here, we can grab the things we want freely and have a look around as we please,” Another group member replied lightly. “Even if Floating Light grew stronger again, do you think he could really be stronger than His Royal Highness Garen?”

Everyone took turns chatting casually and lightly. King Cat, who was feeling frustrated earlier, had returned to his normal state as well. He shook his head and concentrated his gaze on Garen who was in front of him. Both this fellow and Carthage had powers that were simply like endless pits. The depths of their powers were unknown, and they were frighteningly strong. Perhaps Floating Light would be able to uncover some of his exact details.

They turned and passed through some of Blue Frost Sect’s damaged building areas that were used for experimental research before a terrifying gigantic, round hollow which was more than ten meters wide appeared in front of them quickly.

Shrouds of green smoke were escaping from the giant pit slowly, releasing scorching hot temperatures. Red liquid lava could even be seen in the center.

A young, handsome man was standing at the edge of the giant pit. He carried a golden rod silently while pursing his lips and looking at Garen and the others who were rushing over here.

From afar, his gaze resembled two rays of golden light that were incomparably blinding. They made others completely fearful of looking at him directly.

“Garen of Scarlet Snow?” Despite being ten meters away, his voice echoed across the great distance clearly. It was calm and tinged with inexperience, but it was clear that he was not an average youth.

Garen looked at the youth on the opposite side of himself in a slightly surprised manner as well. At this age, he could not be older than thirty years old, meaning that he was just like Garen.

However, his gaze did not linger on the other person’s body but instead shifted to the unimaginably gigantic blue crystal behind him.

That crystal was easily almost the size of a little hill. It was glittering and translucent while a human-shaped shadow was sealed inside. It could not be seen clearly.

Extremely terrifying chills were released throughout his entire body. They enveloped a range of more than hundreds of meters around him, completely covering his surrounding environment in layers of white frost and making it unimaginably cold.

This crystal was more than two times larger than the previous ones that Garen had absorbed.

“Tch… tch… Such a large crystal is probably enough for me to form my third Origin Crystal…” A hint of desire conjured up in his heart.

Carthage’s pressure, the destroyed destinies that would ultimately befall Energy Machinists in the future, and his determined fate that he had to die next time were three things that were constantly shrouding his mind like the shadows of death, suppressing his insane forces of pursuit.

Silently, a chill traveled towards the bottom of Floating Light’s foot and struck it quickly. No one noticed the movements of this chill.

Puff!

This was the first time that his chills had collapsed.

It collided against his Inherited Level Energy Field within a distance that was less than half a meter from Floating Light before instantly perishing together with a golden force; both of them were destroyed.

Both parties looked at each other in a slightly shocked manner. This exploration had instantly proven that both of their strengths were of the same level.

“No wonder there were so many people who had previously said that your chills had already reached stages that could not be countered by those who were not of the Non-falling Level. Now it seems like no one had made a mistake.”

Floating Light continued calmly and said, “Unfortunately…” He raised his head and looked at the sky before a little black shadow flew over faintly.

Whoosh!

He leaped upward and turned into a flash of golden lightning before disappearing completely. His rapid speed simply caused people to stare dumbfoundedly.

“Your life will only remain until I come back to retrieve it next time,” echoed Floating Light’s voice from afar.

“There won’t be a next time,” Garen smiled suddenly.

Shh!

The chills throughout his entire body condensed into a gigantic white gas Energy Field before soaring towards the black shadow in the sky.

Chirp!

The frightening Energy Field that shrouded a range of a few hundred meters turned into the figure of a gigantic peacock. Its sharp beak raised itself toward the sky and held the black shadow in its mouth.

Drastic changes occurred across the face of Floating Light, who was perched on the black shadow before he turned around and suppressed it with his rod hastily and firmly. A spot of golden light lit up at the end of the rod. It was extremely blinding.

“Sky Magnet Rod!”

The golden light traveled directly toward the tip of the peacock’s beak. He swept all of the surrounding magnetic fields over before drawing them towards the peacock’s beak, suppressing it.

The golden light canceled out a large portion of Garen’s Turbulent Chills. However, there were still some chills that tainted both Floating Light’s legs; the ice spread over, covering him instantly and completely freezing his legs into a single ice block.

“Damn!”

“Go!” A frantic voice echoed from the black shadow. The black shadow was actually a black airship. A woman who wore a golden crown appeared there while the both of them worked together to release a large golden cloud to block the peacock’s following attacks. The airship flew higher before finally leaving Garen’s attack range.

The enormous peacock could only raise its head and whine in frustration as its speed decelerated. It grew weaker before finally shrinking back into Garen’s body.

Garen lifted his head and looked at the airship that was merely a black dot in the sky now. Using his terrifyingly powerful eyesight, he could still see the hateful yet slightly frightened gazes of Floating Light, along with the woman with the golden crown.

The group of people behind him, including Eva and King Cat, looked with a flabbergasted manner at the fight that had occurred moments ago. Their degrees of power had already surpassed the domains of the Inherited Level and reached the stages of the Non-falling Level instead. They looked at Garen again and noticed that his gaze had already changed completely. It had changed into the form and manner of their seniors in the Non-falling Level.

The enormous Chill Peacock the size of few hundred meters had immediately scared those two people earlier. Most creatures that were formed by Energy Fields would not be this large, while only those in the Non-falling Level would be able to form such gigantic Energy Field figures.

Therefore, the implications of Garen’s ability to form such gigantic Energy Field figures were still unknown.

“He just ran away like that. How unfortunate,” Garen sheathed the sword that was previously in his hands and walked directly towards the gigantic Cold Night Pond. He did not know why Floating Light fled suddenly. However, it was clear that he had some urgent matters. Moreover, he was probably seeking something other than the Cold Night Pond. It was obvious that he had succeeded already. After all, Cold Night Ponds were not as valuable compared to non-frost-type powerhouses.

The few people behind him were unaware of the unfortunate thing he was talking about. Was it unfortunate that they were unable to fight, or was it unfortunate that…

Once Floating Light had left, no one within the entire Blue Frost Sect could challenge Garen anymore. This applied to the Dragon Light Sect and the local Black Dragon Sect and Sky Sword Sect as well. If they were afraid of the likes of Floating Light, they would not even need to think of Garen.

Garen himself was unaware of the current stage that he had achieved as well.

A regular attack that was formed by his Energy Field had injured the peak Inherited Level powerhouse Floating Light, whose strength rivaled the Non-falling Levels. He did not even have to use a sword, the Destructive Impact Fist, Nine Layers Body Shattering Technique, or even the Faded Creation that was hidden in the most secluded areas.

After walking toward the front of the gigantic Cold Night Pond Crystal, Garen reached his hand out and pressed it against the surface of the crystal closely.

The Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s terrifying Devour ability launched rapidly before the essence of myriad Cold Energy was filtered out and purified by the Ice Coffin. Next, it began to condense the third crystal within Garen’s body quickly.

It greatly exceeded the Cold Energy of every Cold Night Pond before him. All of the Cold Energy that was accumulated by Blue Frost Sect for thousands of years had been engulfed into Garen’s body. The third gem-like scarlet crystal was rapidly condensed there.

Once the third one had appeared, the fourth one came soon after. Moments after the fourth one was successfully formed, the Cold Energy of the Cold Night Pond Crystal had finally been exhausted.

The crystals that were previously more than twenty meters large had now shrunken into the size of half a human.

There were four Origin Crystals.

Garen looked inwardly at the four red crystal gems within his own body.

“I can already solidify them into a wheel. This is truly terrifying… The Hellfrost Peacock Technique and its frightening Devour ability have simply disregarded most of the rules of accumulation and plundered the energy and essence of external creatures directly! No wonder its performance has been so weak all this while. Apparently, its true powers would only be fully exhibited at the final stage.”

Chapter 1075: Chance Encounter 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The major accomplishments of the Living Secret Technique had finally manifested during this frightening technological era.

A terrifying progress rate like this even made Garen himself feel as if it was somewhat unreal.

“We don’t need to rush the process of solidifying it into a wheel for now. We’ll discuss it later after solidifying a few more crystals. For Non-falling Level wheels, the more crystals we have, the stronger its explosive force and stamina will be. It will be even more terrifying during actual combat.”

“Keep this thing. We’ll keep going now.” Garen threw out the last sentence before walking forward himself to other areas to continue the search for the Cold Night Pond Crystals. This thing was simply a great form of nourishment to him. It was even quicker than absorbing other high energy substances.

Despite being major combat forces, both King Cat and Eva had been reduced to watching him passively while the remaining members worshipped and respected Garen greatly. Individuals who were absolutely powerful like himself had brought about an undeniably bright future for the rest of them.

Next, Garen collected all of the high energy substances and Cold Night Ponds throughout the ruins of the Blue Frost Sect. He absorbed it for more than one whole day, and no one dared enter the entire Blue Frost Sect now as Garen’s terrifying chills and icicles were everywhere. When the two elders of Black Dragon Sect and Sky Sword Sect had finally rushed over, they exhausted a lot of their energy to smash the icicles and save their own disciples and members. It looked extremely difficult and when the others witnessed this scene, those who were initially prepared to enter and earn a quick buck turned silent suddenly.

As both of the Non-falling Level elders were extremely scared of Garen, they gave strict orders to all of their members to return to their sects and train painstakingly after leaving the site of the ruins.

Meanwhile, Garen absorbed all of the usable resources impetuously.

The number of crystals had increased to six. At this moment, he had absorbed almost all of Blue Frost Sect’s high energy substances.

The other Scarlet Snow Sect members might have obtained certain benefits as well, as they now carried various heavy machinery and pieces of equipment with them.

By obtaining six of these crystals, although the total number was not full yet, Garen felt that he had reached his limit already.

He was not referring to the limit of his own Vitality, but the limit of the Scarlet Snow Technique instead.

Six crystals were the highest limit of the Scarlet Snow Sect’s Scarlet Snow Technique as well as the upper limit of this skill. If he increased it any further, Garen could clearly feel that his Energy Machine Imprint could probably not support it anymore.

“Looks like this is the difference compared to the other major sects. No wonder Scarlet Snow Sect was just an average minor sect,” Garen had finally understood the difference between Energy Machinist Sects. It was similar to the difference between the number of Origin Crystals when one first entered the Non-falling Level. Despite the greatness of your natural talents, your techniques would still have upper limits that would limit your development and make you weaker than those from different sects who were at the same level as you.

“I can only solidify the wheel now,” thought Garen helplessly.

He had never considered solidification like this initially. It was unfortunate that the Scarlet Snow Technique could only solidify so few of these.

“I’ll settle my score with that escaper later.”

He sighed and stood on the remains of the last valuable building in the ruins. His terrifying chills had frozen all of the ruins below him into a single block of ice.

Under the sunlight, more than half of the ruins of Blue Frost Sect were frozen into a snowy, icy state. Gigantic blocks of pure white and crystal-clear ice could be seen everywhere.

The remaining members of the Scarlet Snow Sect dispersed throughout the surroundings and examined the area for valuables respectively.

Garen did not convene these people and allowed them to look for treasures freely. Getting rid of deserters was a simple task. There would be no problem as long as he was able to find the other party.

While standing atop the solid ice, he took a red and round item, which resembled a pocket watch, from his bosom and glanced at the illuminated red dot that was displayed there.

“We’ll see how your luck turns out. If I find you within half a day, that’ll be unfortunate for you.”

Whoosh.

Garen’s figure slid down the ice quickly before leaving and flying into the faraway distance.

*****************

Planet Gideon of the Four-Star Alliance

Within an enormous crater that was filled with meteorites, a large crowd was painstakingly moving various ores that were excavated from the mining cavity. Some of them specialized in mining, while others either transported or categorized them.

The filthy people had nothing but rags on their backs. Exhaustion filled their faces as they worked while numerous black Spirit Mechs stood at the higher regions of the meteorite crater to monitor and manage this place.

Both Clint and Baylon were carrying baskets of ores on their backs while following the stream of people to the faraway sorting area.

“We need to think of a way to escape from here,” Clint said to Baylon quietly. “We’ve already been here for two days and it’s not an option for us to go on like this!”

“Do you have any good ideas?” asked Baylon softly.

“According to Old Hank, this place is the Spirit King’s mining pit division. The surveillance here is probably not the most stringent. Moreover, they’re also hiding a few Mechs that have been prepared to be used for the purposes of revolting. As long as we find an opportunity and convince Old Hank, we can definitely resolve these Spirit Mechs,” said Clint softly.

“Then how are you going to gain their trust?” said Baylon in a slightly anxious tone.

“Yes… We heard this information from our boss Red Moon secretly. How are we going to convince them to let us on the Mechs…” Suddenly, Clint scratched his own head helplessly.

“I have a way,” Red Moon’s voice echoed suddenly.

“What way? Tell us quickly, Boss. I don’t want to spend my days moving ores anymore!” Clint’s spirits stirred immediately.

“Hehe, Old Hank’s son Hans is quite perverted… Baylon needs to take the field this time… Hehehe…” laughed Red Moon wickedly.

“No… No way…” whispered Baylon timidly. When she sensed that both Clint and Red Moon’s attention were focused on her at the same time, she cowered even more.

“Impossible!” Clint rejected suddenly. When he thought of making Baylon seduce that filthy ugly monster, his heart was filled with uneasiness.

“This is the best way,” said Red Moon while smiling sinisterly.

“Impossible. I’ve said it’s impossible so no can do. I, Clint, have not fallen so low as to require Lonnie to sacrifice her body to protect me!” said Clint with stern righteousness.

“What are you saying?!” Out of a sudden, Baylon was unbearably embarrassed. She hit Clint’s head violently. She had already fallen into the bearing of a young woman completely now. Compared to most girls, she had an exterior that was even purer, prettier and closer to perfection. Thus, she gave off a delicate and charming feeling. She had black shoulder-length hair and her skin was even more tender than a star apple. Her large almond-shaped eyes were bright and watery, while her lips and cheeks were extremely tender and pink. Clint became slightly dull after looking at her for some time.

However, the t-shirt and jeans that she still wore from her time on the Mother Planet did not match well with her delicately pure external appearance. This outfit was chosen to make moving previously convenient. After wandering desperately for a period of time, holes had formed everywhere in her trousers from the wear and tear. Her snowy white skin could be seen faintly when they were occasionally exposed inside.

If Red Moon had not used his camouflaging illusory light to shroud both of them and disguise them as unassuming regular people, a large crowd of ravenous people would have probably pounced on Baylon the moment she entered the mining pit…

When Clint thought of this terrifying possibility, his heart trembled with fear. Feelings of affliction and rejection poured out of his heart when he looked at Baylon’s perfect and pure beauty.

Lonnie belongs to me! I will never allow anyone else to touch a single hair on her head!

His gaze became frighteningly stern suddenly.

He had already thought of Baylon as his own woman long ago despite clearly knowing that she was a boy who had turned into a girl. However, Clint was also a vigorous pubescent boy. Therefore, after spending a long time with her and constantly being unconsciously seduced by Baylon, his mind had long been unable to suppress this anymore. Hence, he thought of Baylon as his exclusive property.

“How could I let my own woman protect me!” In a fit of irritation, this sentence escaped from his mouth.

“Uhh…” Baylon was shocked while Red Moon laughed sinisterly within both of their minds.

“Hehehe… You’ve let the cat out of the bag. I noticed long ago that there was something weird with the way you looked at Lonnie. Looks like it’s like this now! Heeheehee…” sneered Red Moon.

Baylon’s pretty face turned completely red instantly. It seemed as though smoke was about to escape from the top of her head. As she had always been a boy who had turned into a girl, she had never paid attention to the societal barriers between men and women. Therefore, she had unintentionally seduced Clint many times. Moreover, she had instinctively assumed that a girl like herself was not a pure female. With that said, she had an inferiority complex which evolved from her innermost self. She had always assumed that Clint would never look highly on her and had never thought of it from any other perspective. Now, however… She was instantly subdued by Clint’s words that almost seemed like a romantic confession…

“I… I…” The redness of her entire face had reached her neck. She lowered her head, unable to complete her entire sentence as it trailed off softly.

“Break time,” Suddenly, a robotic voice echoed from a high area.

Clint acted as if he had just been given a big break before putting the mining basket down and running away quickly.

“I… I’m going to find some water!”

There was a puff of smoke before he fled swiftly without leaving a single trace.

However, he didn’t see the abjected look that flashed in Baylon’s eyes again.

“He… actually can’t even look up to me… I know… Perhaps… Perhaps he was merely joking casually…”

*****************

Beside a faraway, emerald-green amber that resembled a jade.

Clint pushed his head into the lake firmly at once to calm himself down briefly.

Whoosh!

The water gurgled beside his head and flowed around.

Clint felt as if his entire body was immediately relieved.

He lifted his head out of the water with a splash before spitting out a mouthful of air quickly.

“Curse you, Red Moon! You definitely manipulated my body again secretly, right?! Why would I have said such shameless things otherwise?!” he questioned Red Moon in his mind furiously.

“I’m not interested in manipulating you. The body of my great self still needs to recuperate properly. Older people like myself are unlike youngsters like you…” said Red Moon slowly, in a tone that warranted a spanking.

Whoosh…

Clint was about to speak before the sound of water could be heard nearby suddenly.

He lifted his head and saw a white-haired youth dressed in white at the edge of the lake on the opposite side, currently walking toward the center of the lake indifferently. As he walked, his body was gradually submerged by the lake water quickly. Only a few short seconds had passed before more than half of the white-haired youth’s body was submerged.

“Don’t fret over trivial matters when you’re so young!” Clint’s mind heated up suddenly and he threw himself into the lake instantly and swam toward the youth rapidly. The strength of his Nine Mega Cannon Training Method was frightening. He had swum across a distance of more than ten meters instantly like a speedboat before rushing in front of the youth.

“Let’s sit down and have a good talk about your troubles. Don’t belittle your own life easily!!” He yelled loudly while rushing forward and grabbing the youth firmly before running towards the shore.

“I…”

“What do you mean ‘I’?! Look at how young you are. If there’s something that you can’t figure out, just remember that life is long and the world is huge. You were just captured to mine for ores, right? We can always find a way to escape. We won’t spend our lives like this,” Clint placed him beside the shore in one go before he sat down and panted. He let out a few coarse breaths furiously while sitting on the ground numbly.

“I wasn’t…”

“Don’t say anything else. I’m currently troubled as well, but we have to sort out our own matters ourselves. Everyone has things that trouble them. However, if we simply regarded everything as a matter of life or death, wouldn’t every single person in the universe have died much earlier on?”

After Clint had spent a lot of time with Red Moon, the latter’s careless and crude speech and style had gradually influenced his personality.

The white-haired youth blinked and looked at Clint curiously.

“Back when I was still green, I had belittled my life like you as well. Therefore, I understand these feelings…” Clint took in the white-haired youth briefly. His gaze lingered on his boyishly charming face before he sighed emotionally and spoke in a deep tone suddenly.

The white-haired youth’s complexion turned green suddenly, he opened his mouth in an attempt to retort.

“Don’t explain!” Clint raised his hands and covered his mouth.

“Explanations are merely cover-ups… It’s inevitable that we’ll face obstacles in life. Facing them bravely and spending every day in your future happily is the true meaning of happiness. Don’t abandon yourself to despair easily.”

The white-haired youth’s face turned even greener immediately.

“I really…”

Chapter 1076: Chance Encounter 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“You really don’t need to explain!” Clint interrupted him again. “You’ve definitely suffered in the mining pit, and I really understand the pain you’ve experienced. You had to dress gorgeously every day only to interact with such frightening men… Yet, the world is like this. If we can’t resist it, we can only learn to accept it. Especially fellows like you with such a boyishly charming face that even I cannot help but be aroused by… Scary… It’s so scary!!”

The white-haired youth’s face had darkened already…

“Although I’ve never experienced pain like yours, I still understand that some things are just a part of our destiny. Even though it’s already fated, as long as you resist it, you will definitely see results!” Clint sighed emotionally.

“Destiny? Resist?” A ray of light flashed across the white-haired youth’s eyes.

“Yes… Resist your destiny. Doesn’t it sound pretty cool?” Clint raised his head and looked at the sky. Other than the sun, there was a dark purple planet which was quite near to them. It was also giving off a mild, purple light.

“But how do you know that our own attempts of resistance aren’t already arranged as parts of our destinies?” The white-haired youth could finally speak a complete sentence properly. He had a melodious voice that was very clear and not the slightest bit hoarse. It made others unconsciously relate it to all of the adjectives that could describe purity. It even sounded faintly like a girl’s voice.

“You will always see a fragment of hope in the end if you resist. However, if you don’t resist, you won’t even have this fragment of hope,” said Clint while scratching his head. “I don’t know any major reasons, but I merely do the things that I want to, and this is enough. As for the other troubling matters, we’ll just talk about it later when the time comes!”

A hint of curiosity flashed in the white-haired youth’s pupils.

“You probably have dreams, right?”

“Of course!” Clint rubbed his nose. “My dream is to find a place to live out my days peacefully without being disturbed by others. Of course, bringing another specific person along the way to restore their body is also another part of it,” He smiled bitterly soon after that and said. “But, from the looks of it now, the realization of this dream may be too far away. What about you? Do you have any dreams?”

A cold breeze blew past and lifted a few strands of white hair beside the youth’s cheeks lightly. He reached his hand out and tidied his hair while smiling faintly.

“My dream… is the hope that this world will be devoid of all struggles. I don’t want wars to exist.”

“Yes, that’s a really beautiful dream!” Clint raised his thumb. “Although it’s a bit too far-fetched.”

“I’ve always felt that it would be best for everyone to live together peacefully, isn’t that so? Why must we fight each other for our interests before our hatred deepens finally? In the end, neither side knows the source of the war anymore…” the white-haired youth uttered quietly. “However, generations of struggles continue on like that. Endlessly…”

“You’ve said it perfectly!” Clint patted the youth’s shoulder firmly.

“I did? You feel this way too?!” The white-haired youth’s eyes widened slightly while he looked at Clint whose face was filled with admiration.

“Of course! Honestly, who in this world likes going to war? Other than deviants, war maniacs, and careerists, no one likes fighting,” nodded Clint. “Hence, although your dream is very bleak, I will continue to support you!”

“Will you?” A gentle smile appeared on the white-haired youth’s face suddenly. “That’s really wonderful. I always assumed that no one could understand me. I’d never expected to encounter someone here who could actually understand my dream. You’re actually a good person.”

Clint scratched his head and felt slightly embarrassed. This was the first time that someone had praised him like this.

“Hehe, I’m not as great as you made me out to be… You don’t know this, but the first time I laid eyes on you, I felt a familiar feeling.”

“Perhaps this is a part of destiny as well?” said the white-haired youth, smiling.

“Yes, there’s no point thinking of destiny as something bleak, right? We can’t say for sure that destiny isn’t trying to reverse wars either. However, our strength is insufficient in the meantime,” said Clint while laughing.

Right after these words escaped Clint’s mouth, the white-haired youth’s eyes widened suddenly. He stared blankly at Clint who was smiling stupidly. Faintly, a new radiance appeared on his handsome, pale face instantly. It resembled a sacred halo.

“Yes… Perhaps my dream is merely a part of destiny that is trying to lead me on the right path. The thing that I’m moving towards is the signs of destiny!”

“It’s great that you’ve figured it out!” Clint patted the youth’s head firmly. “Alright, go back and rest then. We need to mine more ores in a while!”

“Thank you,” said the white-haired youth while looking at Clint sincerely. “I’ll strive for my dream.”

“No more underestimating your life next time!” Clint nodded happily. After educating this fellow briefly, his mood had suddenly improved as well. He turned around and took long strides while walking towards the mining area.

The white-haired youth watched the back of his figure leave silently while the radiance across his face brightened.

“Yes… Why wasn’t I The Child of Destiny? The signals in my vision are the places that destiny wants me to travel to…” He closed his eyes before a white imprint that was shaped like the ‘Ω’ omega symbol appeared on his forehead suddenly.

“Destiny guided me, it allowed me to arrive in this universe for me to change everything, no?”

He glanced one last time at Clint’s figure that was about to disappear.

“Everything that I’ve done is my true destiny. A successor of the Red King, I had never expected that you would give me such a lesson… Everything is determined by destiny, huh…”

“For my dream… I’m willing to sacrifice everything… Mother, are you ready…?”

He turned around and walked toward another direction of the wasteland. His body disintegrated suddenly, turning into countless shrouds of white smoke that drifted away into the sky.

No one was aware that both of the future strongest individuals had met each other silently on Planet Gideon of the Four-Star Alliance in what was perhaps a coincidental situation.

They were the White King, who had yet to mature, and the similarly immature Red King.

************************

On Planet Scarlet Snow that was extremely far away.

As he was unable to find the traitor of Dragon Light Sect in time, Garen could only return with his members. He had just dispersed his team and leaped back to his own territory before faintly feeling as if new changes had occurred throughout the forces of cause and effect of the major powers of the world.

“What’s going on?”

He furrowed his brows and felt the changes and movements in his surroundings carefully. There were no other noises, but the whooshing and whistling of wind from far away. The birds were too afraid to fly near his surroundings as well. This was an absolute zero area, and everything had been paused in a frozen state. This was the result of the terrifying power that was naturally released by Garen.

“Could it be that the White King and Clint have finally met for the first time?” He suddenly recalled the scene that he had witnessed in the Space-Time Print.

A short while ago all the way to the present day, the first Crown Prince of the Finite people, Sandfly, had killed his parents before ascending the throne of the Finite king within a short span of ten years. He called himself The Child of Destiny and The Emperor of Eternity. He began to unify the war between the Finites and humans.

“If that really happened, I need to increase my speed now,” Garen was very certain that the White King could see how powerful the terrifying abilities of the orbit of cause and effect were. He could also find every weakness and flaw of his opponent. No one could stand before him and challenge him directly, none except for Clint. This was because Clint was the only person whom he could barely consider as a friend and the only person who could understand him.

Garen used the wireless linking network of his Energy Machine Imprint quickly to begin inquiring about the latest news and incidents that had occurred.

After returning from the Blue Frost Sect, he had brought an abundance of valuables with him. He allowed the Scarlet Snow Sect to examine its details deeply. This was especially helpful to the disciples of the lower grades as a lot of these pieces of equipment were directly useful for disciples of lower grades. This increased the support and praises toward Garen within the sect greatly.

Many people believed that Garen truly had good intentions towards Scarlet Snow Sect. As for the suspicious of him killing Rainy, they were not as certain about it anymore. Moreover, if he had really killed her, as an offender who had stolen the Secret Frost Seed, other than a few intimate disciples, no one would really regard Garen as an enemy because of this.

More and more people had started placing their respect for Garen above righteousness. Therefore, even if he had really killed her, it would still be Rainy’s fault.

After returning to his senses from the vast information, Garen saw that five Two-headed Werewolves had appeared behind him silently.

“You’re back? How were the collections?” he asked quietly.

Garen had bestowed the name Turing upon the strongest Two-headed Werewolf. In the Universal Language, the pronunciation of this name meant wolf of winter nights. As for the remaining Two-Headed Werewolves, they were named by Turing one by one. Garen did not ask about them.

“Reporting back to our great master, there are one hundred and twenty-eight types of high-energy mineral veins in total that can help you. Among the ones with the largest reserves, they are three veins with tonnages of over two billion. They are also the ones that are closest to the nearest star region. However, they have been occupied by the stations of other sects,” reported Turing respectfully. “As for the other smaller-scale mineral veins, we already have brothers who are currently extracting and refining them. When you were traveling to Planet Almanac, a portion of the refined mineral resources had already been transported to Planet Scarlet Snow.”

“You’ve done pretty well,” nodded Garen happily. These life forms with disorderly intelligence that were derived from his Distorted Seeds were absolutely loyal toward him. As his life and death were linked with theirs, it was worth it for him to trust them.

There were already more than one hundred and fifty intelligent Two-headed Wolves that he had released now. All of them were disguised as a new breed of Two-headed Wolves that had started to come into contact and engage in trade with other intelligent creatures. After all, the universe was huge, and various non-human races were not rare. Therefore, it was not strange to have another breed of the Two-Headed Wolves.

“Has White Night returned?” Garen suddenly recalled the Gideon Body that had yet to mature now. The future older brother of Clint’s companion was currently still at his weakest stage.

“I’ve heard that he has returned. It seems like he’s suffered some very strange injuries and is currently seeking treatment in the Frost Hall,” answered Turing quietly. After obtaining Garen’s new confidence, he was given the authority to look over even more information.

“Great master, according to your previous arrangements, weren’t you supposed to have gone to Frost Hell to realize the Secret Frost Seed already? Meanwhile, we seem to have obtained the whereabouts of the bejeweled Staff of Absolute Yin as well.”

“Is it the first staff?” asked Garen quietly.

“Yes. Master, the staffs that you found were not embedded with gems. There were only a few that were embedded with gems. However, I’ve heard rumors that it has appeared at the faraway Finite Royal Auction House,” Turing explained.

“Royal Auction House…” Garen exhaled. The Staff of Absolute Yin that was embedded with gems was the only thing that could produce new potential points without requiring the grinding process. The remaining ones which, without the embedments, could only produce potential qi extremely slowly. Even if less than ten years had passed, one would not even need to dream of producing even one potential point.

“Alright.”

Garen closed his eyes.

“No rush, we’ll go again after awhile. There’s no need to hurry now…” He looked inwardly at the six Origin Crystals inside his body that had started to link with each other gradually. He gradually fell into a state of indifference.

He had a premonition that it would probably take a long time before he could enter the Non-falling Level.

Upon seeing this, Turing and the others retreated consciously and increased the safety of their surroundings.

Chapter 1077: Dissimilate 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A year passed in the blink of an eye with the ending of spring and the coming of winter.

Above Planet Scarlet Snow, a black vortex appeared suddenly before a black-haired youth walked out of the teleporting vortex slowly. His face was dull, and a pure, icy, blue flame was burning from his right hand slowly.

Shh shh shh!

Three waves of crispy noises could be heard consecutively before the figures of three elders appeared in front of the youth.

“Carthage, was the incident with the Imperial Commodity Sect your doing?!” Second Elder asked in a deep voice with an unkind expression on his face.

Carthage’s expression remained calm, a hint of surprise could be seen on his face faintly.

“Second Elder, what are you saying? What does the incident with the Imperial Commodity Sect have to do with me? I was determined in refining my Ice Dragonflame. I haven’t taken a step out of my territory.”

“What exactly have you been doing throughout this year? We’re all very aware already, so why do we have to stand here and hypocritically pretend that we don’t know anything?” First Elder had always supported Carthage, however, he was now glaring at him with a somber look on his face.

“I don’t know what you’re saying,” Carthage smiled. Suddenly, he turned his face and looked in another direction before a strange chill soared into the sky there.

Howl…

A clear and melodious wolf’s howl echoed from afar.

The three great elders heard it at the same time. Grave and aghast expressions appeared on each of their faces.

While looking in the direction of the Black Wolf Lair from afar, all four people could see a chain of white clouds that appeared there. It resembled a pearl bracelet that was constantly turning.

“Non-falling Level… This is too soon!” Third Elder’s voice was hoarse and tinged with envy and disbelief. “He just entered the sect not too long ago?!”

“He’s worthy of being known as my Junior Brother,” The smile on Carthage’s face became even more apparent. “Three Elders, please excuse my withdrawal now. Since the fourth Non-falling Level of the Scarlet Snow Sect has come into being, the sect will definitely organize a celebratory event, right?”

None of the three elders replied. They were slightly fearful of Carthage. This supposed disciple was too unfathomable. They were unable to discover his backgrounds despite probing into him secretly a few times. Compared to Garen who had entered the Non-falling Level, they were still more afraid of Carthage.

“You won’t even let me leave. So what’s the exact reason for the Three Elders to surround me today?” Carthage asked helplessly. “You need to know that I’m still busy with many other things…”

Third Elder’s voice was sharp when he spoke.

“Putting the incident with Garen aside first, someone actually saw huge changes occurring inside the Imperial Commodity Sect after you entered! How exactly are you going to explain this?! Imperial Commodity Sect is an ally of my Scarlet Snow Sect. Don’t tell me that you’ve actually participated in sect-destroying movements?”

Carthage smiled faintly.

“Elder, I’m afraid that you didn’t witness this personally. You are just making a baseless claim, correct? I wonder who told you this?”

“It was the elder of the Hollow Inscription Sect!” said Third Elder coldly. “You thought that no one knew about your actions, but you never expected that the elder of Hollow Inscription Sect would pass by and discover it, right?”

“Elder of Hollow Inscription Sect?” Carthage smiled suddenly. “Third Elder, just recently, Hollow Inscription Sect stopped existing… The proof… is gone,” he whispered profoundly.

“You!” Third Elder’s gaze trembled furiously. “Are you trying to fool me? Very well, very well! First Elder, Second Elder, I don’t believe that we cannot stop him today. Let’s move out together!”

First Elder and Second Elder glared at Carthage solemnly now. Finally, the issue within the Scarlet Snow Sect was about to be torn away fully.

********************

A ring of clouds resembling a white pearl necklace rotated above Garen’s head.

He was sitting upright in the center of the mansion’s courtyard when the cold wind whistled naturally. Shrouds of cold air streams surrounded him, turning into layers of substantial and visible white chill. These chill resembled white streamers or ribbons that were constantly revolving and spinning around Garen speedily.

Sparkling peacock-like patterns could be faintly seen at the top of each of these ribbons and streamers. They resembled numerous intangible Frost Peacocks that were constantly spinning and fluttering around him.

Numerous black, giant Werewolves nearby surrounded Garen and protected his safety loyally.

“Unparalleled supreme master of incomparable holiness, we thank our master for granting us life, intelligence, and strength. There is nothing on the earth or in the sky that does not submit itself to the rule of our master…” The Two-headed Giant Werewolf named Turing crouched on the ground while reciting a chant.

These chants had been recited for a continuous year already. Ever since Garen entered and meditated here a year ago, this place had become a prohibited area for non-frost creatures. Every creature that passed by or approached this place would be surrounded and enveloped by extremely terrifying chills, no exceptions.

The few times when Eva and King Cat came over to take a look, they discovered that it was impossible for them to get close. Therefore, they could only turn around and leave.

After reciting his chant, Turing stood up and carefully observed the new changes throughout Garen’s body. Other than the ring of clouds, he did not notice any other new developments. He continued praying for Garen quietly in his heart before turning around and walking in the direction of the lair’s canteen.

At this moment, Garen, who had been sitting down with his legs crossed all this while, slowly opened both of his eyes after a whole year.

He lowered his head and looked at his own chest. A chain of red pearls was spinning there slowly. It was the Non-falling Level Wheel that had been solidified by the Scarlet Snow Technique’s Origin Crystals.

“After one year and fifteen days, it has finally succeeded. The Hellfrost Peacock Technique… is truly terrifying!” he sighed emotionally in his heart. The speed of the Devour ability was enough to simply frighten him.

All of the substances could be used by the Hellfrost Peacock’s Devour ability. However, the difference and the issues lied in how much of it was used.

He looked inwardly at his current body, including his bones, muscles, and internal organs. A strange layer of light that which had a faint glow of a jade glimmered across all of his body parts. This layer of light flowed across the surface of his internal organs slowly, as if it was alive.

“This is the Non-falling Light. In comparison to the initial Inherited Level Energy Field, its strength has increased significantly. If it were to attack the average peak Inherited Levels while they were merely standing there, it would be impossible for them to find a way to destroy this halo layer.”

Garen clenched his fist happily while feeling this incomparably powerful strength surging within his body.

He glanced at his current Attribute Pane.

‘Nonosiva Lin — Strength 40, Agility 40, Vitality 40, Intelligence 35, Potential 48030%. Soul Limit 40.’

Other than his Intelligence which had yet to be fully achieved, all of his other three attributes had reached their limits fully. These limits referred to the terrifying degree of 40 points.

Garen stood up and reached his left hand out before pointing each of his fingers.

Shh!

A substantial air wave shot out frantically like an arrow and pierced through a nearby enclosure of solid ice with a ‘puff’. No one knew where it had flown to as there was only a clear round hole that was left behind on the wall.

“This is the limit…” Garen exhaled deeply. It seemed as though all of the air in the courtyard was swept away by an enormous beast suddenly. An intense pulling force dragged the surrounding Werewolves immediately and attempted to fly towards Garen.

Some of the broken stones and icicles around them flew around as well and shot towards Garen.

This was the terrifying effect of his single breath.

Pfoo…

Exhale.

The terrifying air currents surged out of Garen’s mouth suddenly, sweeping up violent hurricanes instantly. They blew at the surrounding Werewolves, whose movements were initially being dragged down, causing them to roll out towards the vicinity. It gave them an abnormally hard time.

“This is the Non-falling Level, huh… It’s truly a terrifying degree… But I don’t know if the other Non-falling Levels have such powerful bodies as mine.”

Garen guessed that the answer was ‘no’. The limits of the physical bodies of the humans in this world were much lower than his own. They would probably reach their limit around 20 points or so. After that, the Energy Machinists would not rely on upgrading their physical fitness, but would instead merge external matters to increase their own strengths while simultaneously strengthening their own skills greatly. They would use their skills to produce their Non-falling Light to protect themselves.

This way, they would not rely greatly on their physical fitness. At the same time, their lengthy lives allowed them to fully make up for external substances and fuse with them slowly in order to upgrade themselves.

“It’s fortunate that my physical fitness isn’t something that I rely on,” Garen knew that this quality of his was not considered exceptional among the Energy Machinists of Planet Naga. He was considered average at best because even stronger ones existed among the Energy Machinists who were fused with external substances.

He could feel that his current state was somewhat similar to the Totem world. Every part of him was covered by that layer of Non-falling Light, including the strong winds that had randomly blown out earlier. Everything was like this. After being covered by a layer of extremely powerful Non-falling Light, even a normal attack would become extremely terrifying.

After examining his own situation briefly, Garen noticed suddenly that all of his attacks were covered by this Non-falling Light, making them very similar to the previous Totem world.

At the same time, the ones that made him the happiest were Turing and the other Werewolves.

The layer of Non-falling Light covered not only himself but also Turing and the other Werewolves.

“Isn’t this the real meaning behind the use of ‘Non-falling’ in the Non-falling Level?” Garen could sense that he was the only one who could see this Non-falling Light because Turing and the other Werewolves had not seemed to realize it at all.

Whoosh!

Suddenly, a slender silhouette appeared behind Garen. The person who had arrived held a sword in his hand and looked at Garen calmly while completely ignoring the Werewolves around him.

“Garen, it’s great that you’ve broken through. There’s a ceremony that I need you to attend in my place,” This person was Carthage who was clashing with the three elders earlier.

“Ceremony?” Garen turned around while his heart trembled slightly. Despite him entering the Non-falling Level already, Carthage still had an unperturbed look on his face. Moreover, Garen had not even noticed when he had arrived. This made his heart slightly more fearful.

“Yes, a welcoming ceremony from the Magnetic Field. They may even bring the Major Sect Battle forward,” Carthage said lightly. He glanced at Garen’s chest where the Non-falling Wheel was located. “Your progress rate is too slow.” A black pearl appeared in his hand suddenly before he flicked it gently.

The pearl landed on Garen’s hand immediately.

“It’s Bloody Sea Pearls, devour it,” said Carthage calmly.

Without any hesitation, Garen swallowed the pearl in one mouthful directly.

Other than a large number of blood abilities, he had already guessed that the red pearl from earlier also possessed extremely potent means of activating potential. In order to enter the Non-falling Level so quickly, perhaps Carthage had previously exhibited means of overdrafting his potential earlier.

“Since the Non-falling Level is the seventh stage, one must grasp the Board Realm in order to go any higher. This is the Timeless Board. Take it and comprehend it. I’ll come back and get it after three days. How much you can comprehend depends on you.” Carthage made his hand quiver before a white jade colored board descended before Garen gently and was caught by him.

“What’s the Timeless Board?” asked Garen while furrowing his eyebrows. He had never heard of this thing at all.

Carthage waved his hand and released a separation Energy Field that obstructed their surroundings.

“The seventh Non-falling Level produces the Non-falling Light while the eighth level requires you to comprehend boards. Use it to fuse your Willpower and skills into one body and grasp its energy. You can achieve the first step of controlling your Thousand Gravitational Force through this. The Timeless Board is core to solidify everything that the eighth level powerhouses require. In order to enter the ninth level, you need to create a Timeless Board first. Next, you will create the Sublime Board before finally entering the Ultimate Board.”

“In other words, the Timeless Board is the symbol of the eighth level. Timeless Board, Sublime Board, and Ultimate Board. The ultimate end refers to the tenth level of the Perpetual Motioners, right?” Garen asked quietly.

“You don’t need to know so much. Your maximum limit is Level Nine, while Level Ten will be eternally impossible. Even for a Level Nine, your current self…” Carthage did not continue speaking but turned around and left slowly instead.

Garen’s gaze followed him into the distance.

“When will the ceremony start? To what extent must I be prepared?”

“One month later. Everything is up to you. That’s right, the Timeless Board in your hand belonged to the Guardian of the Blue Frost Sect,” Carthage’s voice echoed from afar.

Garen’s heart trembled violently. As expected!

Carthage’s strength was apparently enough to kill the Level Eight Guardian…

Chapter 1078: Dissimilate 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He watched as Carthage left towards the distance swiftly, before disappearing in the faraway sky.

His heart felt indescribably heavy.

“It still isn’t enough huh…” The Non-falling Level was what he looked up to previously. However, it was merely an unassuming, minor role in the eyes of others.

He recalled the unimaginably mysterious minaret that he had seen in Scarlet Snow Sect previously. It was the Fermium Cloud Tower on Planet Naga. Scarlet Snow Sect was a faction that was established by the Secret Technique powerhouses upon arriving in this world. Meanwhile, it was rumored that the Fermium Cloud Tower was the remains that were left behind by Scarlet Snow Sect during their glory days of the past. Many mysterious things were still left behind inside.

“Frost Hell as well. I’ll go visit Frost Hell briefly first to awaken the Secret Frost Seed. After that, I’ll go directly to the Fermium Cloud Tower before attending the ceremony!” Garen planned as such.

Looking at the Timeless Board in his hands, Garen once again sat down with his legs crossed. His joy of breaking through to the next level was diminished by Carthage.

The Timeless Board resembled a normal blue plate. Engraved silver lines on it reflected silver light, but he could not determine their functions. If he were to discard it at a random auction house, perhaps no one would be able to see that it was actually the core of everything within the body of a Level Eight powerhouse like himself.

Nonetheless, an item that looked so normal could actually support every aspect of a Level Eight powerhouse.

Garen dispersed all the Werewolves to continue protecting this area.

Meanwhile, he fondled the Timeless Board, gently feeling the silver lines on it.

After the Mirror of True Techniques was the Board Realm. Garen did not have any clues in his mind. He was not a true peak prodigy or a person with the highest comprehension. He was merely a powerhouse who had relied on the Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s horrifying Devour ability to improve.

He had yet to even reach the Silver Mirror of the Mirror of True Techniques, much less the Board Realm.

The basic ancient Endorian civilizations did not have Board Realms. Instead, their foundations were purely based off the Living and Dying Secret Techniques. The perfection of his current Hellfrost Peacock Technique already possessed the Appraisal of Army Level powerhouses. These were the strongest aspects of the ancient Endorian civilization that was only second to the True Soul and Demon King Level.

“According to the differentiation of the realm of this world, the Mirror of True Techniques should probably fuse every part of itself to hatch and derive a new strength with qualitative changes. Meanwhile, the board uses some of the strength to fuse with the external world to achieve the effect of controlling a part of the universe’s power.” Garen’s mind related all of the information that he had obtained. He began to analyze and determine what the facets were actually like.

“Carthage said that the Timeless Board could control the Thousand Gravitational Force. Therefore, it’s clear that my assumption tallied with it very much. However, the entire situation is probably much more complicated.” Garen did not even have the Silver Mirror now, much less the Board. After researching for half a day, he did not obtain any results. Instead, a somewhat strange flighty feeling stirred within him.

This feeling stunned him slightly before he gathered his thoughts quickly and stopped focusing attentively on the Timeless Board.

Beep beep…beep beep…

Suddenly, a contact request appeared on his Energy Machine Imprint.

Garen glanced at it and discovered that it was the woman whom he had met at the Remora Business Alliance during his earlier return. Her name was Sandor and Garen still remembered her gift of his Spaceship to him.

“So it’s Miss Sandor. We have not been in contact for a while now.” He turned on the communication channel.

“Yes, it’s been more than a year.” Sandor’s face appeared before Garen. She was still as spirited as ever. “Mr. Garen, we’ve found many of the holy tree branches that you needed. They’re currently being sent to your Planet Scarlet Snow. Please check and accept them!”

“Just in time!” A smile instantly appeared on Garen’s face. “I was just thinking about it when you sent a message to say that they’ve arrived. I’ll transfer the payment right over now.”

“No rush. You can pay later after you’ve examined the goods,” said Sandor while waving her hand. “This is a small matter, but I have a minor problem here that requires your assistance for a while.”

“Just tell me what is it.” The other party had assisted him greatly and even gifted him a Spaceship. It was only right for Garen to repay her kindness.

“It’s like this. My younger brother and sister wish to go to the City of Nagadako to experience the grand meeting of Energy Machinists. I don’t know if Mr. Garen could…” said Sandor in a slightly embarrassed manner.

Among the merchants, those who were ranked outside the first ten of the business alliance did not even have the right to rub shoulders with the rest from afar. Meanwhile, Energy Machinists were like rich and imposing masters. A random Level-Eight or Level-Nine Energy Machinist would greatly surpass a merchant in terms of wealth. Mech Pilots who had yet to reach the Inherited Level did not have a position to brag about within the Energy Machinist world. They were unlike level five Energy Machinists. Hence, someone like her from the Remora Business Alliance was even worse off.

If Sandor had not come into contact with a sect Energy Machinist like Garen, she would not be able to even dream about attending grand meetings like this.

“The Three Major Metropolis will be organizing grand meetings at the same time so this won’t be a problem. I will send someone from my sect to meet them. You can just send me the information first. When the time comes, you can contact my junior brother directly.” Garen responded frankly and gave Bainster’s contact to the other party immediately. He shared brief instructions to pay attention to certain matters before disconnecting the connection.

He contacted Bainster to receive the Spaceship that was on the way delivering the goods and briefed him on the tasks and other matters ahead.

“Why haven’t I seen Hillco for so long?” Garen recalled suddenly and asked casually.

A resentment look appeared on Bainster’s face immediately when he heard Garen’s words.

“My Lord, are you only recalling this now…? Hillco left a long time ago.”

“Left?” Garen truly did not notice it. He furrowed his eyebrows after hearing what had been said.

“Yes. You didn’t like her the same way, My Lord. When she had lost all hope, she just left naturally,” said Bainster honestly.

“What does that have to do with anything?” Garen was speechless. “Have there been any new changes over on Planet Naga?”

“There were indeed changes and major ones as well.” Speaking of this, Bainster’s face darkened abruptly. “Numerous small and middle scale sects have been completely destroyed but we don’t know the culprit behind it. The Alliance has already called many meetings but no one has been able to take any effective measures. Another thing is that not long ago, Dragon Eye Sect was…annihilated as well.”

“Dragon Eye Sect was annihilated as well?” Garen’s heart sank. Such quick speed! This was definitely not Carthage’s work only. There were about ten more years between the present day and the historical Energy Machinist Extinction. So how could it begin now?!

“Senior Brother, do you think our Scarlet Snow Sect will…” Bainster’s voice was trembling slightly. “There have been people within the sect who have been leaving quietly. However, they are merely the children of wealthy households who wasted money to make a quick fortune here.”

“I’m well aware of this matter. You go and complete the task that I instructed. The other matters will not affect our Scarlet Snow Sect temporarily so don’t worry,” said Garen calmly.

He recalled Carthage’s mysterious attitude all this while. He knew that Carthage had nurtured himself until now because his true identity had yet to be exposed. Moreover, his relationship with the Red King was not revealed yet either. Once these layers and relations were exposed, perhaps the first person who would want to kill Garen himself would be Carthage.

Right now he was solely nurturing another reliable helper but everything else in the future was uncertain.

Garen’s face was solemn as he disconnected the call. He picked up the Timeless Board again but could not feel any main threads still.

He heaved a long sigh. He felt that he had given up completely.

“I’m not a true prodigy after all, huh…I didn’t get anything despite confronting a mountainous obstacle.”

Putting down the Timeless Board, Garen stood up.

“I’ll go to Frost Hell first then. I’ll look on briefly at the Secret Frost Seeds of my Scarlet Snow Sect seniors of the past eras. Perhaps I will be able to gain something.”

Garen leaped up and released an Energy Field out of thin air to suspend his own body in mid-air. The Energy Field canceled out gravity directly, allowing him to fly towards headquarters.

All of the Werewolves below raised their heads and looked upwards before crouching on the ground devoutly.

“We bid you a safe journey, respected master.”

A string of voices echoed upwards from the ground below.

Garen glanced down and saw that Turing was ordering the Werewolves and members of the sect to dump high energy substances and crystals into a giant pit. Spending at least a few thousand golden crystals which was not a small sum, these were the items that they had extracted from other places. The sum was also equivalent to the yearly income of certain countries. However, only a small amount had been refined despite all of this.

From afar, Garen could see Turing crouching on the ground towards his direction, while praying for him loudly and respectfully.

He shook his head. These Werewolves had already viewed him as an almighty and unparalleled deity. After correcting them many times, he was too lazy to concern himself with this matter anymore because it was completely useless.

He focused his mind on Frost Hell again. This was Scarlet Snow Sect’s highest temple that was much more precious when compared to the Ancestral Temple and the Great Wall Library. In order to enter this place, one would need to request permission from the three elders first.

Without thinking further, he flew in the direction of the First Elder.

“The First Elder has shut himself off for the purpose of studying. Please do not disturb him.” Just as he had entered the First Elder’s territory, a robotic patrolling bird in the air alerted a warning.

Garen frowned, retreated and flew in the direction of Third Elder.

In the woods, an elderly guard captain dressed in white spoke in an embarrassed tone.

“The Third Elder has yet to return from his expedition until now. Senior Brother, would you mind waiting?”

“Expedition?” Garen’s eyebrows were knitted together tightly. “What about Second Elder then? Do you know what has happened?”

“I know a bit. It seems like Second Elder left with Third Elder together for the expedition,” the guard captain answered quickly.

“What a coincidence? None of the three elders are here?” Garen felt something was amiss. “What about the Great Supervisors?”

There were numerous Great Supervisors and Inherited Level powerhouses who lived in seclusion at the headquarters. As there were less than ten of these people, at least one of them should be around, right?

“At least half of the Great Supervisors have left on an expedition as well. The remaining ones are still in their respective precincts.”

“I see. You can go back down now,” nodded Garen. Carthage had also left on an expedition to attend some ceremony. It was obvious that his main aim was to send himself away as well.

“Could it be that they’re about to battle the Guardian masters now?” His heart trembled when he made this assumption.

At this moment, he felt a sudden, explosive burn spreading through the inside of his body. It resembled a bomb that was exploding at an extremely terrifying speed.

“It was the black pearl that I ate earlier!!” Garen recalled the pearl that Carthage had given him earlier. He had never expected that it would only display its effects now.

He stumbled a few steps backward, his face turning green and pale. His body seemed like petroleum had been ignited, burning instantly.

“Is it starting to make an overdraft on my potential now?!” He suppressed the flames firmly and turned to fly in the direction of Frost Hell. The qi around his body seemed as though it had solidified and was scurrying upwards madly. He had just achieved Non-falling Level qi before it began to expand suddenly.

The cries, painful screams, and yells of countless people echoed beside his ears like phonism. Garen’s vision began to blur, his ears were turning deaf.

“It’s really not a bad human body…” In the midst of his daze, he seemed to hear a cold voice. “Carthage had really troubled himself to actually prepare such a good human body for me…”

Boom!!

A thunderous noise crashed through the clear sky. Garen’s body suddenly stiffened while flying through high altitude. He stopped in mid-air.

An unknown and terrifying qi locked him in place firmly.

A white colored dwarf that was only the size of a child appeared slowly behind Garen. The dwarf was dressed in a suit of white technological armor with purple lines; two horns that resembled those of a cow grew from the top of his head.

The dwarf’s eyes and lips of this were dark purple in color. There was a wicked and cruel smile on its face while the strangest thing about it was that it only had three digits respectively on both of his hands and feet.

Raising his right hand, the dwarf used his thick, three fingers to claw the back of Garen’s head gently.

Instantly, his entire body melted into shrouds of white smoke and flew towards the back of Garen’s head burrowing inside quickly.

“The prelude begins! Hehehehe…” It’s high-pitched, terrifying laughter echoed throughout the high altitude endlessly. However, no one else could hear it besides Garen.

Chapter 1079: Legacy 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“So this is Carthage’s secret weapon!?”

Garen felt his heart drop, yet surprisingly, he was strangely calm.

He expected Carthage to have some sort of ace up his sleeves, but he did not expect Carthage to build his body as a target to be possessed.

Allowing the creepy dwarf behind him enter his body, Garen’s expression was blank. Although he could neither see nor hear, he could feel the trace of an evil intention surging into his hindbrain, the main organ that controlled an Energy Machinist’s Energy Machine Imprint.

“Possession? That’s what I’m least afraid of!!”

As he slowly curled his body, Garen took a deep breath.

Hiss… A huge terrifying swirl of air started spreading wildly in the air.

Waves of white, silk-like airstreams were sucked into Garen’s lungs from all directions.

“It’s useless… There’s no point in struggling because every fiber of your being shall become a part of me…” The sinister voice started ringing in Garen’s body.

Garen gave a smile and abruptly opened his mouth wide.

Roar!

An indescribably deafening rumble came out of his mouth.

Black shadows of nine snake-like salamander were projected below him, looking ferocious and demonic.

“Idiot! I haven’t even got to devour the creations outside, and you dare scramble around in my body!!” There was a trace of sarcasm of Garen’s face.

“Wait! What is this!?” There was something off about the voice. “Why do you have something like this in your body!?”

Golden spots started forming on Garen’s skin. They were like dragon scales, covering Garen’s entire body and gradually spreading toward his head.

“You’re merely a Non-falling Level!” The vicious voice was getting more furious. “No! That’s not possible! There’s no way your body is not reformed!! Damn it! Carthage, how dare you fool me!”

All of a sudden, the golden spots spread upward and covered Garen’s head entirely.

The voice instantly let out a horrible shriek.

“No!!”

A wisp of smoke was urging to rush out from the back of Garen’s head, an arm slowly reaching out. Suddenly, a black shadow emerged and bit on the figure.

Garen, who was floating in mid-air, started opening his eyes slowly, his entire body was glowing a bright golden hue. Meanwhile, bursts of beasts chewing could be heard.

“No! How can I die at a place like this!!” The voice roared in a fit of rage as he struggled, along with the dreadful sounds of the nine salamanders.

Bulges started forming around Garen’s body. His arms, his chest, his back, and both his legs started swelling. The swells would last just a few seconds before shrinking and disappearing. The swollen areas then returned back to normal. The body parts continued to swell and shrink simultaneously, causing an extremely disgusting scene.

“It’s useless,” Garen said calmly. “The ancient Nine-headed Dragon Soul is specifically used against souls. Therefore, if you still existed in flesh, I wouldn’t even stand a chance against you. Unfortunately…”

Thick layers of frost started spreading upward from his foot.

“Let us form into one then…” A cold smirk crept up Garen’s face. As he raised his arm, a huge, black dragon’s shadow emerged from his palms and encircled him above the air. The several black dragon shadows had him entirely cocooned in the middle, forming a ball of black shadow.

“No!” I am Jeros, and I will fall in a place like this!! I have not gotten my revenge yet! Not yet…!” The scream stopped abruptly.

Inside the dark shadow, Garen reappeared.

The black shadows gradually went away, and everything went back to normal. Garen’s body was back to normal as well, leaving no trace of anything that just happened.

Poof!

A large cloud of smoke started spreading to all directions from Garen, forming a white ring of cloud in the sky.

What initially seemed to be an extreme danger, was eliminated within seconds.

Garen could feel his Cold Energy reaching its limit within his body. With his Fourteenth Level of Scarlet Snow Technique just recently being achieved, he actually managed to engulf its energy during that short period of time when his spiritual body was possessed, and he succeeded in breaking through the Fifteenth Level. The cloud of white ring just now was the sign of a breakthrough to the Fifteenth Level.

“Level Fifteen…” There was no change in Garen’s expression. To Carthage, if he was not at the peak of the Eighteenth Level in the Scarlet Snow Technique, it would be tough for him to actually inflict any sort of harm.

From Jeros’ powerful spiritual body, Garen intercepted plenty of information.

“Oh, Jeros, a member of the Light of Justice huh?” He was swiftly rearranging all the information he was getting.

The Hellfrost Peacock Technique and Nine-headed Dragon both had a formidable power against soul abilities. After all, the Endors were specifically against the culture of modern soul practicing. In this universe, there was probably nobody else other than Garen who knew more about the battles from a spiritual perspective. Jeros actually died in a pretty decent way.

After the Nine-headed Dragon engulfed most of his energy, it swiftly shrunk back to its soul form, but not before spitting out some of Jeros’ memory fragments.

“As expected… Almost the same as what I’ve guessed.” After briefly looking at the memory fragments, he swiftly remembered all the content recorded.

At that moment, people started crowding around below due to the commotion in the sky. A lot of the people from the Scarlet Snow Sect thought Garen was actually practicing some sort of a special technique, hence the terrifying tremors of energy.

Even some of the Great Supervisors, who were constantly practicing all day, were taken aback and probed into what was happening with Garen.

Swoosh!

Carthage appeared right before Garen.

“Jeros wasn’t a problem, was he?”

“Of course not,” Garen responded with a familiar smile from Jeros’ memory, a sinister aura dissipating from his body.

“That’s good, don’t get in the way of my plan.”

“It was just a minor accident,” Garen mumbled. “I’m just having some spiritual connection problems with that kid, so I need some time to completely fuse with him spiritually. Fuse, mind you!”

“Fuse? Can I help with anything?” Carthage glared at Garen, his eyes were cold and as sharp as knives.

“Level Fifteen!” Garen’s heart missed a beat. He had finally managed to see Carthage’s level clearly! Level Fifteen Scarlet Snow Technique! Other than the giant arm’s true form he called forth the other day, the power he held within this body should be Level Fifteen!

“No need, I can handle it myself. Just focus on managing your own things,” Garen’s voice was filled with an indescribable sinisterness.

“Are you sure?” Carthage suddenly chuckled.

“Yes I’m sure,” Garen said coldly.

“Alright then, this body is the best there is. Try not to spoil it, it’s very hard to nurture another one,” Carthage said while walking away.

“Oh yeah, Kaos has arrived at the South Pole Planet, do you want to go fetch him?” He asked suddenly.

Garen remained expressionless.

“Kaos, are we even that close? Stop playing with me, Carthage.”

Carthage turned around and stared at him with a silent smile.

“Seems like the fusion process was just nice, rest well and recover soon then.”

“I don’t need you to remind me that!” Garen snorted.

Beads of cold sweat were actually trickling down his back. He had no idea who Kaos was, he could only sense that Carthage was suspecting him already, so he simply connected bits and pieces from his memory. He was tensed and ready to make a move already, but who knew he would actually make the right connection.

“You shall be in charge of the Scarlet Snow Sect, I’m leaving for a period of time.” With his last words, Carthage suddenly shot out into the distance, disappearing into thin air.

“Hmph!” With a snort, Garen dived toward the Frost Hell. Perhaps the Secret Frost Seed’s Inspiration might do his Nine-Level Tempered Body Technique some good, other than the Destructive Impact Fist. These two secret techniques were well-suited for him. If he could advance to a higher level, these techniques would definitely boost his Hellfrost Peacock Technique.

Below them, Eva and Solomon, the eighth Demonic Spirit, witnessed the whole conversation between Garen and Carthage. They just could not hear the actual conversation.

“What are these two up to this time!” The mummy-like Demonic Spirit said in an eerie tone.

“Someday, I shall seek revenge for Rainy one way or another!” Eva said in an icy-cold tone before flying off toward Second Elder’s place.

*******************

“If I really had turned against Carthage just now, what are the chances of me winning?!” Walking along a white-blue ice tunnel, Garen recalled what just happened.

Right now, he had fully caught up to Carthage’s body power, which was a Level Fifteen. Besides that, he was sure by now that this body was not Carthage’s true form. The terrifying huge arm that he saw the other day was Carthage’s true ability.

“Every member of the Light of Justice under Chinande is a Level-Ten Perpetual Motioner. If Carthage is one of them as well, I definitely don’t stand a chance against him. But, I’ve already been advancing to higher levels in the shortest time possible, it’d be meaningless to continue pushing myself, even with most of my Hellfrost Peacock Technique. Perhaps I shouldn’t be merely focusing on this world’s pure energy…”

Once again, he focused on superimposing his secret techniques.

There was a total of eighteen levels of the Scarlet Snow Technique, but other than the Teacher Ancestor who started up the sect, nobody else had managed to practice this certain secret technique up to its peak. It was simply unrealistic to think that one could reach the peak by relying on this secret technique. Even Garen originally wanted to practice this secret technique just to condense more of his Scarlet Snow Technique’s soul.

At this point, if he were to refer to the process earlier before, he should be able to condense a new kind of Soul Seed already. Yet, Garen still did not feel any trace of his Soul Seed condensing.

“Perhaps the Secret Frost Seed would inspire me.”

Passing through the blue-white ice tunnel, Garen came to a wide, arched white hall.

The hall was densely packed with shimmering blue spheres of light, and every light had a name carved on to it.

As he first stepped into the hall, Garen could sense a strong presence of souls that overwhelmed him.

“This!?”

He was shaken.

An immense force was pushing toward him.

“I don’t have any rights to summon, that’s why I was rejected by all the other seeds! But this…” Although Garen was stifled by the monstrous force pushing at him, there was a sharp, never-before-seen glint in his eyes.

“This… All these are Soul Seeds!”

He had always wondered what was all about the Scarlet Snow Sect’s Secret Frost Seed, but he had never expected them to be beads of souls of secret techniques that were extremely concentrated and condensed!

Click…

A solid layer of dark blue was slowly creeping up Garen’s legs.

“Freeze me? You want to freeze my Hellfrost Peacock?” Garen smirked.

“All creatures of the world can never escape from fading…”

With his arm raised, he placed his palms against the tremendous force gushing toward him.

Chapter 1080: Legacy 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The atmosphere started to vibrate.

Whoosh!

A strong gust of Cold Energy started gushing out from Garen’s body, covering the layer of frost on his legs, which was then shattered. The Cold Energy was pure and white, with seemingly no contamination whatsoever. It then continued along the mysteriously-patterned floor and spread towards all the soul seeds in the hall.

“Faded Creation!”

Garen stretched his arms wide, and a horrifying burst of Cold Energy started spreading to his surroundings even faster until everything was completely still, frozen in the pure-white ice blocks.

A billow of crystals started forming in layers beneath Garen’s feet as they started spreading toward the entire hall.

The hall was degenerating. The original layer of ice was cracking, and after being infected, its original ice-blue color turned into a shade of pure white, which was an even higher leveled pure crystal.

“What… is this Cold Energy!!??”

Virtual shadows appeared above every Soul Seed. These shadows were somewhat tall and short, some of them resembled males and some of them resembled females. Every one of them had a formidable chill that would make people fear. For an ordinary person, just one glance would have thoroughly frozen the person’s soul to death.

They were the dead Teacher Ancestors of multiple generations in the Scarlet Snow Sect’s history, either sacrificed in war battles or died from natural causes. They all did have a similarity: they had all practiced the Scarlet Snow Technique to its peak already.

“These are Teacher Ancestors of the past generations!” Garen was shocked and the violent chills stilled suddenly.

The white chill fused with the blue-white chill, turning the hall into two ice rooms, with Garen and at least Teacher Ancestors being at two completely different spectrums.

“I did not expect there will still be disciples who can practice such a pure and ultimate chill…”

A female Teacher Ancestor spoke solemnly.

“So many years… We’ve waited for so many years…”

“I can’t remember already. A hundred years, a thousand years, two thousand years, or perhaps even longer.”

“But the wait was worthwhile, and we made it through the long wait, didn’t we?” Among the few figures, the black shadow with the strongest trace of chill silently appeared.

“Just when our souls are almost drained out, destiny has sent us such a pure Body of Ice.”

Garen focused his stare on the figure who was entirely pitch black, only a pair of fluorescent blue eyes glowing could be seen. Even the figure’s face was unnoticeable.

“The original ancestors?!”

“An unprecedented Body of Ice… So authentic, so pure…” The person was in awe.

“Such a chill has far exceeded the Scarlet Snow Technique’s standards!” A tall and scrawny Teacher Ancestor said in a hushed tone.

“Everyone, have we come to a decision?” The original Teacher Ancestor asked.

The entire hall was quiet.

After a good while, a handsome Teacher Ancestor finally laughed out.

“At first, we thought we’d never see hope, that’s why we were forced to just wait. Yet, when the time has now come and opportunity has landed right in front of our faces… here we are, being anxious and mindful.”

“Yeah! Isn’t this the hope I’ve always been waiting for? Now that it’s here, I’m recoiling in fear instead,” Another person among the crowd laughed as well.

“Teacher Ancestors!” Garen wanted to say something.

“We’re not Teacher Ancestors, we’re just their last trace of conviction condensed by their will,” The black shadow in the center answered. “If it wasn’t your chill that activated us, we might have just vanished forever in history after another hundred of years, and nobody would’ve known that we actually existed before.”

Garen inhaled deeply. Leaving one’s will in a Soul Seed to last a couple thousand years was something he understood, it was one of the magic of the Endors as their knowledge regarding souls had reached great heights.

“Due to the fact that I didn’t reach the so-called Board Realm, I never had the chance to join the Perpetual Motioners even until the day I died. I’m not reconciled to this yet!!” The original Teacher Ancestor who spoke just now said with a sour expression which clearly showed his reluctance.

“As one of the most powerful prodigies in the Scarlet Snow Sect history, even transmigrating between worlds along the Mother Stream until here, but I still wasn’t able to break through any single Perpetual Motioner Level!”

“So what if I don’t understand Board!? My Secret Technique is Army-Level, even the Demon King Level is nothing less than a Perpetual Motioner!” The original Teacher Ancestor spoke softly. “That’s why I didn’t accept defeat just like that. Even when I died in battle at the end, I still gathered all my essence and converted it into my very own Soul Seed, so I can wait for my next chance.”

Garen finally made out the person’s background story, he was indeed the original Teacher Ancestor, the Secret Technique powerhouse who established the Scarlet Snow Sect. Not only that, the other person was freakishly similar to Garen. Both of them traveled along the Mother Stream until they reached this current world, it was just that he was less fortunate as he did not have such an intrepid born talent. Besides that, he was not able to see through the general trend of events and he could not transmigrate through several worlds continuously. He could only drift around according to the current.

“Now, I’ve finally seen hope.” The original Teacher Ancestor was staring at Garen with eyes overflowing of hope. “Tell me, is Army Level really any lesser than a Perpetual Motioner?”

Immediately, the hole regained peace once again while every single soul had their eyes on Garen.

Garen looked around and saw the same expression everyone was wearing on their faces. Each of them seemed anxious and exhausted, not forgetting the hopeful looks they were aiming at Garen. They had been waiting for this answer far too long. This was the highest form of belief of Secret Techniques, a sort of devout, a kind of unbreakable faith!

As a Secret Technician, Garen had the same faith and belief. Although his faith was once shaken, now that he had successfully broken through Level Eight of his Hellfrost Peacock Technique, all his doubts had been completely erased.

On the other hand, these people, the ancestors, were different. Their conditions were far worse than his when they began, yet they still adhered for so many years.

Ignoring viewpoints and personalities, just this perseverance alone that lasted a couple of thousand years, this willpower they showed, was enough for him to pay them the highest respect already.

“To be frank, I don’t know whether Secret Techniques or Mechs are stronger.” He said slowly. Looking at the stunned stares from the people around him, he changed his direction.

“But I will personally give it a try. I might be able to see the things that you can’t see clearly.”

The hall returned to its original quiet state as the slightly-disappointed expressions lighted up once again with a glimmer of hope.

“I shall become the strongest Frost Secret Technician in the history of this world. Not just one of them, but the strongest!” Garen held out his hand as a deadly chill hovered above his palms. Traces of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s pure chill started converging and slowly, a white crystal started forming bits by bits in his palms.

“If it’s you, then perhaps…” The original Teacher Ancestor said softly.

A cold wind constantly whirled around the hall, and everyone fell into silence instantly.

Maybe it was half an hour, maybe it was an hour, or maybe it was longer than that. Finally, the original Teacher Ancestor spoke again.

“Your presence today is just to seek inspiration from the pure Cold Realm that I’ve been waiting for, am I right?”

He looked around.

“Are all of you still unwilling to let it go?”

“Not let it go? How is that possible?!” A tall and slender female Teacher Ancestor snickered, “Isn’t this the ultimate hope I’ve been waiting for all these years? Let us lend him a helping hand!”

She suddenly turned around and transformed into a thread of blue chill. She then rushed toward Garen and encircled him before spinning around him rapidly.

“Even Annie gave up willingly, how can we be lagging behind so much!” The second Teacher Ancestor suddenly broke down before turning into a blue thread and rushing toward Garen.

“With all that we have, go… Improve your Scarlet Snow Technique to level so great it is never-before-seen by anyone else!” The third Teacher Ancestor, too, transformed into a thread of light.

“Our will, our faith, take it… Take it all… All creature of the world can never escape from fading.”

“You! You shall become the strongest of them all!! Freeze everything…”

A bunch of threads starting swarming towards Garen, encircling him and spinning around him swiftly.

The sturdy, black shadow standing in the middle then held out his hand, placing it relatively against Garen’s palms from a distance.

“Inherit all our willpower, may you freeze anything that comes in your way. It’s too bad… I can’t see it anymore…”

Boom!

With a soft crash, he transformed into a blue thread and joined the torrent of chills; it encircled Garen and started spinning as well.

“Go… Go and become the most powerful man of this generation! Bring along our will and faith!!”

The original Teacher Ancestor spoke lastly and his words echoed in the hall.

The blue threads were still spinning around Garen rapidly like an exquisite chiffon. It even looked like a shapeless blue cloud.

A vast amount of pure Cold Energy was swarming around Garen. At the same time, extensive experiences of practicing the Scarlet Snow Technique from the Teacher Ancestors of multiple generations were also pouring into Garen’s mind.

Garen understood that the wills instilled within these Soul Seeds were waiting for a perfect moment like this.

Yet, he did not expect that he would trigger such a massive legacy. Every Scarlet Snow Technique essence of Scarlet Snow Sect’s Teacher Ancestors was fusing within his body at the moment in high speed.

Various chills of different attributes were sinking into the faded, dead-silent peacock’s chill. Along with the strongest faith of Secret Techniques, every chill surrendered to the dead silence unconditionally, which then fused together within his body.

A delicate layer of armor, as white as jade, slowly covered every inch of Garen’s body – his head, chest, arms, lower body and both legs. Two horns arched out of the ice armor at his waist part as if it was covering Garen’s waist like a belt.

Buzz… A white ring of halo appeared at the back of Garen’s head. That was a product converged from every Teacher Ancestor’s soul’s energy focused together, meaning that this armor was extremely powerful.

The dead silent chill was getting stronger by the moment, while his Scarlet Snow Technique’s grades were once again increasing under the increment of the armor.

Grade Fifteen was slowly broken through… Grade Sixteen… Grade Seventeen… Grade Eighteen!

The last three grades were just suddenly broke through within such a short amount of time. The last three grades were mainly to increase the texture of one’s chill. Garen’s chill itself already had a decent texture, to begin with, in addition to the priming given by the Teacher Ancestors of multiple generations and the input of past experiences through the soul armor, he had reached a whole new level of understanding toward chills.

A breakthrough like this was nothing extraordinary.

Grade Eighteen represented the ultimate Scarlet Snow Technique. There were altogether eighteen grades of Scarlet Snow Technique, which would be equivalent to a Level-Nine Energy Machinist.

“Who knew there would be martyrs like them in this world!” Garen stared silently at everything shattered in front of him. With his head bent low, he solemnly paid respect as a fellow Secret Technician.

“I will fulfill all your wishes.”

The armor on his body shone a flicker of white light which vanished within seconds, it then formed a V-shaped white pattern. His aura once again returned to the Non-Falling Level, and he finally turned away slowly.

The Frost Hell shall no longer exist from today onwards.

Chapter 1081: Mad Increase 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The weather on the Scarlet Snow Planet was becoming warmer. The land initially covered in snow was now warming up, the snow was gradually melting away, turning into icy water flowing down the sides of the mountains and forming new rivers toward the city.

The people of the Scarlet Snow Planet went out to investigate. The Great Supervisors handling the daily matters, who were usually separated from the external administrative people, also realized the changes.

The headquarter region was where the Great Elders and the hidden powerhouses stayed. This, on the other hand, was an independent managerial department. Other than the occasional request for assistance from the inner sect, they would not usually enter the inner sect.

However, now that the snow mountains melting was causing the rivers to converge, this anomaly had attracted the attention of the administrative people.

Garen had just exited the Frost Hell when the guards at the entrance were investigating the changes outside, so no one realized Garen had already left the Frost Hell.

“Senior Brother! Senior Brother Garen! I didn’t know you left!?” As he reached the front entrance of the cave, one of the guards exclaimed as he noticed Garen walking out.

“Mm… What’s happening outside?” Garen asked, confused.

“I’m not sure, but I think the snow is melting,” one of the guards whispered.

“The snow is melting?” Garen suddenly thought of the souls disappearing from the Frost Hell. It might have been him who triggered this change because the source of the snow mountains’ cold temperature had always been the secret souls in Frost Hell.

Now that the secret souls had fused together and formed a horrifying ice armor, it was the merged inheritance of all the ancestors. It was the condensed essence of Scarlet Snow Sect.

Garen knew that him taking the armor meant that he was accepting the wills and wishes of Scarlet Snow Sect’s past ancestors over thousands of years.

“Is a ceremony going on?” He remembered what Carthage said before he left. The ceremony was the so-called Major Battle to gather all the elites. In the end, they were all defeated by the Pilots, which resulted in heavy casualties among the entire population of Energy Machinists in the City of Nagadako.

The only thing was that the Major Battle would last a long time; it was not something that could be finished quickly.

Returning to reality, Garen started thinking once again. How was he going to answer to the Great Elders about the disappearance of the Frost Hell?

He left the entrance of the Frost Hell, heading straight to the main peak’s courtroom where Renee was once put to trial.

The entirety of the Scarlet Snow Sect had become chillier by the minute. Perhaps it had been chilly before, it was just that Garen was only realizing it now. Not many people were to be seen around on the way there. As the headquarter of Scarlet Snow, there were very few people around.

The extreme cold made it difficult for normal people to enter. Only the ones who practiced Scarlet Snow Technique could survive there in the long run. Not many people left their homes during the weekday anyway, only the trained ones dared to.

However, those trained ones were likely to retire into isolation for several years at times, hence explaining why the area was deserted.

In the desolate sky, Garen glanced down. The rare sight of a few sporadic figures could be seen flashing quickly across the ground. It was evident that plenty of people were moving about using Teleportation Arrays.

Soon, he reached the courtroom. From a distance, Garen could hear what sounded like a subtle roar, as though something was colliding against a heavy object.

As the courtroom became closer and closer, two white silhouettes could be seen crashing against each other between the huge ice sculptures.

A gigantic Ice Fox was hovering in front, constantly playing around with the small white spot on the other side.

“This won’t work, the strength’s not enough!”

“Speed! You’re too slow! Faster! Go faster!” An old man, who was in the middle of the Ice Foxes, yelled.

“Ah ah ah!” On the other side, a white youngster suddenly lashed out a clean palmprint that had a strong chill; it was still increasing in size toward the Ice Foxes.

“Too weak!”

The low rumble sounded among the Ice Foxes once again. A tail whipped out and shattered the clean palmprint.

“You just ruined a perfectly ruined the good old Snowstorm Palm! Yours just looks like a slow and powerless ordinary palm!” The old man’s hoarse voice continued to lecture.

Two young, beautiful girls were standing by the side, watching quietly. It turned out they were Little One and Little Two, the two guards given to Garen by the First Princess. From the worried looks on their faces, it was evident that they were very familiar with the two people on the spot.

Ever since Garen’s surroundings had been conquered by the Two-headed Werewolves, they were not able to receive any commands from Garen ever since. So, they roamed around Scarlet Snow Sect’s headquarter freely. Their lives were peaceful yet boring, and they somehow met people around the area.

With just one glance, Garen recognized the two people who were in battle.

The golden-haired teenager was Senior Sister Rainy’s grandchild of direct bloodline, Hong Guo, one who inherited a Secret Frost Seed.

When he first ventured into the Scarlet Snow Sect’s headquarter along with his buddy, it was said that he was imprisoned. However, to everyone’s surprise, he was now safe and sound.

The one standing against him was a Great Supervisor within the sect. He had the powers of the Inherited Level, the Ice Fox Nasata, and he was one of the Great Supervisors in charge of foreign affairs.

“Hong Guo, huh?” Garen was floating high up in the sky to avoid being noticed by people on the ground. He was just observing how the Ice Fox was instructing Hong Guo how to unleash his powers as well as the Secret Frost Seed’s strength.

He also noticed the mysterious teenager, the one always ranked at the bottom among the Third Hearted, was standing far away, witnessing the battle as well. He thought he had gone unnoticeable, just staring blatantly at Hong Guo with a greedy look on his face.

Garen recalled the incident that involved Hong Guo last time.

If this fellow had followed his original track, he would have been the leader of the lucky Energy Machinist survivors. After the Battle of Ice Age about a hundred years later, all the Upper Energy Machinists would be completely dead. Meanwhile, he would lead the leftover younger Energy Machinists away to start over a new life at a new place.

Since Little One and Little Two were somewhat congenial with him, he should just let them protect him then…

Garen did not move anything other than his lips, silently passing a message along to Little One and Little Two who were below.

The two girls’ faces instantly lit up with shock. They searched around for Garen, but they did not see him at all. As for Garen’s original worry that the Great Supervisors and Great Elderlies would notice the disappearance of Frost Hell, there had been no sign so far. Everything was in peace in the courtroom.

The Great Elderlies were not there, the Great Supervisors seemed to be busy with their own matters, and most of the Three Hearted Disciples of the entire Scarlet Snow Sect were still out, so they had not entered the Frost Hell and realized anything.

Without the Great Elder, Garen was currently the strongest in Scarlet Snow Sect.

Observing the battle below, Garen paused for a bit before leaving quietly.

Along with Carthage’s ruling, the top reclusive powerhouse headquarter of the Scarlet Snow Sect had gradually died down, becoming extremely quiet and lonely.

The moment he returned to his own place, Garen immediately noticed the few Great Supervisors waiting for him outside his Black Wolf Lair’s mansion.

“Senior Brother Garen, we have something urgent that needs a decision! An urgent matter! It’s a pressing matter so we do not dare to make any unauthorized decisions!” One of the Great Supervisors, who was unusually sensitive, sensed Garen approaching and started shouting frantically.

“What about Senior Sisters Alice and Eva, and King Cat?” Garen frowned. If foreign affairs had started coming to him for help regarding emergencies, did that mean that the people in front of him were dead?

“Senior Brother Carthage rearranged all the rankings before he left, so you’re the second one now. You’re ranked number two!” One of the Great Supervisors quickly explained. “You have to make all the big decisions in the sect now!”

Only then did Garen understand the true meaning of what Carthage meant with his parting words.

He landed on the ground swiftly. He had yet landed properly when the Great Supervisors already rushed forward.

“Senior Brother Garen, we have an urgent situation! The Medicine of Creation has finally produced the fifth secret medicine! Should we send people over!?”

“There’s also the military situation. Our Scarlet Snow Business Alliance’s third lane was attacked by pirates and they’re in need of a powerhouse to help out!” Another voice followed.

“I’m here to report about the Sky Capital. Star Cloud and Black Blade have officially initiated a war! The thirteen cities will be destroyed, and the battle fire will soon touch upon Planet Naga!”

The three back-to-back information caused Garen to be taken back by surprise.

“Started war? Star Cloud and Black Blade? The Star Cloud and Black Blade Magnetic Field was one of the strongest organization of Energy Machinists, and now they were at war? This gave Garen an uneasy feeling.

“At the Blue Sky Capital?” He asked in a hushed tone.

“Yes… That’s right! The Blue Sky Capital already has thirteen of its major cities destroyed and completely wiped out. Their death count has reached over ten million already!”

“What about the few Three Hearted Royal Highness?” Garen asked quickly. Since he was the person in charge now, he should just get straight to the point.

“Some are in solitude, some are taking a break on holiday, but all of them basically have no idea what’s happening.”

“Make public the third piece of news you just gave me now. Inform the stationed personnel over at Planet Naga and reach out to families and relatives from other places to bring them back. Nobody is allowed to travel long distances from this moment on.” Garen barked out commands swiftly. Nobody knew the future as well as him, he just did not expect things to disrupt this soon.

“Also, inform everyone, including the Three Hearted Royal Highness, that I am calling together at a meeting at the courtroom! The Great Elder and Senior Brother aren’t here, we have to immediately confirm my authority as the decision maker of Scarlet Snow Sect!”

“Yes!”

The three Great Supervisors responded solemnly and dispersed, immediately going about to deliver the news.

As the three of them left, Garen returned to a state of calmness. He had reached a moment of life and death, this was not the time to hesitate.

He got up once again and ordered his Two-headed Werewolves and Turing to save up resources before he started toward the Second Great Elder’s main peak.

*********************

The white, cold tower stood above the mountains, rings of white halos could be seen surrounding it.

There were no signs of any bodyguards around, a completely different situation compared to the last time Garen dropped by. There were only a few automatic robots patrolling the area.

“Garen here to pay respect to Master,” Garen called out gently as he landed in front of the tower.

There was no response; the tower remained silent as if nobody was around.

“Garen here to pay respect to Master, request to open the defense screen,” Garen repeated himself.

Perhaps it was the loud echoes, someone finally rushed out from inside.

“Great Elder has said that he doesn’t want to see anyone, he’s in recluse now!”

“He doesn’t want to see anyone?” Garen’s eyes were cold as he made his way toward the tower. A terrifying aura of chill was emitting from him, turning into wisps of white smoke spreading everywhere.

“Stand still! How dare you enter the tower without permission!” The person shouted after Garen furiously.

The peak of the tower instantly flickered in fluorescent white.

A translucent screen appeared before Garen’s eyes, blocking his path.

Rip!

The screen was torn apart in Garen’s hands within seconds.

Garen continued on his path. At the speed of a lightning, he appeared before the man and grabbed the man’s head, freezing the man’s entire lower body so that the man’s brain was the only system still functioning.

“Forgive me! Have mercy on me! I’m just a messenger! It’s nothing to do with me!” The man’s reaction was strangely instantaneous. As it turned out, he was just a trash with a Level Three or Four Scarlet Snow Technique.

Simply throwing the person aside, Garen strode into the tower. The normally-filled place was now deserted, with no sight of the daily maintenance crew.

Remaining silent, Garen headed straight for the stairs.

Just as he reached the second floor, his eyes landed on Second Great Elder who was walking slowly toward him in the corridor.

“Are you rebelling, Garen?! Simply tearing the tower’s defense screen, you are just trying to ruin my hard work aren’t you!?” Second Great Elder shouted angrily, glaring cold at Garen with his hands behind his back.

Garen studied the Second Great Elder for a while and then bowed his head after making sure there was nothing wrong.

“As your disciple, I dare not do such a thing.”

“Dare not? You killed your Senior Brother and your Senior Sister; you disrespected your teachers and acted irrationally. Is there

anything else you dare not do?!” Second Great Elder scolded him.

“Seeing as you are well, teacher, I shall excuse myself…” Garen turned to leave, his face calm and steady. He suddenly realized that Second Great Elder’s hands were empty.

“Teacher, why do you not have your pipe with you? That’s your favorite pipe.” Garen narrowed his eyes against Second Great Elder.

Chapter 1082: Mad Increase 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“A pipe?” Something odd flashed past the depths of the Second Elder’s eyes. “My lungs haven’t been feeling all that good recently, so I don’t really want to smoke, that’s why I put it away. Why, do you have a problem with that? Are you trying to dictate whether I smoke or not as well?!”

“Naturally, that is not my intention, Master.” Garen’s narrowed eyes grew sharper.

“If that is not your intention then hurry up and scram!” The Second Elder instantly lost his temper.

“Your lungs aren’t feeling well?” Garen laughed coldly. “I’ve been getting much stronger lately, maybe I can help you check, dear Master. Let me see just what’s wrong with your lungs…”

Before he finally finished speaking, Garen reached out his hand like a claw, grabbing at the Second Elder. With a tearing sound, a void-like vacuum was ripped out of the air, it was a terrifying vacuum left behind by immense speed. Before the air around it could even fill in the void, Garen’s claw had already reached the Second Elder’s chest.

The dazzling white Non-Falling light covered Gardens palm, dying his whole hand jade-white. From afar, it did not even look like a human hand.

The claw was just about to grab the Second Elder’s chest.

“How dare you!!”

A layer of black light abruptly exploded beside Garen, turning into a black whirlpool. Several black bugs the size of fists shot out of the whirlpool, rearing their jaws at Garen’s head.

The Second Elder also looked extremely shocked, the Non-Falling light all around his body exploding mercilessly, but even then he just delayed the progress of Garen’s arm, reaching forward quickly.

“One Time Fist Pressure.”

Garen’s right arm abruptly doubled in strength, and crashed towards the Second Elder’s chest with an even more intense and heavier pressure.

The intense fist pressure from the surroundings instantly caused his black bugs to exploded in mid-air, reduced to several mounds of foul-smelling pus.

An unstoppable, terrifying pressure pressed down on the Second Elder tightly, and right now, he was completely unable to fight back. He could only watch, wide-eyed, as the hand

approached him.

“You dare kill your master!!!?”

He howled madly.

Booom!!!

Garen’s palm disappeared, and the terrifying traits of the Ten Thousand True Technique meant that he could instantly transfer that immense power somewhere else, crashing it into the chest of a person in black who had just appeared.

Thick blood sprayed out from under the black-robed man’s hood, and he screamed, flying backward into the wall. Large cracks spread across the wall, and the layers of Non-Falling power fell off his body like layers of an onion, disappearing and shattering layer by layer.

“I… won’t yield…!!” His body instantly turned into a flash of black light that darted away.

“Cowardly sneak, you dare escape!” Garen harrumphed coldly, and took one step forward.

“Two Times Fist Pressure.”

Boom!!!

A terrifying pressure suppressed the black light, and the black light crashed onto the floor like a mound of lead, sending out a large spray of black shards.

The air began to coagulate slightly, like a thick liquid, and even the wind could not flow.The falling of the black light, the expression on the Second Elder’s face, the shards of the wall, everything seemed to move in slow motion.

Every movement would consume a great cost. This was the terrifying power of Garen’s destructive abilities, the 88-times fist pressure seemed to increase completely according to the

capabilities of the user’s own physical body. As long as the user’s body could withstand it, the number could keep on rising indefinitely.

Right now, Garen’s Strength was at 40 points, and by doubling the power of his Destructive Impact Fist, it could reach 80 points in Strength. Even a powerhouse at the same level as him,

at the peak of the Non-Falling Level, would not be able to fight back against such a terrifying pressure. They would be suppressed like infants. Faced with Garen’s fists, their Non-Falling power was no different from eggshells.

To put eighty Strength points into perspective, back then Garen had dominated the Totem World with less than twenty Strength points. All the giant beasts or terrifying monsters several dozen meters tall could not do anything when faced with his fist. And a giant beast that was several dozen meters tall could destroy a skyscraper in one hit.

And now he had eighty points of Strength, four times what he had back then. If he split up the power and used it separately, he could destroy more than ten skyscrapers in one hit, and could instantly demolish some smaller cities.

This was all just the terrifying power of Garen’s One Time Fist Pressure. Such power was concentrated fully in this space that was less than a hundred acres large.

“Sunshine!”

The black light on the ground made its last desperate struggle, exploding out with a terrifying golden light and heat. This was evidently his Origin secret skill.

“Three Times.” Garen took one step forward, and the terrifying power just grew more intense. Faced with the overwhelming power of 120 Strength points, the black light’s explosion was instantly extinguished like a flame being put out.

After a whoosh, the black light shattered and scattered, and everything returned to normal once more.

Up until that point, this unidentified Non-Falling powerhouse had died powerlessly in the tower, and all that remained of him was the web of cracks across the high-density alloy wall. And this was after Garen controlled his power, making sure not to waste too much.

“You—Y-y-you–!” The Second Elder’s pupils dilated, and as he watched Garen walk toward him slowly, a sweat broke out on his forehead. Even his teeth kept chattering, he could not fight his instincts at all.

“Master, do you have any problem with the way I finished off that suspicious character?” Garen asked calmly.

The Second Elder’s lips shook, all the blood drained out of his face. But he tried hard to maintain his image anyway. “No… no problem… You did well! You did very well!” He kept nodding his head. By now, he had lost all his poise and dignity as a teacher.

As his power increased, the Army-level Garen already had the beginnings of an invisible, formidable aura. Since he had completed his training for the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, it was now rapidly displaying its ultimate power.

Garen could see that his Vitality value had reached the Soul Limit, but some of his physical attributes were still increasing drastically, the most crucial one being his regenerative powers.

The most significant aspect of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique is immortality, or regenerative powers that border on immortality.

Garen was already feeling it.

Before this, when he activated the triple fist pressure, his body would tear internally from the burden, but now, it was a piece of cake. That was just a few days ago… and the speed of his regenerative powers was still increasing rapidly.

Even he did not know to what extent the Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s regenerative powers could reach. At the end of it, even he did not know just how strong the highest level of a Living Secret Technique, the Army Level, could be. And Garen did not know just what heights he could reach when he merged it with the Willpower training of this world, either.

All he knew was that he was getting stronger and stronger, stronger and stronger…

Looking at the Second Elder cowering before him, Garen was now certain that this man was indeed the Scarlet Snow Sect’s Second Elder. But he was only that person in body and in strength, whereas he was no longer that person in spirit…

Perhaps this was the same as what Carthage did to Garen in the past, right now, this person was just a Bodysnatcher they found from somewhere else. Thinking back to the Second Elder’s personality, Garen knew that he would never be this scared by such a small matter.

Sadness flashed through Garen’s heart, but even more of it was killing intent toward Carthage.

The Second Elder and Rainy were all people who had helped him, but now they were being treated like this, and he could do nothing about it.

“The Destructive Impact Fist has reached five times… this is the limit my body can take, if I go any further, I’ll need to increase my speed. When the Major Battle starts, I might not have any time or energy to upgrade myself so relaxedly anymore.

Garen understood in his heart, and gave the Second Elder one last look, before he closed his eyes, turned around, and slowly walked away.

“It’s time I focused on increasing my Nine-Level Tempered Body Technique. I need nine different types of precious mineral essences to temper my body. It will cost an arm and a leg, so I had best use my power in the Scarlet Snow Sect to gather and provide what I need. To face Carthage, I need all the power I can get.” Garen already had a plan lined out.

“Master, I plan to call a Courtroom Meeting, please make your way to the Courtroom, and it’s best if you’re not late,” he said calmly, without even looking around.

“I won’t, I won’t…” By now, the Second Elder had already been scared out of his wits, and could only say yes to everything.

If he was not mistaken, the Second Elder had been Bodysnatched.

Garen did not need to go see the First and Third Elders, they were probably in the same state. Perhaps the entire Scarlet Snow Sect had already changed hands. Carthage’s aims had been achieved. If it were not for Garen, an anomaly, perhaps this Energy Machinist sect would have already been reduced to existing in name only, being used solely as a base to ambush other sects.

As for that hidden black-robed person he killed, Garen was not worried in the slightest. This had always been “Jeros'” character: bloodthirsty, evil, and a lover of destruction above all.

He was just a Non-Falling Level, Carthage would not really mind even if he did know. Theoretically, Jeros was at the same level and position as him, so naturally he would not be controlled by his orders.

Leaving the Second Elder’s tower, Garen went to the First and Third Elders’ places as well, barging in forcefully. Unsurprisingly, it was completely empty inside, with only a few blood stains left. Perhaps they were killed, perhaps Carthage did not think they were worthy of even the lowest-level Bodysnatching, and just killed them off cleanly.

As for the guardian, if the Scarlet Snow guardian still had not shown up at this point, that must not be good news either.

“Carthage…”

Garen floated in mid-air, he could feel the last Will of several dozen ancestors in the armor on his brow, they were furious and roaring out in anger. That was a fury and hatred born from the imminent annihilation of the Scarlet Snow Sect.

Some of them had lived for far too long in the Scarlet Snow Sect, some had been raised and protected by the Scarlet Snow Sect, and treated this place as their home. Yet others had poured too much of their blood, sweat, and tears into the Scarlet Snow Sect.

“Please relax, I will return this favor to Carthage properly…” murmured Garen softly.

He could feel that his powers were constantly growing madly with every passing moment, the mad dash as a result of the overnight explosion from the Army-Level, completed Hellfrost Peacock Technique was still in effect. And the tree branch of the Staff of Absolute Yin that he was getting from the Remora Business Alliance would arrive soon enough, and then he would have another new source for replenishing his potential points.

After this, he wanted his true form to try and break the next level of the Scarlet Snow Technique. Reaching Grade Sixteen Level Eight, or even Level Nine, would not be a problem, because the ancestors’ Armor of Ice had given him the experience to level up completely. He could even reach the very top level of the Scarlet Snow Sect without a problem. All he needed was time. But after Level Nine, he would once more face the same dilemma his forefathers did, and be unable to reach the Tenth Perpetual Motioner.

This was the Demonic Curse, a Demonic Curse that no one in the Scarlet Snow Sect could avoid.

Unless they could reach Level Ten, they would not be able to fight Perpetual Motioners, much less the powerhouse among Perpetual Motioners, Chinande. Perhaps the final key still lay with the secret techniques…

Chapter 1083: Sect Visit 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Maybe it’s time to make a trip back.”

Garen recalled everything that had happened since he arrived in this world, and his deepest impressions still came from his time in the Blackboard Region.

Right now, the Scarlet Snow Sect existed in name only. The Elders were gone, the Guardian was missing, so the only ones left holding the Sect up were the Great Supervisor and the Three Hearted Disciples. But even so, the power of the Sect had not really been reduced, because of Carthage, because of Garen himself. But Carthage had not truly revealed his identity yet, so he was still a part of the Scarlet Snow Sect. As for Garen…

On the surface, he was just a Non-Falling Level Five, but in truth he had the Armor of Ice, and could reach Level Nine. But he had no idea about the Level Nine fighting style, and with just the power of a Level Nine fighter, he could not understand the corresponding knowledge.

Garen flew straight for the Courtroom.

Clang clang clang…

The heavy sound of the clock rang from the peak, spreading across the whole Scarlet Snow Sect headquarters, and many bolts of light quickly shot toward the hall at the peak of the Courtroom. Some of these lights were strong while others were subdued, and they instantly turned into figures of different heights once they entered the Courtroom, each landing quietly on their respective seats.

When Garen flew into the Basilica, most of the people had already gathered there, only a few were absent because they were either away or in seclusion.

Some of the Three Hearted Disciples looked impatient, these summonses had evidently interrupted something. Most of the Great Supervisors were quiet and thoughtful, betraying no emotion and taking no stances.

And then there was the headquarters’ Head Manager, a chubby middle-aged normal person whose gaze swept across the whole area as soon as he landed.

“The Elders aren’t here, Great Senior Brother isn’t here, so who has the right to sound the emergency summons bell?!” he asked gravely.

“It wasn’t the Elders?” One of the Great Supervisors grew confused. He was joined by a few others around him.

Even some of the Three Hearted Disciples began to frown. If it was not the Elders, who could it be? It could not have been the Guardian, the Lord Guardian would never make a direct order, circumventing the Elders. Could it be Great Senior Brother?

Eva stood in the number three position, her lips pursed and her expression cold. She did not really care who rang the bell, but since they had rung the emergency summons bell, that must mean something extremely serious must have happened.

Number Two, Alice, was still hidden in her white robes, her facial expression hidden, and giving off a similarly calm feeling.

Beneath her, Number Four, King Cat, was playing with his little white kitten, and seemed completely unconcerned with the meaning behind the summons.

The fifth position was empty, that used to be Rainy’s. The Sixth, Angola, was dressed in blood-red robes, his face expressionless and his thoughts unsurmisable.

Number seven was Mandi, a strange loner of a guy. Usually, most of the Sect’s Energy Machine Imprints came from him and his disciples, so he was the master of Energy Machine Imprints within the Sect. This old man with the disheveled beard did not look particularly eye-catching, but no one would look down on him.

The eighth was Mies, after he was carelessly knocked out by Hong Guo and the others last time, he was currently staring at Hong Guo and co as they stood behind the Great Supervisors, his expression cold and dark. Evidently, he still had a grudge over what happened last time.

Ninth and Tenth were Demonic Spirit Solomon and Aloran. The two of them were discussing something in whispers, and Aloran’s expression did not look particularly good.

And then there was Eleven, a member of the Ballfish race. This giant and round creature was basically a Ballfish, floating above the eleventh position. Everyone had forgotten its name, and they just called it Eleven. There were two small and short fins on the surface of its black body, and they fanned around occasionally, creating a stark contrast with its roly-poly body. It actually ended up looking rather cute.

Twelve was empty, that was originally Garen’s position, and Thirteen was Lonray, a newbie who had just risen here together with Garen. This person had luckily managed to survive the Void Battlefields, and seeing Garen descend from the sky now, he immediately sent word via voice transmission, enquiring about the situation.

Garen chatted with him idly, waiting for everyone to arrive.

But his gaze swept past all the Three Hearted Disciples and the Great Supervisors.

The last Fourteen was White Night, this guy had just returned recently, covered with wounds. Even now, there were still bandages on his arms. Clearly, his journey to unearth the treasures of his family did not go very smoothly, and he had no leads on his younger brother either. Right now his expression was cloudy, and he looked to be in a very bad mood.

Fifteen, on the other hand, was that mysterious young man. After reaching Three Hearted, he had changed his name, and gave himself the title Prism Light. Right now he was dressed fully in white and looked average, completely outshone by the handsome and ice-cold White Night beside him. He was wholly inconspicuous.

Garen’s gaze turned, and he looked at the Great Supervisors.

There were not many Great Supervisors who had the right to participate in the Courtroom, only five in total. The middle-aged one who taught Hong Guo, the Ice Fox, also stood among them, whereas the other four were two men and two women respectively. They came in different shapes and sizes, but looked like very normal academics, such as teachers or professors. If it were not for the occasional flicker of Inherited Power around them that resisted against the chill of the Courtroom, no one would have guessed that these very average-looking academics were actually Inherited-Level powerhouses.

Three of them were the Great Supervisors who had come to report to Garen back then, and right now all of their gazes considered Garen slightly, indicating respect.

The three Elders seats at the very top remained conspicuously empty.

Whoosh!

There was a distortion of white light, and the Second Elder instantly appeared on the Second Elder’s seat.

As soon as he appeared, he instinctively looked at Garen, who was standing at the Three Hearted position. The Three Hearted position did not indicate their rank, because the ranks of the Three Hearted Disciples had changed recently, and there had not been enough time to readjust them.

Rainy had died, and her seat was emptied, so naturally the rest would take one seat forward.

So even though Garen stood at that position, his rank was not just number twelve.

“The other two Elders can’t make it.” The Second Elder calmed himself down. “Now, I want to tell you some devastating news.”

The Basilica fell silent as soon as the Second Elder spoke, and everyone’s eyes gathered on the Elders’ seats.

“Due to an accident, the First and Third Elders have perished in the line of duty…” said the Second Elder in a grave and sorrowful voice.

The voice echoed around the Basilica, and everyone who heard that news doubted their ears. Some people blinked, and instinctively turned around to ask the people next to them, wondering if what they had just heard was simply a figment of their imagination.

Some people frowned deeply, completely disbelieving.

Eva lowered her head, and no one could see her expression, but they could tell from her tightly-clenched fists that she was in deep shock.

She knew better than anyone else what state the Scarlet Snow Sect was in, Carthage and Garen have been acting all mysterious, as though they barely belong to the Scarlet Snow Sect at all. Recently, she had been secretly investigating the two of them, and the information that she gathered shocked her tremendously, so she grew more and more suspicious of the two. Especially with regard to their powers, their rate of progress had reached terrifying levels, needing only several decades to accomplish what others took hundreds or thousands of years to reach. For two such impossible prodigies to appear in the tiny Scarlet Snow Sect at the same time was a total anomaly…

And during such turbulent times, the two Elders had suddenly perished…

The entire Scarlet Snow Sect had reached a point of life and death!

“I don’t believe it!”

The Silver Fox Great Supervisor stood out and barked loudly, looking slightly panicked and dismayed.

“Father just talked to me a week ago! How could he have died!!??” He was referring to the First Elder, since he was the First Elder’s son in the direct line.

And beside him, another female Great Supervisor also looked disbelieving, as she too stood out and spoke.

“That’s right, my grandfather just sent me a message three days ago, asking me to get him the newest Blue Eagle Stone! Ever since he entered Non-Falling Level, for several hundred years, he had never left the headquarters, who could just sneak into the headquarters and kill two Non-Falling Levels like that!? Second Elder, you…” Her grandfather was the Third Elder. After all, as Great Supervisors who could enter the Courtroom, the two of them had to have relied on their connections to the two Elders, otherwise it would not be plausible for them to get in.

“Silence!” The Second Elder’s authoritative voice interrupted her, and his Non-Falling aura instantly pressed down on them, suppressing them mercilessly.

“You dare doubt my words?!” The Second Elder stared at them coldly. “Guards!”

Two white-armored guards appeared abruptly behind the two Great Supervisors.

“Take them away, throw them in the dungeon, and have them executed tomorrow!”

Executed?!

Just then, not only did the two of them doubt their ears, everyone present there wondered if they had heard that right.

Execution just for doubting what the Elder said? Executing two Inherited-Level powerhouses that had always done their job for the Scarlet Snow Sect properly?!

Has the Second Elder gone crazy?!

Or could it be, that the deaths of the two Elders were closely related to the Second Elder…?

For an instant, Eva, Alice and the other high-ranking Three Hearted Disciples thought of this possibility, and felt that the situation was getting stranger and stranger. No one knew if the two Elders were dead or alive; after all, they were two long-established Non-Falling Level powerhouses, and it was not like people would believe that they had died just because the Second Elder said a few things. Without proper proof and evidence, no one would truly believe that they had died.

“Is he trying to cover up his own actions?” The possibility occurred to some people.

The two of them were instantly apprehended by Non-Falling Light, all their powers completely disabled. They were restrained by the two white-armored guards, and were about to be dragged away.

The Basilica was completely quiet, no one dared to forcefully voice out. The Second Elder right now was very strange, and instead of being calm and low-key as he used to be, he was acting rather impulsive now.

“Wait!”

Suddenly a voice rang out in the hall, gentle and clear.

It was Alice!

She was ranked number two, the leader of Moonshine, and right now, she finally spoke.

“What do you have to say?” The Second Elder glared at Alice coldly. Although all of the Three Hearted Disciples had hidden their abilities to some extent, this woman was the most mysterious of the lot. Back then, when Rainy had been rescued, she could actually manage to hold the Non-Falling-Level Carthage back without getting injured. That was practically unimaginable.

“Executing some Inherited-Level powerhouses just for talking back and suspecting you a little, don’t you find that a terrible waste, Second Elder?” said Alice calmly.

Garen watched this scene with interest, at first he had planned to step out, but Alice had actually gotten one step ahead of him.

Even without the two Elders and the Guardian, even putting aside Garen himself for now, the power of the Scarlet Snow Sect was not all that weak.

Chapter 1084: Sect Visit 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Alice was mysterious, but it was highly likely that she had Non-Falling Level power. Out of the Three-Hearted Disciples, there were already eight Inherited Levels, aside from the late Rainy, Carthage, White Night, and the mysterious young man Prismatic Light.

And of the Great Supervisors, the four of them present here were already the strongest four. Other than them, there were thirty-five other Inherited Levels who were scattered across the planets, either living in seclusion or managing the sect’s various operations, returning only once every fifty years to hand in their report. This was also a huge asset for them. Apparently, some of these Great Supervisors had even started their own branch sects, and some of their disciples were Inherited Levels too, adding up to an astronomical number.

A rough estimate calculated that the entire Scarlet Snow Sect would have at least more than sixty Inherited Level powerhouses and two Non-Falling Levels. This would have been unimaginable to his Black Flood Party from back then, this was equivalent to all the power in the Blackboard Region. In fact, it was even stronger! Once you put it that way, it could be said that an Inherited-Level Energy Machinist could fight with at least two Inherited-Level pilots of the same level.

“…” The Second Elder exchanged glares with Alice for a while, but his bark was worse than his bite, and the situation slowly calmed down.

“Since Alice is the one pleading for them… I guess I’ll spare them for now.”

The two white-armored guards finally released the two of them, and by then, the duo was already dripping with sweat. They had practically put one foot in the coffin, so they were still not over the shock, their hearts beating wildly.

“Alright, alright.” Only then did Garen step out, and speak with a smile. “Every Inherited Level is a precious asset to our Scarlet Snow Sect, how could Master execute such elites so casually? Wouldn’t that hurt the hearts of the Great Supervisors stationed outside?”

“Stop pretending!” said Eva coldly. She could already tell that there was something wrong with the Second Elder, and it was not just her, every Energy Machinist here was an elite. After living for so long, they could deduce a lot of things from just the tiniest clues.

But to Eva’s surprise, the Second Elder changed from his previous impulsiveness, and actually nodded very gently now, as though fully approving of Garen’s words.

“Garen’s right, I was being too rash just now.”

“Alright, time to get to the main point.” The Second Elder grew solemn. “The main reason I called this Courtroom Meeting was to hand over the rights to the Sect. From now on, all the Elders’ rights, as well as the rights to manage and mobilize the Sect, will be handed over to the Three Hearted Disciple Garen!”

These words were like another bombshell that instantly exploded within the Courtroom, shocking everyone’s minds into a blank.

“Put Garen in charge of all matters!? Master, are you joking!?” Eva finally lost it, yelling loudly. Her almond eyes widened, as though she had never thought that her master would give such an order.

Surely! Surely he had been controlled by Garen! Even back then, Garen was already so terrifyingly powerful, now he must surely be working with Carthage. He must have taken Master off-guard, and then controlled him with some unknown method, that must surely be it!!

When she thought of that, the hatred rose straight to her head, and her glare at Garen was almost burning in its intensity.

“Why would you put Garen in charge!” yelled Aloran too, as he stepped out. “He’s ranked further than number ten! Even if you want to put some in charge of the whole Sect, that person should be Senior Sister Alice, right!?”

“Although Junior Brother Garen is talented, I believe he has yet to reach the level where he can be in charge of everything, no?” Alice spoke too.

A cold air blew through the Basilica. It was not just the Three Hearted Disciples, but Great Supervisor Ice Fox, Hong Guo, and the others all began to murmur softly. There were also other onlookers, the higher-ups brought by each of the Three Hearted Disciples. Even though they did not have the right to speak and join the meeting, and could only watch from the sidelines, they still began to whisper among each other in spite of themselves.

In that instant, the Basilica became a mess, the rowdy buzz of conversation lingering around everyone’s ears like a swarm of bees.

“Are you… doubting me?” The Second Elder’s expression darkened, and instantly, the Non-Falling Light spread everywhere again. It suppressed the auras of everyone present.

“Second Elder, are you trying to get your way by brute force!?” Alice took one step forward, emanating ice-blue Non-Falling Light from her body, with a whoosh, shot into the sky in the form of a blue pillar of light.

It directly split the Basilica into two, one side white and the other blue.

To everyone’s surprise, even though he was the strongest among the Elders, the Second Elder was losing ground. His Non-Falling Light no longer had that strange ability to gather into a snowstorm, and it instantly disintegrated the moment it made contact with Alice’s Non-Falling Light.

The two powerful Non-Falling Lights suppressed everything else, those who had not reached Non-Falling Level yet could not do anything but watch. The Non-Falling Light was significantly stronger than the Inherited-Level force field, and someone who was not at the same level could not hope to join the conflict.

“Second Senior Sister, are you trying to disobey your master?” Garen took one step forward as well.

“You have no right to speak here!” said a voice suddenly.

Psst!

A white ice crystal abruptly shot at Garen’s head, but he shattered it with a flick of his finger. The ice crystal shattered in mid-air, reduced to countless twinkles of white light.

“Is that so?” Garen smiled slightly.

Boom!!

A most terrifying Non-Falling Light exploded from his body, surging madly in all directions.

Eva, who had shot out that ice crystal, turned pale. She took more than ten steps backward in a hurry, until her back was pressed against a huge ice sculpture, as she gasped for breath. There were despair and disbelief in her eyes.

“How’s that… possible!? Non-Falling Level!!?”

King Cat and the others looked shocked as well, he was just at the peak of the Inherited Level, and now he was at the Non-Falling Level!? Even Carthage had not been this fast back then, right!?

“M-Monster!” Aloran’s eyes were full of fear as he stared at Garen, this had gone beyond merely being a prodigy.

The three powerful lights fought and resisted each other in the Basilica, but it was not a three-way battle. Instead, it was just Garen single-handedly suppressing the Second Elder’s and Alice’s Non-Falling Lights.

“Before he left, the Senior Brother left everything to me. I have received Master’s trust and support, and since the two fates of the Elders are currently unknown, who is more suited to bear this responsibility than me?” Garen smiled as he looked at the Three Hearted Disciples, who were too heavily suppressed to say a word, and then at the managers and higher-ups around them.

The cold wind howled, making his robes billow in the wind. His gentle yet ice-cold smile sent a chill down Eva’s and Aloran’s spines, and even the Second Elder looked faintly fearful.

Boom!

A huge power landed on Alice abruptly.

Alice’s body was instantly sent flying, and she was embedded into the ice statue behind her with a bam, sending down a storm of crushed ice and snow.

The air had solidified, the huge and terrifying fist pressure instantly pressing down on the surface of Alice’s body as though it were truly air pressure, rendering her unable to break free.

“You…” She opened her mouth with difficulty, but an even stronger pressure attacked her suddenly, forcing her words into her throat. If it were not for the fact that just recently reached this stage… A hint of furious shame flashed past her eyes.

“Anyone else has any opinions?” Garen looked around him.

The Basilica was completely quiet, no one dared to say anything.

Even Second Senior Sister, who was a Non-Falling Level, was being suppressed, so who dared to say anything else?

“Very good.” The Second Elder retracted his Non-Falling Light, and smiled in satisfaction. “Looks like everyone’s perfectly fine with my suggestion. In that case, from now on, Garen is our Scarlet Snow Sect’s Highest Supervisor, after this I will propose to the Lord Guardian that we make him our Sect Master as well!”

Sect Master!!

The Three Hearted Disciples below all had strange expressions, Sect Master? How many years had it been since someone held that position? A Sect Master had to be agreed on by all the Elders and the Guardian before they could accept the Frost Hell’s Willpower test.

“No need for that.” Garen smiled slightly. “You don’t need to propose anything to the Guardian any longer…”

As everyone watched in confusion, he walked up straight to the highest point in the Basilica.

With every step he took, a white chill spread from his body, turning into white light that surrounded him.

The white light grew in volume, as did the white air.

Phew…

Garen raised his arms, and a pair of sharp jade-white arm armors appeared on his arms. Pure unadulterated chill emanated from the armor.

“That’s…!!” The Second Elder’s pupils diluted abruptly.

Step by step, Garen slowly stepped up into the air, as though there were invisible stairs beneath his feet, holding him up as he walked toward the air above the highest point in the Basilica.

With every step, another piece of clear ice armor appeared on his body.

When he reached the very top, and stood level with the statue, he was already wearing a full suit of luxurious white armor made of ice, with a sharp horn poking out of its scabbard.

Psst…

A giant helmet that was as fearsome as a crescent moon appeared out of nowhere above Garen’s head, covering his entire face.

Countless chills gathered in the air to form a Throne of Ice that floated in mid-air.

Garen turned around, and slowly sat on that empty chair.

Bzz…

The Basilica began to tremble slowly, and all the ice statues, several dozen meters tall, began to shake.

Garen, wearing his Armor of Ice, had already transcended what a normal Energy Machinist could understand, his power spreading through the whole area. To everyone here, Level Nine and Level Seven were both beyond their reach, they were both untouchable, overwhelmingly strong, and hence they were practically the same.

Baroom!!

The originally clear skies rumbled with thunder, and countless black clouds appeared out of nowhere, spinning and roiling in the sky right above Garen.

Garen looked down at everything beneath him, the Three Hearted Disciples were flushed red under the pressure of his power. Eva, Aloran and the rest were still holding on, but King Cat, Demon Spirit and the rest had already succumbed without resisting, just looking at Garen with unprecedented respect in their eyes.

The Second Elder had already stood up, his expression respectful. Clearly, he had thrown all pretenses to the wind. When faced with ultimate power, everything else was arbitrary.

As for the remaining Great Supervisors and those who were here as witnesses, they could not even raise their heads to look at him. The difference in power was far too large, if they saw just a little bit of his white light now, they would feel a piercing and irresistible cold, and they might even be instantly frozen.

“From today onward,” Garen’s voice spread throughout the entire Scarlet Snow headquarters, “I, Garen, will officially be the Scarlet Snow Sect’s sixty-ninth Sect Master.”

Nobody dared to say anything, and no one could say anything. The chill emanating from Garen had instantly sealed everyone’s mouths.

“While the Sect is on the brink of danger, I, Garen, will continue the battle, and bring more glory to the Sect than has been seen in the last thousand years!”

And thus, I will prove that the highest realm of my Living Secret Technique will not lose to mechs!!

Garen secretly added in his heart.

“All disciples, this is an order!” The Second Elder immediately understood, and ordered loudly. “Bow!!”

He actually took the lead, bowing first.

The followers under his faction immediately bowed as well, showing their allegiance. Most of the people who had been shocked by Garen’s power also bowed, to them, as long as it was someone in the Sect who was strong enough, anyone could be Sect Master.

Only Alice, Eva, and Aloran clenched their teeth and continued to hold on. However, they could no longer affect the bigger picture, everything was settled now. The Second Elder was in the lead, the other two Elders were missing, the Guardian was nowhere to be seen, so nobody in the Sect could fight against Garen.

This is the reality, the stark truth!!

Chapter 1085: Officially in Power 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Congratulations to the Sect Master, infinite glory over a thousand years!!” yelled the Second Elder very cooperatively. He spread his arms open wide, the Non-Falling Light emanating from him dazzlingly, shooting into the sky and turning into a pillar of light, as flawless as white jade.

Psst…!

The pillar of light shot up from the Courtyard and shot straight into the clouds, but it was completely engulfed by the black clouds all over the sky, and did not make so much as a ripple in them.

“Congratulations to the Sect Master, infinite glory over a thousand years!!”

“…Congratulations to the Sect Master, infinite glory over a thousand years!!”

“…infinite glory over a thousand years!!”

The echoes of the voices stacked over each other, and grew larger and larger in volume, like waves from a distance.

Garen sat in his Throne of Ice, the thick and grotesque Armor of Ice on his body covering his entire figure, such that his face underneath could not be seen at all.

Although he did not have long to prepare, the Second Elder did very well with the preparations. After Carthage left, the people in his faction all automatically came to Garen instead, so most people in the Scarlet Snow Sect considered him Carthage’s successor. This was originally Jeros’ privilege.

“It’s too bad… you miscalculated…” When Garen saw this scene, he knew that Carthage could no longer return, so he would surely change his identity. Garen had more or less gained control of the Scarlet Snow Sect, so he might infiltrate another sect instead, or perhaps he might continue managing his plan in secret.

“Jeros, is there anything you need help with?” Suddenly, a sharp voice reached Garen’s ears. That voice was very distinct, and anyone who had heard it once would not forget it.

It was Red Robes!

Garen instantly remembered whose voice it was.

“This is already my territory, if you don’t have anything to do with me, go find Carthage yourself,” Garen replied mildly through voice transmission. He noticed that a few of the Three Hearted Disciples already had a mind to leave, their gazes twinkling uncertainly, and they were obviously communicating in secret. But he did not stop them, it was good if they left too. Right now, the Scarlet Snow Sect needed a large-scale clean-up operation, from the top to the bottom, so that he could grasp all the power before the danger arrived.

Since he had already inherited his ancestors’ Will of Ice, he should naturally fulfill his promise, and do everything he can to bring glory to the Scarlet Snow Sect, in order to meet his elders’ expectations.

It did not matter in the bigger picture whether these disloyal Three Hearted Disciples left or not, they were of no great importance. In fact, it would help to gather up the sect’s power, so that they could advance to the next step.

“Hehe, looks like your control isn’t stable enough yet…” Red Robes began to laugh piercingly.

“Don’t forget Master Carthage’s plan. You must move on cue during the Major Battle, since the Scarlet Snow Sect is one of the three central figures, you and I both understand what will happen if you don’t complete the mission.” Red Robes actually started transmitting his voice to Garen boldly, even though everyone was right there and watching.

“Do I need you to tell me what to do?!” Garen’s palm gripped the armrest it was resting on lightly.

Bam!

A large hail of white snow and ice exploded from a certain spot in mid-air, and countless clear white shards scattered everywhere, accompanied by the screams from a red figure. The red figure was instantly torn to pieces, turning into several shards of red cloth that floated down, and moved no more.

“Here, I have 64 glasses of Scarlet Snow Wine, it’s a reward specifically for the elite powerhouses of the Scarlet Snow Sect. It can boost the body’s qualities significantly.” Garen gave a sweep of his hand.

64 ice-crystal wine glasses suddenly appeared, floating before him, filled with what looked like a fragrant emerald liquid that emitted an intense aroma of wine.

The 64 ice-crystal glasses of wines just stayed floating there underneath the Throne of Ice, and with a whoosh, the glasses suddenly shot downward, some portions naturally landing in front of everyone present, floating in mid-air.

“In order to celebrate my official ascension to the throne today, this is the Secret Scarlet Snow Wine that I have obtained from the Frost Hell. I will now share it with all of you, and I hope that we will be united as one, for the glory of the Scarlet Snow.” Garen’s icy-cold and deep voice had a hint of authority, and it spread like a tremor from underneath the Armor of Ice, spreading throughout the entire Basilica.

“This…” King Cat frowned, his instincts were telling him that this wine would not harm him, and instead the chill emanating from it was extremely tempting, as though that was the tastiest delicacy in the world. But his logic was telling him that Garen would never be so generous, if he was trying to hand it this wine with strengthening effects to everyone equally, he must surely have a motive behind it.

He glanced at Alice, she was the leader of Moonshine, so not only did she have influence and power with the Scarlet Snow Sect, she also had her own financial group and power in the mortal world. She could survive independently even if she did leave the Scarlet Snow Sect, and her gaze clearly said she wanted to leave, but right now she was being suppressed by that huge aura, and could not get away from it at all. She had just escaped from the ice statue, but now the danger was this choice that might lead to poisoned wine.

“Garen would never let a Non-Falling Level like Alice leave, this meeting is no conference at all, he’s just using this chance to take over, and control all the higher-ups at once…” King Cat lamented inwardly, glancing at Aloran and Eva, and seeing that they were looking at him too. He thought back to the mission he had gone on with Garen recently, as well as that terrifying, bottomless potential. Helplessly, he reached out his hand and took the glass. Instantly, a sharp cold came through the glass and pieced through his body. He could not help but shiver.

Psst!

In one gulp, King Cat finished all the wine without any hesitation. He did not even taste the wine, and just drank it all in one go.

At about the same time, the Demon Spirit Solomon also drank it with a nonchalant smile. She never really had a fixed stance, she just went where the best benefits were. She did not have any fixed likes or dislikes, her personality was strange, and she did not really matter who was in charge, as long as they were strong enough.

After two of the Three Hearted Disciples drank it, the Ballfish’s huge body frowned unhappily, glancing at Alice, and then looking at Garen’s thick, ferocious-looking Armor of Ice. He knew that he would not be able to leave this place without drinking it.

“I’m sorry, Alice,” he said inwardly, and he had no choice but to finish all the wine in one gulp.

Everyone present actually understood that they would not be able to leave the Basilica without drinking the wine. Garen’s rampaging, terrifying chill above them was the proof, the chill had turned to a solid white smoke, and had completely surrounded the entire Basilica, making the peak of the mountain look like a divine realm.

Once the few Three Hearted Disciples led the way and drank it first, the remaining few could only follow suit reluctantly. Only Alice, Eva, and Aloran remained steadfast.

“It tastes good! As expected of the wine to come out of the Frost Hell! New Sect Master! Do you have any more, how about seconds?!” Of the Three Hearted Disciples, the Energy Machine Imprint master, Mandi, was all flushed and drunk, yelling at Garen without pretense.

This guy was rather blunt in nature, although he was often isolated, that was mostly because he did not mix around enough. It was not as though he did not understand the way the world worked, he just happened to only trust his own instincts, and his instincts were telling him that this new Sect Master, Garen, had no ill intentions. That was why he decided to just not think about it, and he never did care two hoots about the battle for Moonshine and Star Plate.

Now that the Second Elder, who was the support pillar behind Star Plate, had completely thrown his lot in with Garen, that meant that Garen had gotten the support of most of the Sect. Moonshine’s Alice could not support much on her own, the situation had practically already been decided, and there clearly was not much of a fight. That was why he decided to take the initiative and offer his allegiance.

“I have wine, but only that glass can increase your powers, the rest can’t.” Garen laughed exasperatedly, and raised his hand lightly, sending another glass of wine sliding up to Mandi, who made sure to taste it carefully. Standing there alone, he stood at the Three Hearted Position, and watched with a smile as Alice and the rest continued to hold on, trying not to surrender in the face of that terrifying pressure.

Nothing happened to those who drank the wine, and this confused Alice and the others slightly. Perhaps this wine really was harmless, and Garen was just using it to confuse them?

The situation here now was that Garen had the whole area suppressed, and you could not leave unless you drank that wine. Be it Alice or Eva, none of them could see where Garen’s limits were anymore. Such rapid growth could no longer be explained by saying he was a prodigy. There must be a huge secret behind this.

Alice gritted her teeth, and glanced at Eva.

“If we drink it, will you let us leave?” she asked icily, looking at Garen.

Surprisingly, Garen actually raised his hand lightly.

“You can choose to not drink, just make sure you don’t regret it later.” He actually acted as though he did not care whether they drank it or not.

“It’s up to you too if you want to leave. Of course, you are still considered a member of the Scarlet Snow Sect even if you’re away. Everything you have was given to you by the Scarlet Snow Sect, even if you don’t admit it, unless you throw away all your powers, your roots are still in the Scarlet Snow Sect in the eyes of others. This will never change,” said Garen calmly.

Just then, there was the continuous sound of people drinking, and this meant everyone, including Hong Guo. Nothing strange at all happened. On the other hand, this allowed Alice, Eva, and Aloran to relax ever so slightly.

“Fine, I’ll drink it!” Aloran grabbed a wine glass decisively, tossed her head back, and drained it.

Smack!

She smashed the glass onto the ground, turned around, and left. She flew straight out of the Basilica, turning into a bolt of light and flying off.

From the beginning to the end, Garen just watched coldly from the side, without any intention of stopping her.

When they saw that, Eva and Alice also took their glasses decisively, draining it on one go, and they rose into the sky at the same time, leaving the Basilica.

After the three of them left, there were only nine out of the original fifteen Three Hearted Disciples left.

The few strongest ones had all left, and now the strongest one was King Cat. He sighed, looking around, and felt as though it was instantly a lot quieter now.

“Second Elder, you can start to organize all the Inherited Levels in the sect now, and order all those Inherited Level and above to gather at the headquarters, Planet Scarlet Snow,within aa week. Those who disobey will be punished as traitors!”

Garen ordered calmly.

The armor on his body grew thicker and thicker, as though it was getting thicker, bigger, and bulkier as time went by. It had almost merged together with the Throne of Ice.

This was activation proof that he was constantly sensing the higher realm and fundamental qualities of the Scarlet Snow Technique in the armor. He needed to understand how the ancestors could reach the ninth level without understanding the Board. Normally, anyone Level Eight and above would need to understand the Board, but the ancestors had somehow directly crossed this hurdle. This was an extremely precious bit of experience, even if he had all sorts of trump cards and immense confidence that he could make it past this challenge, he would still like to save some time wherever he could.

Chapter 1086: Officially in Power 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Once the Second Elder received his orders and started handing out orders, the powerhouses beneath him who had drunk the wine finally gave up for good. Even those who had not given up, those who refused to accept this, had to pretend to obey the orders. Otherwise, they might be punished to set an example for the others.

The Energy Machinists had lived for so many years, so none of them were fools. They all saw clearly that Alice, Eva, and Aloran might have been spared because Garen still cared for their old bonds, but the remaining people might not be so lucky.

Some of the more experienced Energy Machinists had already realized that Garen’s aura now might have already surpassed Non-Falling Level, and they quietly spread the news of this possibility, so that the atmosphere in the Basilica grew even more fearfully respectful.

Right now, Garen was sitting on the Throne of Ice, and he was also considering how to manage the entire Scarlet Snow Sect. Other than for Alice and the other two, he had added the Distorted Seed into every other portion of wine.

By now, his Distorted Seed was even more terrifying than ever, it could increase the parasite’s physical fitness by six times, but since there was a limit to the human body’s physical fitness, so this increase would manifest in a different form, and that was the Armor of Ice.

When the extra power was activated, it would automatically envelop the parasite, forming an extremely powerful suit of Armor of Ice, and increase the parasite’s physical fitness by the maximum of six times that way.

This was very similar to Garen’s current situation.

But even then, the increase was already exceedingly frightening. Once Garen activated it, everyone’s physical fitness would be increased by six times, reaching an extreme degree.

After all, every one of the Inherited-Level Energy Machinists here had already reached the limit of their physical fitness, they were all at twenty points. If they all had that increased by six times… that would equal to 120 points, that was strong enough to force their way into the Non-Falling Level!

“If the effect really is as good as I imagine it would be, then I would instantly have many Non-Falling-Level assets.” Garen closed his eyes to rest, and it looked like he was quietly waiting for the orders to take effect, waiting for all the Inherited-Level powerhouses to meet, when in fact he was considering all the possibilities.

He needed to take complete control of the whole Scarlet Snow Sect right now in one go, and catch all of Carthage’s spies all at one go, turning them all into his assets through the Distorted Seeds. This was the only thing he could think of.

The time passed by. To Energy Machinists, even a few months barely counted as anything, it was equivalent to what normal people considered a few days. Nobody was impatient, and even if they were, they would not dare to show it.

A day passed.

Some of the Energy Machinists had completely white hair, and brought their disciples back to the headquarters. They were quickly led to the Basilica, and gifted the Distorted Seed wine, then they were sent to an area near the Basilica to rest.

The Great Supervisors and powerhouses who had retired into secrecy all streamed back to the headquarters, and to Garen’s delighted surprise, two of the old men had been hiding their powers, and had actually already reached Non-Falling Level.

These two were the brothers Ice-Crack and Ice-Grand who had retired to the South Pole base, they were old-time powerhouses from the same generation as the Second Elder. Back then, they had lost in the battle for the Elder positions, and had retired in their despair. No one had thought that they would unexpectedly reach Non-Falling Level.

Although Garen did not know how they did it, regardless of the result, he just happened to be in dire need of powerful helpers right now, so Garen did not care all that much about the process. He offered them the Distorted Seed wine, and he only had to release his Level-Eight aura to get those two old geezers, as well as their four disciples’ disciples, to obediently drink the wine.

The Scarlet Snow Sect’s secret power was extremely considerable, and contrary to Garen’s expectations, on the fifth day, even more powerhouses appeared, one after the other, from the outer planets. Many of these were capable powerhouses who had been exiled to the other planets, and one of them was even one generation older than the Second Elder. This person was truly a long-lived elder, currently aged 5602, and was also at the Non-Falling Level, but this one was at the peak, making him(1) overwhelmingly powerful.

This person came with all his disciples and grand-disciples, carrying a fearsome momentum. He clearly planned to usurp Garen’s position, and had even brought some of his friends from other sects to buff up his forces.

Unfortunately, he met Garen. Garen just had to release his Level-Eight aura, and the whole group deflated like balloons, each of the Inherited-Level and above powerhouses obediently accepting the Distorted Seed wine, and all turning into parasites.

This parasitism would not take effect immediately, but it would slowly and subconsciously affect the parasite’s Will and Soul, gradually turning them into the Hellfrost Peacock’s larvae. They would then be unable to resist their inherent fear and respect for the original mother queen. Although they would not obey the queen unconditionally, they must still never have the slightest intention of disobeying the queen, and whether they were alive or dead, they would eventually merge into the queen. At the same time, their affinity for ice would increase tremendously, and naturally they would also possess the talent for the Cold Chaos ability, that was the true power of the Hellfrost Peacock. When an army of countless soldiers brought out their Cold Chaos ability and spread it everywhere, devouring everything, unless they were stopped, the whole world would truly fall apart at the seams.

This blindly ambitious old man was forced down by Garen, and even the thirty-odd Inherited-Level powerhouses he had brought with him became the Distorted Seed’s parasites. These included not just the older members of the Scarlet Snow Sect, but even the powerhouses from other sects, and in turn, this greatly benefited Garen’s succession to the throne.

After half a month, the main situation had settled. Every member of the Scarlet Snow Sect was under the control of the Distorted Seed, and all the powerhouses, Inherited-Level and above, were completely unaware of the parasites. Instead, they felt the wine slowly strengthening their regenerative powers, and at the same time, a layer of ice armor gradually appeared on their bodies, one that they could extend and retract at will. When they donned the armor, their fitness would also be greatly increased.

Garen had always been sitting in the middle of the Basilica, high above the ground. A thick white pillar had naturally appeared beneath the Throne of Ice, connecting it to the Basilica underneath.

The armor over Garen’s entire body had completely fused with the Throne of Ice, fixing him onto the seat. He had also sent the others away, so he was the only one left in the entire Basilica.

An extremely terrifying chill was circling around the Basilica, turning this place into a true Frost Hell. As soon as any living thing entered this place, even their Wills and souls would be instantly frozen, and they would completely be paralyzed as Garen’s Faded Creation skill slowly devoured them.

Unless they were powerhouses at Inherited Level or above who had become parasites of his Distorted Seed.

Ever since Garen succeeded the throne, the sky in the Basilica had been covered by a whirlpool of black clouds with the occasional rumble of thunder, the pressure low and cold. The whole Basilica glowed with an eerie cold blue light, and the ice-blue cold flames flickered sometimes, burning slowly on the torches.

Garen sat on the Throne of Ice, his eyes glowing with an eerie cold blue light, the patterns on his armor growing more and more intricate, marks like sword scratches appearing on the surface of his armor. Some sharp Wong-like thorns of ice had already started appearing on his back. These thorns were blue-black and extremely sharp, stacking on top of each other without any rhyme or reason. Seen from a distance, they looked like a random pile of bird wings, without any order or symmetry to speak of.

But they vaguely gave of a sense of holy, majestic sharpness.

The many wing thorns were wide and long, and had nearly become the most eye-catching symbol in the whole courtroom. Compared to Garen and his throne, which were only several meters tall, the blue-black wings on his back, more than a dozen meters tall, were even more iconic and memorable.

From a distance, all that could be seen was the infinite chill emanating from the piled-up wings, such that anyone who even glanced at it, even from several kilometers away, would feel all cold all around their bodies.

It had already been half a month since Garen gathered all the powerhouses. The sky was calm without even a hint of clouds, because all the clouds had gathered above the Courtroom, forming a black whirlpool there that seemed as though it would never cease. And everywhere else was as sunny as could be, without the slightest bit of chill, as though the entire headquarters had instantly gone from winter to summer.

Psst!

All of a sudden, from a building within headquarters, a pillar of pale blue light shot into the sky. It shot straight for a dazzling star in the sky, and the pale blue glow it emanated almost outshone even the golden light of the sun.

“I’ve broken through! I’ve broken through! Hahaha!! Hahahaha–!!” A man’s deafening, almost mad laughter rang out, and echoed infinitely across a large area of the headquarters.

In a small alley between the palace’s many buildings, Eva and Aloran looked at the pillar of light in the sky, shocked.

“That’s… Non-Falling Light??!”

Eva said disbelievingly.

“Who else in the Sect could break through to the Non-Falling Level in such a short time? Could it be King Cat?”

“No way! That’s not King Cat’s voice!” Aloran was equally shocked, and murmured softly.

Ever since Garen dominated the entire Scarlet Snow Sect, they had left the Courtroom, thick with conspiracy, in a rage. They wanted to leave alone, but they could not break away completely, both of them had their own relatives. They both came from large family clans, with at least a hundred members in total, their parents, their children and grandchildren. All of these people lived under the protection of the Scarlet Snow Sect, and could not escape at all.

So all they could do was turn a blind eye to this, and secretly investigate the change in the Elder while also secretly transferring their families and assets away.

At first, they had thought that since they did not support Garen, and the Scarlet Snow Sect had two of its Elders go missing, the Sect’s strength would be affected. But now, someone had actually broken through to Non-Falling Level!

“If it’s not King Cat, then who is it?” Alice sighed. “I just got the news, two weeks ago Garen announced the latest situation, Star Cloud and Black Blade have started warring against each other, and the impact is felt far and wide. The battle has already spread to more than thirty planets, and our Scarlet Snow Sect has been implicated as well. The Major Battle has been delayed indefinitely now.”

“Then what do we do now?” asked Aloran dejectedly, looking at the Non-Falling Light with some envy in her eyes.

“I heard that two Perpetual Motioner Holy Lords have joined in as well, once it’s reached such an extent, our Scarlet Snow Sect can only hide in our headquarters, keep a low profile, and wait to see how it ends.” Alice was melancholic. “But even such a wish might not come true.”

“You mean…” Aloran suddenly thought of something.

“That’s right. That one will probably come…” Alice nodded.

Psst-psst-psst!!

Suddenly, three more pillars of light shot into the sky. They were all Non-Falling Light!

This time, Alice’s eyes widened, and Aloran was completely stunned.

“Wh-what’s this?!” Her mouth fell open as she stared at the four pillars of white-blue light shooting into the sky, and she could not close it for a long time.

Chapter 1087: Chaos 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the dark blue Courtroom basilica.

“What’s the situation?” Garen’s voice fell from a height. It was grand and broad, giving people a sense of extreme prestige.

Second Elder and the other two old men quietly stood in the center of the basilica in a shape that resembled a fan.

The two old men were similar in their appearances. They seemed to be twin brothers and were advanced in years. They had white hair and white beards. Each of them had a black cane in their hands and their white robe was constantly puffed out by the cold stream.

They were the Ice-Crack and Ice-Grand brothers who had returned to the headquarters from the polar base. After acquiring the Distorted Seed, the two Non-falling Levels’ strength had entered an unfathomable state. Adding to the ambiguity of their body aura, even Garen did not know what level they had reached. After all, the greater the strength of the parasite of Distorted Seed, the more terrific the increase was.

After Second Elder acquired the Distorted Seed, from his initial stage at the bottom of the Non-falling Level, he had only risen to the peak of the Non-Falling Level. He could be considered to have only just restored the dignity of the original Second Elder. But now, he was somewhat shrinking in fear in front of Ice-Crack and Ice-Grand.

If Garen had not checked to confirm that the real Second Elder had been completely killed off by Carthage, leaving only this flesh for this fellow to parasitize, and if it were not for him occupying the body of Second Elder, he would have gotten rid of this disgusting waste with a strike earlier on.

“The statistics are already out,” Second Elder reported with a fawn smile. “In the whole sect, there are a total of one hundred and sixty-seven Inherited Levels with more than half of them breaking through recently. Under the increase brought about by the Scarlet Snow Wine, they have acquired the Armor of Ice and their strength has greatly improved.”

“Get to the point!” Garen said coldly.

“Yes, yes, yes…” Second Elder, or the parasite, whose real name was Dansey, quickly put it short. “The number of Non-falling Levels has been completely stabilized at about eleven people.”

“Eleven people? Is it possible to have even more?” Garen asked.

“The possibility of having more is not big…” The Fake-Second-Elder, Dansey, quickly answered.

“Since this is a Secret Technique Sect, we must restore the glory of Secret Technique…” A thought flashed through Garen’s mind. “From now on, discard the system of elders and put all those who entered Non-falling Level into the new position of Ice Demon General. Their authority is one-third of the original elders.”

“Sect Master, that’s eleven people. Would the number be too many?” Ice-Grand frowned from beside.

“Many? How could it be many?” Garen shrugged it off. “I think it is too few instead. That is how it will be. In addition, change the name Armor of Ice to Ice Demonic Armor. You are all dismissed.”

“Yes.”

The trio retreated respectfully. The more powerful they were, the more they felt the horrific aura around Garen, and the more they realized the gap between Garen and them.

After the trio had left, a white old man soon entered the basilica slowly.

It was Osho Ice-Ocean, who had originally wanted to return and seize power. He was an over five-thousand-and-six-hundred-years-old ancient.

At this time, he looked not much different from those old gentlemen; white slim suit and a neat white-golden short hair with a strand of it hanging from the right side corner. A small tuft of white beard was left on the chin, while the rest was shaved cleanly.

Holding a white cane in one hand and an eyeglass, which was just taken off, in another hand, his posture was straight and tall and his expression was solemn.

Anyone who saw him the first time would get an impression of one who was clean, elegant, calm and steady. But, in the same way, such a face would also give people an ambitious sense of power.

“Sect Master, what have you sought this old man for?” Ice-Ocean asked with a hint of awe from the depths of his heart.

“As the best-informed family, how is the situation now?” Garen went straight into the topic. He had asked Osho to go collect information these days and now it was time to grasp the information.

“There is something wrong with the situation. The Major Battle has been delayed and Magnetic Field did not give any specific reply. However, there is news circulating from many small and medium sects that the Major Battle this time is likely to cause a reshuffle in three major organizations,” Osho Ice-Ocean replied softly. “I am sending people to conduct a careful investigation. Because of the uncertainty of the news, it was not reported to Sect Master yet.”

“Did Alice and the others make any movements?”

“No. They wanted to leave, but now that there are wars and disputes, the Stargates nearby have been dominated by the big Sects. It’s okay for a single person to leave, but it can be troublesome when there are more people,” explained Osho.

Garen also understood that this may be the work of the three major organizations, but it was more likely that Carthage and others had given impetus to the situation. Only by sealing off the Stargates could the Energy Machinists be completely eliminated.

In any case, the Scarlet Snow Sect had finally survived the original storm. As one of the surviving sects, the Scarlet Snow Sect was eliminated only after more than a hundred years in the Battle of Ice Age.

From this perspective, there was just enough time to settle his own business.

Garen’s eyes glimmered slightly.

“Go prepare. You will temporarily preside over the sect. I’m going out on a trip.”

“Going out!?” Osho Ice-Ocean was a little surprised. “Sect Master, the situation within the Sect has just been settled, and there are wars and chaos on the outside. At this kind of time, we need a powerful figure such as you, Sect Master, to keep watch. Going out now might cause instability in the hearts of the people!”

He was not feigning it but was really considering it. Although he had vainly tried to seize power, during this times of war, strength and capability were the foundation of it all. With a powerful figure like Garen keeping watch, it was served as a reassurance.

“It’s okay. I’ve got my own arrangements,” Garen said lightly. “Pull back the Business Alliance completely and drop the peripheral parts of the business first. Have everyone return to the headquarters of Planet Scarlet Snow. All the powerhouses on Planet Naga are to return as well. The resources in stock are sufficient for us to use up to hundreds of years. During this time, we just need to quietly wait for the war to pass.”

“Since Sect Master has already made a decision, I will not say anything more. It’s just that, Sect Master, the present situation hasn’t reached this level yet, has it?”

Garen was calm and collected. His knuckles gently knocked on the seat.

Pap.

A silver resplendent star map suddenly appeared in the air between the two people.

The star map was a square. The map was full of twinkling stars and dots. Each star represented a planet.

“These are the two major nebulae. The Human Race and the Finite People are divided into two sides.”

Garen lifted his finger and the square star map was immediately divided into two blocks: red and blue. On the blue parts, there appeared the logo of Human Race, while the red showed the Finite logo.

Hiss…

The nebula of the Human Race quickly magnified and occupied the entire square star map, making the entire star map a blue one.

“We are…here.” Garen raised his finger and gently pointed.

Hum!

On the blue star map, a small, irregular area emerged from the furthest corner, turning white with the Energy Machinist logo appearing on it.

“Whether it is the Positive Spatial Universe or the Negative Spatial Universe, our star region is only this large, less than one-tenth of the entire Human Race area,” Garen continued.

Osho Ice-Ocean knitted his eyebrows together and was puzzled.

“However, we have occupied one-third of the entire Human Race’s resources, and perhaps even more,” The Garen’s tone changed, becoming increasingly low and deep.

Osho Ice-Ocean was immediately startled.

“You mean…the pilots might take action against us… That’s impossible! We Energy Machinists have the support of the Regent Level!”

“Nothing is impossible,” Garen said plainly. “By now, perhaps many of the top-level people have already seen some indication of it. This is an open secret. But as the Stargates have been sealed off, there is also no way to escape.”

“If that is the case! Then all the more you should not leave!” Osho was stunned and spoke in a low voice.

“I have my plan and intention. You need not worry,” Garen raised his hand to stop him from speaking. “In addition to that, I may bring someone to leave together. Rest assured.”

Osho frowned hard and felt that the situation was turning more complex and stranger. He was feeling more and more that this Sect Master, who had always been mysterious, was unfathomable. The Scarlet Snow Sect was a small sect and yet, he could actually know this kind of classified information. One could imagine how profound the card this new Sect Master had in his hand.

“In that case, who are you planning to bring along?”

“Turing,” Garen whispered with a smile.

******************

Mother Planet.

Central Academy.

The vast towers and castle of the Central Academy stood quietly on an isolated island in the middle of the ocean. The white castle had an irregularly triangular, cone-like shape with honeycomb-like black holes on it. A large number of small spaceships went in and out of the mouth of the honeycomb continually.

From time to time, a flock of white seabirds would circle around the castle and made cawing noises.

Blue sky, white clouds, sunshine, beaches, and white gull birds together with the white castle and minaret which stood in the middle.

A spaceship in the sky slowly released a white projection.

“Celebrating the three thousandth year of the establishment of the Central Academy.”

The white projection was still as it continued to surf in the sky, displaying to anyone passing by below.

The castle was surrounded by white roads extending in all directions. Exquisite and gorgeous sedans continued to hover above. Many of these cars were driven by students and instructors. Occasionally, one could see a Mech flying out of the castle heading far away.

In one of the cars, a tall and robust man admired the huge Central Castle.

“It’s beautiful. One will definitely feel good to study in this environment. With the beach, pretty girls, swimsuits, tsk tsk…”

The man had a V-shaped white mark between his eyebrows. It seemed to be an inlaid metal tattoo. He had short purple-black hair, and his outfit was no different compared to any other students. The white T-shirt and jeans looked very inconspicuous.

“Nono, if you want to go back to the Blackboard Academy, you can only transfer from here. There really is no other way. Only this place has a long-distance teleportation portal. This thing is extremely expensive. It costs at least ten thousand Universal Units to teleport once. Apart from the rich people, most people are forced to either drive or to fly by spaceship.”

The driver was a student of the Central Academy, Luke, whom he encountered on the way by chance and gave him a friendly ride.

Luke was a typical rich kid. He was only an ordinary second-year student at the Central Academy and was only here to gild himself.1

The two men looked out of the window. On the golden beach in the distance, one could see some girls in bikinis and men walking and playing with water over there.

“I heard that there are also many beautiful women in Blackboard. It is said that the people in Maria Region are all women. Tsk tsk, how nice. Unfortunately, my hometown is on the Western continent. Otherwise, I can go and have a look too…” Luke was a standard dandy disciple, but he was enthusiastic about making friends and liked to travel. “I also know a few friends from Blackboard who came to study at Central Academy. How about going with them together when the time comes?”

“It doesn’t matter to me so long as I can go back,” Garen smiled faintly. He was sent directly to the Mother Planet through a Star-Level teleportation portal. From Planet Scarlet Snow to the Mother Planet, he had spent two golden crystals. The expense was huge. But he did not expect the teleportation portal on the Mother Planet was in disrepair since the early years, causing an error in the teleportation positioning and sending him directly into the Radiation Zone in the wilderness. Furthermore, the current Mother Planet was still in the stage of an inter-region blockade, as the Predator Wave was still at its peak.

Garen could only quietly enter the nearest region, and he did not expect it to be Central Region, which had the largest territory and was the site of Central Academy. He then simply went straight to the Central Academy to use its long-distance teleportation portal to return to Blackboard Region.

As a result, he met Luke on the way. According to him, he saw that Garen had an extraordinary temperament and was clearly not an ordinary person. He sincerely wanted to befriend him, which was why he took the initiative to pull over and gave him a ride.

Chapter 1088: Chaos 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I don’t know how it is like in the Blackboard Region recently and what has changed there. I haven’t been back there for a long time. After graduating for so many years, I really don’t know if a lot of things are still there,” Garen sighed.

“Hehe, people always miss their hometown when they are outside. It’s also human nature,” Luke laughed. “Speaking of which, Black Star Diofie who came from your Blackboard Region is really awesome. He withstood the alliance between two major regions by himself and has become a pillar of the region at such a young age. My sister especially adores him and keeps viewing him as her idol, constantly telling me about him…”

Garen shook his head. Black Star Diofie actually became the pillar of the Blackboard Region. He wondered what kind of changes had taken place in these years. His fame had even spread to Central. Presumably, the recent reputation of Blackboard Region was very great.

“That year when the Divine Wind General rebelled, the vitality of the Blackboard Region greatly suffered. The Black Flood Party was divided into two, one part in the Blackboard Region and another in the Polar Region. If it wasn’t for the emergence of Diofie, I reckon that the Blackboard Region would have ceased to exist. Our battle-class professor regarded this reversal battle as a classic,” Luke praised. When speaking to a certain kind of people, one had to find a certain common topic to talk about. Since Garen was from the Blackboard Region, he would naturally pick this area of topic.

“I don’t know how my professor is doing now,” Garen sighed.

“Once you return, you’ll know.” Luke raised his hand and pointed forward. “See that? That right there is the long-distance teleportation portal. The one on the leftmost leads directly to the Blackboard Region.”

Following the direction of his finger, Garen looked up and saw that there was a row of tall, circular arched doors at the far end. The middle of the door was flowing with a thin, membrane-like liquid that flashed with a blue light.

The doors were more than ten meters high. They were extremely large. There were more than ten doors in a row, and each of them corresponded with the names of the different regions. Among them, the rightmost one was the Blackboard Region.

There was also the Polar Region and other names that had not been heard of. Obviously, only when the scale reached a certain level would it be qualified to arrange a teleportation portal here.

Chhh!

The car drifted sideways and stopped.

“I can only send you ’til here,” Luke said with a smile. “There are soldiers in front that do not allow cars to pass.”

“It’s okay. Thanks a lot for sending me all the way here,” Garen politely expressed his gratitude and looked up at the large door to the Blackboard Region. The doorway was still sparsely lined up, with about a dozen people waiting for an inspection before teleporting.

“It’s all right! Remember to get your teleportation card. Without such a thing, you’re not allowed to be teleported,” Luke kindly reminded.

Garen smiled.

“Don’t worry. When you have time, come to the Blackboard Region. You must remember to contact me then.”

“Hehe. Have a safe journey,” Luke waved, drove his car and left after turning around the bend.

Garen looked at the electronic inspection device on the white road ahead, smiled and walked over.

Doo. Doo.

After a subtle sound of inspection, Garen, who did not have any proof of identity, naturally passed it. His identity wrist-watch was already destroyed by the Blackboard Region back then. Nonetheless, what was the point of a proof for him now?

He went along with the queue, slowly waiting for the inspection. However, with the use of Inherited Level Willpower, he easily mingled in. Garen followed the crowd flow and directly walked into the blue liquid of the huge teleportation portal, disappearing instantly.

Just as he entered the teleportation portal, the entire portal shook violently and the surface surged with large ripples.

“A high-energy creature had mingled in just now! Check the equipment quickly! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!”

“Notify the Blackboard Region and immediately send out a warning!!”

A few senior officers in a group of soldiers stationed over there immediately panicked and issued a series of instructions loudly.

“What’s with the panic? People were just passing by!” A white-haired old man with a goatee appeared out of nowhere in front of the teleportation portal and was hovering in the air.

“In… Inherited Level professor!”

Most of the soldiers were ordinary people. They rarely had the chance to see an Inherited Level powerhouse in the castle. At this time, there was a sudden exclamation.

The old man breathed out a sigh of relieved without anyone noticing.

“Fortunately, that lad, Luke, had safely sent this old monster away…”

Recalling the message his grandson had sent him, he said that he had encountered a horrific guy whose limit could not even be detected by the aura detector. He immediately rushed over and did not expect that from far, he could feel that this guy was definitely extraordinarily powerful. Even the Dean of the Academy was incomparable to that vast ocean-like aura. How could a powerhouse of this level appear on the Mother Planet!?

The resources of the Mother Planet had long been scarce. There was nothing else valuable other than some ruins. Non-falling Level was almost the strongest ranks. Most of the more powerful powerhouses had left the Mother Planet to more prosperous places. It was impossible for them to come to such a barren place to hamper their own development.

“Anyway, as long as he has left, it’s fine. It’s fine…” The old man was relieved.

“Someone! Immediately close the Blackboard Region teleportation portal!” He ordered loudly right away. “There is something wrong with the teleportation portal and it needs to be repaired immediately.”

He himself, on the other hand, flew directly to the main castle. He must immediately report this incident. His instinct told him that there probably was going to be a major change of events in the direction of the Blackboard Region.

**********************

Osiris City by the border of Blackboard Region.

Osiris was only a small city, but it was garrisoned with one of the Five Great Border Corps, the Lion King Corps. It was led by a military chief, who was a Level-Five pilot stationed here named Lion King Ryan.

This place was also the main checkpoint to examine the incoming and outgoing of people teleporting.

Soldiers and Mechs in black uniforms guarded the huge, long-distance teleportation portal.

One by one, the teleporters came out from the inside, each pulling their own luggage. They quickly began to go far away to make a call.

“Please show your wrist-watch and then leave quickly along the safe route. This is a high-radiation zone.”

“Please do not stay near the teleportation portal so as to avoid high radiation from damaging the body.”

The sweet broadcaster kept on giving out instructions. There were cars parked outside the railings in the distance. They were all vehicles that had come to pick up their loved ones and friends.

The noisy crowd lined up. After the entire body was scanned by the Mech soldiers’ electronic scan, they quickly left one after another.

Hum…

Suddenly, the entire teleportation quavered, triggering a large number of ripples. It then abruptly closed off with a screech.

Garen had just stepped out of the teleportation portal when he felt the teleportation portal closing behind him.

He smiled lightly, not at all surprised. Luke’s appearance and the observers in the dark on the way made him aware that Luke was not so kind as to help him. Although this situation was obvious, it was also expected.

Hiss…

Taking a deep breath and closing his eyes, he felt the familiar scent in the air.

“Finally… I’m back here again…”

Returning once again, he looked at the surrounding Mech soldiers that were just Level One and Two. Faraway, an estimated Level-Four aura that was rushing over here was probably the most powerful person in the vicinity. After just coming back from the busiest metropolis filled with powerhouses, he was reflecting on the barren state here where a Level Four could be considered a powerhouse.

The huge gap made Garen shook his head slightly.

In the Three Major Metropolis, Level Four Energy Machinists could only be considered as technicians and they were the largest group of workers. Meanwhile, over here, they could be high-level generals who guarded this kind of important teleportation portals.

If such pilots were put on Planet Naga, they could only be the underlings of the ordinary Level One and Two sect disciples.

Mixing in the crowd, he watched a grand spaceship fly quickly into the sky. Black standard Mechs with a black disc on their back jumped down from it.

Professor… Seventh Divine Wind General… and also a biochemist Bamente, Ice Dragon, Fila as well as the Sixth Divine Wind General who had saved him before. One by one, their faces flashed through Garen’s mind non-stop. Finally, it was fixed on a pretty and striking girl’s face.

“Celine…”

Garen let out a breath lightly.

It was time, to end everything.

Fila, who had caused him to almost die back then, Seventh Divine Wind General, and Bamente. These three were his primary targets. As for the Professor, who had once helped him even though he gave up in the end…

“Turing, what do you think I should do?” Garen’s lips were motionless, but he used Willpower to transmit his voice directly.

Turing had always been hidden in the air around him. As Garen advanced to the Non-falling Level, they had also advanced to the degree of Non-falling Level. It was just that they had a layer of cutting-edge invisible clothing on them.

“Mother Planet is merely a poor and underdeveloped area used by Energy Machinists as their experimental zone. With Master’s power, there is absolutely no need for any fear. Nobody will try to offend Master because of the Mother Planet,” Turing answered faithfully.

“I used to live here for many years. There are many people here whom I have once known…” Garen said plainly.

“Master’s will is the fate of Mother Planet,” Turing’s voice slowly came about.

The wind was blowing, and the sun gave off a warm feeling as it shone on the body.

There was silence for a long time.

Garen slowly laughed.

“In that case…”

He gradually closed his eyes, and an invisible wave of power slowly spread out.

The sky was gradually filled with dark clouds and they were getting denser. In just a few moments, the entire city was covered with darkness.

“Is it going to rain again? Didn’t it just rain?”

“Didn’t the weather forecast said that it will be sunny today and tomorrow?”

“The weather forecast has never been reliable!”

The teleporters who passed by Garen complained.

“Blackboard Region, Polar Region… Your destinies are about to be the same as this dark sky. Will there be anyone who can break open this dark cloud… who can break through this fate…”

Garen murmured in a whisper. His figure suddenly blurred, instantly disappearing among the crowd.

Numerous dark clouds covered both the Blackboard Region and the Polar Region at almost the same time. Even the vast Radiation Zone in between was covered. The abundant dark clouds obscured the sunlight in the sky.

The temperature dropped rapidly, and reports of the sudden formation of cold air were everywhere.

The atmosphere that was supposed to be summer seemed to have returned to winter all of a sudden.

The Capital, Blackboard City…

“Snow! It’s snow! It’s snowing! Mommy, mommy, it’s snowing!” A child on the street was so surprised that she caught a snowflake in a glove and hopped and ran in the direction of home.

Plentiful snowflakes descended from the sky.

At the highest point of Blackboard City, a slender, black, pointed Mech was half-squatting on the tip of the minaret on a Blackboard battleship.

Black Star Diofie in the cabin was no longer the handsome young man back in those years. His hair was white on both sides and there were obvious wrinkles on his face, showing signs of senility that were not supposed to be there.

Chhh…

The roof of the cabin opened. He sat in the Mech and looked up at the falling snowflake in the sky.

“Snow?”

He reached out his hand in a daze, caught a little snowflake, and watched it melt gradually in his palm.

As soon as the snow melted, he felt an intense anxiety in the depth of his Willpower.

“Dean.”

Suddenly, a light curtain screen appeared in front of him automatically. A young woman on it spoke solemnly.

“It’s weird. The Intelligence Bureau sent news that the Polar Region and we have a sudden unusual gathering of clouds in the sky above. All areas, including the Radiation Zone, have begun to snow as such.”

“Notify the professors in the Inner Courtyard to organize a group of experts to conduct a research. We must make clear the source of this snow,” Diofie frowned.

“Understood.”

“I don’t know why,” Diofie whispered. “I have a bad feeling.”

Chapter 1089: Return 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Blackboard City

The city which was once referred to as the Blackboard City had fallen more and more into desolation and disarray. The prosperous streets and alleys were full of rubbish, and broken pieces of newspapers were scattered all over the ground. Some wild dogs and cats were still looking for food residues in the trash, and whimpering sounds could be heard from time to time.

The vagrants and wanderers who had never appeared squatted and wandered in the depths of the alley, fighting with the wild dogs for food.

The ruined walls of the building, the dark and dirty streets on the green belt, and the occasionally-agitated curses coming from the vehicles that passed by.

Garen walked slowly in this capital, Blackboard City. From the teleportation point, he arrived here straight away without any delay at all. Fila and the Seventh Divine Wind General from back then, as well as the biochemist Bamente, had surely left this place.

Coming here, Garen’s only wish was merely to have a look at the current Blackboard Academy and to visit his previous professor.

He slowly walked down the street.

“Hehe… Kid, people from outside who pass through this place have to pay a protection fee… Do you understand the rules?” A few thugs came out of the alley and stopped in front of Garen. They wore an aura of teasing and malice on their faces.

The few remaining passersby around hurried to flee and pretended not to have seen anything at all.

Garen’s black, top-grade clothing looked no different from the rich young master wandering on the outside. His smile was mild, but it gave people a kind of pretentious feel.

He recalled that once, he did not know who had told him that if he did not know how to be nice to the people around you, then just keep on smiling. By doing this, it would let those who were genuinely thinking of you know that you were doing well and there was no need to worry…

“Protection fee?” Garen looked at the three bullies in front of him. “When does Blackboard City have this kind of thing there?”

Looking at the calm and composed Garen, something seemed amiss. The few bullies started to have a bad feeling.

“Our boss is…” Boom!

A muffled sound was heard. The three bullies flew out at the same time, slamming into the sides of the walls. The sound of their bones being cracked burst out. Before they could even shout out in pain, it was unknown whether they were dead or alive. Blood slowly flowed down from the three people and formed a small bloody puddle on the ground.

Garen did not even lift his hands. This was only one-hundredth of his One Time Fist Pressure. One Time Fist Pressure would not increase any power but evenly dispersed the force from the fist into the vacuum around it, instantly breaking out the same force in all directions.

It was not merely a little power of the fist.

“Was it still a little over?” Garen frowned slightly. He had originally intended to keep them alive, but he did not expect one-hundredth of One Time Fist Pressure to be this heavy…

Boom.

There was a light sound of windows closing in the upper floors.

The surroundings suddenly became emptier. The entire street became increasingly desolate; several cars darted pass in an accelerated speed as if the drivers were fleeing for their lives.

Garen put his hands in his pockets and looked at the city that had become even more desolate due to the war. If this place had become as such, let alone other places.

“Go and see Celine’s residence first…”

As soon as he thought of it, Garen went a little further to stop a taxi.

Once in the car, he mentioned the name of the place Celine’s house was at.

“That place… Oh, the original villa district of the Academy,” The driver was a chubby, middle-aged man with a crew cut and he had a black, knife-like leather by his side. He looked at Garen from the rear-view mirror.

“Are you a student of the Academy?” He asked as he started the car. “Your temperament does not look like the average person.”

“How is it over there now?” Garen smiled and asked.

“Still okay. In the war these recent years, many have died. The Academy has rushed to recruit a lot of freshmen, but it has become a bit messy,” The driver replied casually. “Now, even an ordinary bully will not dare to go to that place. That place is filled with powerhouses with Willpower. Ordinary people who go there are just looking for a beating. In the beginning, I have also mingled over there, but I did not expect that in the blink of an eye…”

The driver began to talk incessantly. Although he looked fierce, no one would expect him to actually be such a long-winded person. He could not get to the point after talking for half a day, and he immediately began to talk about his brilliant years back then.

Garen was not impatient. Instead, he sat quietly looking out the window.

It was really regrettable that this once-prosperous city had become dilapidated to this extent in such a short period of time.

Along the way with the driver’s babble, Garen finally arrived at the villa district near Blackboard Academy.

He got out of the car and paid with a black card that had been prepared beforehand. This black card was previously stolen from a rich man. The order here had been chaotic to a point where even the number of soldiers was far from enough. Not to mention, the police was also lacking in quantity. The social order could only be maintained at a basic level.

Garen knew the way well and went around the path with ease. He soon saw Celine’s villa in the middle among rows of small white villas.

This place was vacant and there were not many people living in. It was afternoon. With the dark clouds in the sky, the snow falling and the lights dim, it was still dead silent here, seemingly deserted. Only a villa was spotted with lights on in a far distance away.

Garen followed the road in the district. On his way, he did not see anyone else except for the broken streetlights. The entire district had almost become a dead city.

Walking to the door of Celine’s villa, there were specks of thick dust on the ground everywhere. The self-defense guarding system of the villa had also stopped monitoring and defending for a long time. The entire villa was dark and unusually quiet.

Reaching out his hand and with a light flicker, the door creaked open. Garen slowly entered inside.

The huge living room was pitch-black. Only the metal armor figure of an ancient knight reflected a faint silver glimmer.

The air was filled with strong dust particles.

“Sure enough, there was no one…” Garen sighed. With a thought, a cold wind instantly rolled up in the villa, promptly blowing all the dust out of the house and gathering it in a corner.

The entire villa suddenly became much cleaner.

After wandering around the villa, Garen entered the basement again and looked at the place he had constantly trained with Celine back then. It was also dusty. He gazed at the familiar furnishing, but the people had completely left. It came upon him that he had not contacted Celine for a long time. Presumably, she had completely abandoned this house.

Many years ago, Celine returned the news that Nonosiva’s parents and sister had been completely settled down in the most peaceful center, the Freshwater Galaxy. Celine herself had also followed the Professor to the Freshwater Galaxy, and could only send back news once in a long time because the distance was too far away. Now that the long-distance Stargate was completely sealed off, there was absolutely no way of knowing what had happened.

“Freshwater Galaxy. Don’t know how they are doing…” Garen thought of Baylon again, who was destined to become the younger brother or sister of Royal Star. If it went according to history, she might soon be returning from Four-Star Alliance.

Just when they returned, there would be an eruption of an enormous energy tide. This grand occasion was just as nice as a good opportunity for him to devour energy. Garen came back at this crucial time for this exact reason, not only for revenge.

Moving about Celine’s basement, the familiar environment was still there, but the person was no longer here anymore. He himself could not escape from this vortex.

“If there is no relationship with Red Moon, no relationship with Baylon, perhaps whitewashing1 to become a pilot is also a good evasion method. Unfortunately… Life isn’t so kind as to allow so many ‘if’s. The moment I am noticed by White King, I will absolutely be the target to be used for coercion.”

Garen left the villa. His heart was still unable to calm down.

Walking along the path toward the outside of the villa district, he finally saw a few people: three men and a woman. The three men were dragging a girl toward the darker area. Their lustful laughter was mixed with the girl’s horrified crying sound. Obviously, they were not up to something good. Sure enough, the trouble that the driver mentioned was no ordinary because, among the three men, there was actually one who had Willpower fluctuation.

“Is the impact of the war really this big?”

Garen sighed.

“Even this city has decayed to such a point in just a few years’ time…”

His voice traveled from far into the ears of the four people. It was calm as if the event occurring before him was irrelevant. It was like he was watching a movie with total stillness.

“Who’s there!?” One of the three men pulling the girl shouted loudly and glared at Garen with a warning.

“Don’t meddle in, or else…” He did not finish his sentence, but the threatening message behind it was obvious.

“Help! Save me!” The girl seemed to have found hope and cried out loudly for help. “As long as you save me, I can give you money, Universal Units! One hundred thousand, one million! Please! Save me… ”

Pap!

The man who spoke gave her a hard smack across the face.

“Bitch, back then when I pursued you, you were unwilling and humiliated me with all kinds of way. You looked down on me, eh? What about now? Hehe!”

He grabbed the girl’s hair.

“Aren’t you virtuous? Aren’t you a goddess? Why are you crying like this now? Didn’t you look down on me? Ah! Now you know how to seek help?”

The man laughed sinisterly.

“Let go of Nolan!” In the quietness, a quivering female voice suddenly rang out from the darkness not far away.

A black-haired girl in a white tunic dress slowly walked out of the darkness. She also held a pair of high heels in her hand. Her black, clean single ponytail and her delicate, fair face gave out a simple yet elegant aura.

It was only that the girl now looked abnormally discomposed. Her forehead was slightly sweaty and her breathing was a bit too quick. It was apparent that she ran over here. Parts of the black tights on her legs were torn.

“Tesna!” The girl who was held was instantly overjoyed. “Save me, quickly save me! These fellows are crazy!”

“Tesna, nothing concerns you here. You had better not butt in,” The man warned fiercely.

The response he received was the white dress girl doing a run-up to give him a ferocious elbow strike.

The lightning-like elbow accurately struck the tall man who had come forward from behind to block her. He was the one with Willpower, clearly the man’s bodyguard.

“Spin axis!”

Tesna’s elbow was blocked, but her arms suddenly straightened out, changing to a knife-hand to strike the other party’s neck.

“What?” Garen viewed from his peripherals. The girl’s moves faintly resembled his Twelve Flying Dragon Fist. When he taught Celine at the beginning, he did not restrict her from teaching others this fist technique. However, he only did not expect to encounter someone who knew this fist technique in this vicinity by chance.

Chapter 1090: Return 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The girl, Tesna’s fist technique was very surface-leveled. Compared to the other party’s Willpower, she was obviously a little weaker in her actions, reactions, and prejudgment. Coupled with her lack of strength, she gradually fell into a disadvantageous position. If it were not for the fact that the concept of the fist was stronger than the other party, she would not have been able to hold out long ago.

“I’m someone who wants to pursue ultimate power! How can I lose out here?!” Celine’s roar from that time reverberated in his ears again. Seeing the girl was still struggling, Garen recalled how Celine persisted under his fist technique back then.

These ordinary people were far from achieving the realm of flawlessness. Although flawlessness was something relative, when the strength and speed were not equal, there would be an outburst of flaws. However, to be flawless in the scope of ordinary people could be achieved through advanced computer-simulated training, just like Eagle’s Nest of the Blackboard Academy back then. Obviously, Tesna was just an ordinary person incapable of reaching that level.

“Left knee forward.”

Garen suddenly voiced out.

Boom!

Tesna involuntarily gave a knee-forward hit and it strangely landed on the lower body part of the opponent, who had wanted to dodge.

A sound was heard, and something seemed to have broken…

The tall man clasped his lower body and howled miserably, rolling around on the ground.

Tesna was dumbfounded on the spot. She did not expect her earlier move to be so powerful.

Suddenly, two other men surrounded her. Their face darkened.

Meanwhile, that girl who was held captive had already fled some time ago, leaving her alone instead.

Both sides were going to start another fight for the second time, but Garen was somewhat impatient.

Although the girl who had betrayed her friend brought him a little surprise and fun, this kind of drama was also very sparsely common. It was just that this girl in a white dress, Tesna, still had such a naïve kindness within her, making him felt something.

“Turing, get rid of them.”

Garen informed plainly.

“Yes.”

A dark shadow suddenly lunged out of the darkness and swept past the three men in an instant. There were three muffled sounds at the moment, and all three fainted at the same time. The dark shadow quickly penetrated into the darkness and disappeared.

Garen was too lazy to watch and turned away.

Tesna was left standing on the spot, stupefied. She immediately knew that she had met an expert.

“Must be a powerhouse!” Her heart suddenly thumped. The outbreak of war brought a serious loss of sense of security. As a result, there were more and more martial arts practitioners with relatively good battle skills. Some even installed a miniature Mech to strengthen themselves. This was a good way for self-defense. The government had also liberalized the restrictions on miniature Mech because of the ever-growing legal problems. Anyone with money could purchase a set. This had also led to the increasing popularity of battle skills.

Tesna was a typical fanatic lover of combat, at the same time, she was also a typical character of one who had a serious lack of security.

“Wait up!”

She shouted loudly and ran after Garen right away.

Unexpectedly, even though Garen seemed to be pacing slowly in the dark, she could not catch up no matter what.

Tesna felt strange, but this all the more confirmed that the other party was an absolute powerhouse, and not just not any ordinary ones.

“I will absolutely not let this opportunity pass this time! Absolutely!” Tesna gritted her teeth and ran madly. Even though her socks were worn out and her skirt was flapping due to the wind, she did not seem to notice them at all. She chased after Garen madly without any shoes on. However, the distance between them did not close in even with her accelerated speed, instead, it was getting further.

“Why are you chasing me?” A voice sounded in her ears.

“Whew… Whew… To be your disciple…!” Tesna was out of breath. She was sweating profusely and there was an abnormal flush on her face.

“Be my disciple?” Garen stopped. The momentary pause caused Tesna to almost bump into him from behind. She immediately braked, and only then did she feel a burning pain in both her feet. Obviously, she had injured the skin.

What Garen appreciated was people with a strong determination, just like Sinno from Radiation Zone; that child was untalented, yet she was constantly putting in hard work. And so, he helped her to obtain the hope of having Sixth Divine Wind General’s guidance; a hope to bail herself out of her own fate.

And now, he seemed to see a trace of this quality again in the girl.

“Bring my disciple is not an easy thing…” He turned around and spoke quietly as he looked at this girl, who was not quite pretty but had a good temperament.

“I know,” Tesna did not talk much, but her tone was resolute.

Looking at this little fellow, Garen immediately remembered that, in the Totem World and Secret Technique World, he seemed to be in favor of those children with this kind of cold temperament but a firm determination. It was the same, even for now.

“You must understand that if you want to be my disciple, you must accept my test. And the hardship of some tests is beyond your imagination.”

Tesna recalled the strange scene she had just seen. It was just the spin of a shadow and the three people totally fainted without any resistance.

As an untalented ordinary person, even if she cultivated Willpower, it would still be like a balloon leaking. There was no way to deal with it. Perhaps this person was her only hope!

“I’m not afraid!”

She nodded with certainty.

With Garen’s current status, he naturally would not simply take in disciples. As the Sect Master of Scarlet Snow Sect, the greatest genius in history, and the strongest person who had inherited dozens of ancestor’s Will, he was destined to surpass the first Sect Master and reach an unprecedented realm.

With such a level of power, taking in disciples would have a far-reaching impact. It was not just to him alone, but a kind of adjustment to all the people under his command as well.

“What do you want to learn from me?” Garen asked with interest.

“Battle skills! Powerful battle skills!” Tesna said without hesitation.

“Battle skills…” Garen immediately smiled. “I have three tests. If you can pass, I will decide to take you in as my disciple and teach you these battle skills.”

Tesna’s eyes lit up at once. The rapid breathing just now was forcefully suppressed to slow down, fearing she had misheard anything.

“Which three? I’m sure to pass without any problem!”

“Don’t overestimate yourself,” Garen extended a finger. “First, it is now snowing heavily. Within two days, dig out a two-meter-deep pit by hand. Remember, only by hand.”

“Only by hand?” Tesna repeated.

“Go ahead. At the unmarked burial-mounds outside of the city to the south. Remember, you can’t use other tools. You have to use your fingers to dig out the soil bit by bit,” Garen added. “I will come to see you when the time comes. If you can’t do it, then don’t mention the matter about being my disciple.”

“I’ll go!”

Tesna did not hesitate at all and flatly agreed. She did not ask how he would find her, instead just turning around and left without any disinclination.

“Tsk tsk… Maybe she really is promising,” Garen shook his head slightly. “Next up, let’s go and visit Professor.”

Looking at the figure of Tesna leaving, Garen turned around and slowly merged into the darkness, disappearing completely.

******************

Passing through Inner Courtyard was only a simple use of Willpower to Garen. The computer protection capability here was basically useless for high-level Energy Machinists.

The Energy Machine Imprint could calculate the loophole in a split second. Garen walked leisurely into the Outer Courtyard and roved around the Academy which had not changed much. He did not see any acquaintances. All of the people there were new students, so he went straight to the Inner Courtyard.

The Inner Courtyard was underneath the ground. After getting himself the status of a student, Garen naturally entered the underground space with a few Inner Courtyard students.

The artificial sun was still shining upon the entire Inner Courtyard.

Like the outside world, it was also rather deserted here. Obviously, there were too few people who met the high standards of the Inner Courtyard. There was almost hardly anyone on the street, and most of the shops were closed. Only a few were open but the customers were also very few.

Compared to the outside, there were still maintenance robots doing cleaning and maintenance work here.

Garen checked the address in accordance with the map obtained from the internal network. There were no changes made.

However, the Director of the Security Bureau had been changed from Fila to Red-Eyed Medero, who was a very mighty resonance powerhouse back then. He had no idea how strong her strength was now.

Following the original route, Garen once again came to Professor Van Doe’s residence, that same small, double-storey house which was white. It looked very ordinary.

Just when he was ready to knock on the door, the door opened automatically.

A yellow-haired woman about two meters tall looked at Garen puzzlingly.

“Who are you looking for?”

Garen’s image and temperament at this time had changed dramatically. In the eyes of those with Willpower, his entire body exuded a touch of faint chill, and he was completely a different person from the original Nonosiva. Adding to the horrific transformation of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, there was now only a faint contour of the past.

“Senior Sister Galafil?” Garen smiled and easily called out the other person’s name.

“Senior Sister? How do you know me? I don’t remember the Professor having you as a disciple.” Galafil was one of the three among Garen’s two senior brothers and senior sister in those years.

“Are Junior Brother Milo and Junior Sister Nehri doing well? Have you forgotten me after just a short period of time?” Garen said with a smile. “I’m Nonosiva…”

“Nono?!” Galafil’s expression suddenly became abnormally bizarre. The Nonosiva whom the Professor announced had betrayed and left the Blackboard Region was suddenly back!?

“Aren’t you going to invite me in?” Garen shrugged.

Only then did Galafil react over from her stunned expression.

“Please…come in.” She hurriedly let the door open.

Garen walked through the door, but he did not hear the voice of the smart butler.

“How did you think of coming back suddenly? Didn’t you leave?” Galafil seemed to have only heard bits of the original news. Obviously, Professor Van Doe did not tell her everything.

In any case, Garen was a victim of the conflict between the parties. If the truth was really announced everywhere, it would be harmful to the reputation of the Black Flood Party itself.

“After leaving for so many years, I miss my hometown, so I came back.” Garen entered the living room and sat down on his own to rest. “At that time, I was lucky enough to have escaped from the Blackboard Region. What happened after that? Senior Sister, why don’t you tell me? I heard that Fila and Seventh Divine Wind General who besieged me at that time were all declared as rebels. So, my case should have definitely be overturned?”

There was a trace of complexity in Galafil’s eyes as she sat opposite Garen, pouring out a glass of fruit juice for them both.

“Indeed, it has been overturned. Your matter has long been determined to have been wronged. The statement of your case was issued long ago. It’s just that, the monster that suddenly appeared when you were besieged had slaughtered many soldiers and civilians. Even though it was eventually encumbered and terminated, but…” She was not a fool. Although she did not know the truth, there were some things that could still be felt, such as Van Doe’s attitude back then, Britney’s attitude which initially supported Garen, as well as the sudden appearance of the besieging Mech forces at the hospital.

His own disciple was beleaguered, but as the Professor, he was unmoved. Was not this attitude obvious enough?

Chapter 1091: Test 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Oh, I’ll immediately ask the Professor to come back. He must be very happy that you have returned!” Even though there were some doubts in her heart, Galafil still knew that in the end, Nonosiva was naturally here for Professor Van Doe.

Although she did not know what Nono had experienced during these years, it could be seen from the huge change in the other party that these experiences would probably be nothing good. A good experience would never make a person change so much.

Garen took the glass of juice and gently drank it. Sitting on the sofa in the Professor’s house and drinking juice as such was something he left behind many years ago.

This kind of peaceful and lackadaisical life was not appropriate for the present him.

“How are you doing now? I have also tried to get hold of some news about you through my connections. Unfortunately, no one has ever seen you since your disappearance at that time. Everybody guessed that you went to the Radiation Zone. Otherwise, it was impossible not to have found you in the whole region,” Galafil informed the Professor and asked Garen at the same time.

“Still alright. I was able to manage through these years,” Garen knew that the other party still thought of him as the student from that year. Perhaps he had not even entered the higher stage of resonance. Now that he was back…

“Rest assured, the Professor will understand you for sure. Coupled with your case being overturned, you will definitely be able to live a good life in the region again. Oh right, what about your family? I went to the address of your family sometime later and found that they had already moved out,” Galafil was a very kind woman. Although her appearance was wide and tall, nevertheless she took care of the junior brothers and sister without any requests. If it were not for her own kind-heartedness, no one would even think of doing such a thing if there was no payment involved in this acquisitive society.

In the beginning, because Garen was also her junior brother, she put some effort to go around and investigate. Unfortunately, there was no result.

“Settle down?” Garen smiled.

“Yeah, you can rest assured. The Professor is now a lot older. In the last insurgency, your two senior brothers were…” Galafil lifted the cup and took a sip. Her expression was dejected. “Now, in retrospect, everything that had happened was just like a dream.”

“I’ll plead with the Professor. Plus, you were being wronged back then. Coming back to resettle and re-enter the party should not be a problem,” Galafil showed a gentle smile.

Garen lowered his head and the expression on his face could not be seen.

“He’s coming! Professor is back soon!” Galafil suddenly raised her voice. “I saw his location pointer. He’s not far away and is rushing back!” There was a smile on her face, “You see, as soon as he heard you are back, he immediately came back without any delay.”

Garen held the glass of juice. The glass covered most of his face as he drank quietly.

The two sat on the sofa. Galafil kept talking about what had happened in recent years in an unceasing flow of words while Garen listened silently, smiling from time to time.

Boom!

Suddenly a dull voice came in from the outside. A travel-worn black figure wearing a trench coat strode into the hall.

Van Doe was still that wizened old man from that time. He had a crutch in his hand, his back was a little hunched and the wrinkles on the skin of his face were increasingly packed. The right side of his neck could be seen with a dark blue code-number printed on the skin. It was the same compared to that time, except the color had faded slightly.

When he entered the door, his gaze instantly fell on Garen.

“You still know to come back!?” A severe tone.

Concerning this disciple whom he had given up at that time, his heart was somewhat guilty. This genius disciple had become a victim due to the conflict between the parties. It was also because he did not really support him fully. However, as a professor, having him admit his mistakes to his disciple was not something he could do! He, Van Doe, had lived for so long, and never had he apologized to anyone for his mistakes!

Garen and Galafil stood up and turned around to face Van Doe.

“Professor…” Garen spoke softly and looked calmly at this old man who was increasingly showing signs of senility. The death of the two disciples was a huge blow to him. Originally, there were many disciples under him. However, whether Garen was alive or not was unknown to him, and the two senior brothers died in the insurgency. Because of this, he was left with only a female disciple, his status was still considered stable. However, he no longer had the original influence he once had within Black Flood Party anymore.

“I don’t have you as my disciple!” Van Doe said coldly. Looking at Garen’s current appearance, there was not even a sense of Willpower left in him, and his looks had changed dramatically. Eventually, his heart softened a little. With the Willpower expelled, being alone on the outside was naturally extremely difficult, not to mention the previous years were during a period of war…

“Since you’re back, go to Eagle’s Nest right away! Get your Willpower back as soon as possible!”

“Professor…” Garen was still speaking calmly. Initially, he had no resentment for Van Doe. Although he finally gave up on him, he had also helped him a lot in the beginning. “This is my last visit here as a disciple. Perhaps, it is also the last time I’m addressing you as such…”

As soon as the words came out, Galafil was instantly dumbfounded in the hall. Van Doe’s expression was also stunned. He took a deep breath.

“What are you talking about, Nono!?” Galafil hurriedly said out loud. “Quickly apologize to Professor! Don’t destroy your future just because of an impulsive act! The Professor was only…”

“Shut up!” Before the words were finished, she was interrupted by Van Doe.

Van Doe’s face flushed and his hands trembled slightly. He fixed his eyes on Garen.

“You, what was it you just said? I didn’t hear clearly,” His voice was shaking a little. This was the biggest compromise he could make. He was Van Doe, who would never admit his faults! Never!

Ignoring Galafil’s frantic eye gestures from the side, Garen looked up and calmly faced Van Doe.

“Professor, there are some things that can never be reverted once they have happened…”

Some things that can never be reverted?

It was all silence in the hall.

Without having completely accepted the deaths of his two disciples whom he had trained wholeheartedly, no one could imagine Van Doe’s feelings at this moment. Back then, he had given up on Garen, but it was also for the reason that this disciple was too much of a troublemaker. Not only was he hostile to the branch party, there were also Fila’s forces. Not to mention, he was working with another inexplicable force.

Now…

He had initially put down everything in his hands and quickly came back, thinking that he had seen hope, or perhaps Nono had thought it through and therefore returned to his place. Perhaps, this was exactly the opportunity to make up for his mistake. Yet, now it seemed that…

Van Doe looked at this genius disciple whom he once had high hopes for. Now he had completely fallen to become an ordinary people. There was not even a trace of the pilot’s Willpower left. But even in such a situation, he was still not willing to bow his head before him.

Two of his disciples died in a battle, one of his disciples wanted to rebel, and there were two children who fell seriously ill… There was only one female disciple left, but her aptitude was insufficient, and she could possibly not break through forever…

“…Was I…really wrong? …”

For the first time. Van Doe could not help but ask himself for the first time.

“No! I am not wrong! They are! It’s them who do not understand me!” The distorted and restrained emotions erupted from his heart.

“I just came to tell you, Professor, that I don’t blame you for the matter back then. But everything from that time is even now.” Garen opened his mouth again. Looking at the clearly stubborn old man before him, he finally calmly said what he intended to.

“Nono!” Galafil yelled anxiously from one side.

“It’s okay,” Garen smiled mildly at her.

“It’s okay?!” Van Doe spoke up. His face was dark. A deep sense of fatigue emanated from him. “You, an ordinary person, without any Willpower. In this age of war, even if you rely on your brain, you could live well for a while. However, do you think you can live on like that for a lifetime!? Foolish! Funny! People can only rely on themselves!”

“Yeah, people can only rely on themselves,” Garen smiled. “Professor, you taught me this profound principle back then, didn’t you?”

Van Doe moved his lips but did not speak again.

For a time, the three people no longer spoke. There was only a deep sense of indescribable atmosphere in the hall.

After a long time, Van Doe raised his hand and his whole person seemed to have aged even more.

“After exiting this door, you will no longer be a disciple of my Black Flood Party. I will never give you another chance even if you beg me the next time!”

He stared at Garen steadfastly. In his eyes were anger, despondency, sadness, and a trace of plea in the deepest part.

Van Doe had no children in his lifetime. His disciples were his everything. But now, some of them were dead while some of them were sick. Everything he had worked hard for and had nurtured throughout his life seemed just to have just proven his mistake.

He repeated in his heart over and over again that he was right, he was right. However, the calmer Garen’s gaze was in front of him, the sadder he was in his heart. He remembered not only his two disciples who had died but also his wife who had died because of him…

Garen looked at the old man who was almost overwhelmed by the war. He himself did not know what he had hoped to see when he returned this time. Did he come back just to have this old man admit his mistake from that time?

Perhaps.

He smiled, turned around and headed outside of the hall.

“So be it,” His voice plainly echoed in the hall.

“I tell you! Without Willpower! Do you think other people will really value you!? Don’t ever come back once you step out of this door!” The old man’s shivering voice came from behind.

Garen did not stop but only paused. Still, his steps slowly moved toward the exit of the court.

A mistake was still a mistake. Many things were lost because of a mistake. Yet he was still reluctant to admit it. This was also the unfortunate part about Van Doe.

Everyone was unwilling to admit that they had done wrong.

The moment he stepped out of the door, Garen did not hear any sound behind him. It was all quiet, a dead silence.

He knew that Van Doe was not feeling sad for him, but he was feeling sad for own life instead. He vainly tried to prove that he himself was right by using coercion and dissuasion on him; to prove that he was without fault and that it was others who were at fault.

“Now, everything should be cleared up,” Garen looked up at the artificial sun overhead.

“I should go and see how the progress of that little fellow digging the pit,” Garen did not look back and strode to the exit, leaving the underground.

He did not go far before he saw a tall woman in a red, leather fitting-suit standing beside him. The woman had crimson eyes, and her messy shoulder-length black hair gave off a wild aura.

“Red-Eyed Medero?” Garen instantly recognized this person.

“Although I do not know who brought you into Inner Courtyard, but take out your proof of identity,” Medero specially made this trip for Garen.

She received a report that someone had entered Inner Courtyard in a non-conventional way. After looking at the data, she found out that something was amiss and she quickly rushed over herself.

Suddenly, Medero seemed to hear some sort of voice transmission, and her face instantly relaxed. She gazed deeply at Garen.

“You can go, but don’t let me catch you again the next time!”

Garen nodded with a smile.

He stood sideways slightly and glanced behind, knowing that it must have been his senior sister or Van Doe who spoke up to help mediate the situation.

In the end, he did not say anything more. He strode off and walked toward the elevator exit.

Chapter 1092: Test 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The unmarked common graves in the South District

A delicate and pretty young girl in a white dress continuously dug her fingers into the earth. However, the soil on the ground was very solid. Although her hands were already covered in scabs from the digging, she did not have the slightest intention of stopping.

The hole in front of her was already more than ten centimeters deep and half a meter wide. Blood-stained soil could be seen everywhere around the edges of the hole.

This place was deserted except for a few people who came to visit the graves. While minding their own business, they glanced at the girl from afar. People who went mad from the death of their relatives were not a rare sight. Hence, this was not their first time witnessing actions like these.

People came and visited the graves before leaving after that. The sky was filled with dark clouds from one end to the other. The snowfall kept increasing until the ground was covered in a thick layer of white snow. The young girl shivered from the cold and both her hands had turned a slight purple. The digging even caused her wounds to become badly frostbitten. Despite her strong body that was the product of constant training and the fact that she was currently wearing special warming underwear, long periods of going without rest and the lack of food consumption caused her physical strength to deteriorate.

Despite her broken fingernails, the young girl did not regret her actions at all and continued to dig downwards.

Unfortunately, the soil was extremely solid. Moreover, there were some rocks inside that were even harder than the ground. Some of the broken rocks even got embedded into her skin, causing the girl’s forehead to drip with sweat from the pain.

“Tesna! Why did you run here?! Come back with me!” A tall and muscular man spoke in a stern voice while standing beside the young girl.

“This is a test,” Tesna glanced at the man. “Big brother, you should go back. It’s cold here.”

“Can you just give up and stop bothering yourself just because you lack Willpower? Test? Who would test you by making you dig the ground until your hands are covered in blood?! Go! Go back with me!” The man took long strides over and grabbed Tesna. His great strength and Willpower instantly made it somewhat impossible for Tesna to retaliate.

“Let me go!!” She began to resist.

“Your hands will become useless if you keep digging!” The man was so furious that he could not think straight. “You’re just a normal person who can’t practice Willpower! If those people hadn’t teased you, would you really think that there was someone who could change your Appraisal?!”

“This is my decision! Let go!” yelled the girl as she bit the man’s arm.

“Do you want to die?!” The man instantly flung her off in one go. When he saw that his own arm was bleeding from the bite, he immediately became angrier. “If our old man hadn’t asked me to take care of you before he died, do you really think I’d be willing to care about you?!”

“I told you, you don’t have to care about me,” Tesna fell and sat on the snowy ground. Her cheeks were red and tinged with purple but it was unknown whether it was from her rage or the cold.

She and this man were not blood siblings. She had followed her father when he rebuilt his family with the man’s mother which meant that they had no blood relations. When her father was still here, she could still live a pretty good life even though she had no natural endowments. However, now that her father was gone, their family property was completely occupied by her older brother’s mother who had started to treat her coldly.

Although her older brother spoke fiercely, he was actually constantly looking after her. On the surface, he would say that he did not care if she died but he was endlessly concerned about her.

However, her older brother was about to get married and start his own family now. She had also grown older and did not have any reason to let him take care of her anymore.

She had to become independent and walk on her own path.

“You can go home. I’ll take care of my own matters,” said Tesna loudly.

Her older brother nagged her for some time here but could not change her mind. He finally gave up and went home angrily. Nonetheless, he could not help but leave a thick pair of leather gloves and a shovel before he left.

Unfortunately, Tesna turned a blind eye to this and continued using her bare hands to dig the soil.

It was not her first time doing something like this. Someone had lied to her before but she continued to trust them. Later on, an incident had almost occurred but she pressed on with a hint of wishful thinking that their promise would definitely become reality one day if she kept on trying. If she had given up and in the unlikely possibility that her wish actually became true, all of her past determination would be completely wasted, no?

Far away, Garen hid in mid-air silently and watched Tesna unearth the soil. He saw that she was not wearing the gloves or even using the shovel at all. Her fingers were about to be wrecked from the digging. Garen himself was somewhat unconsciously moved by this as well.

After all, he had merely said some words before the other party carried out his orders completely. Disciples and subordinates like her could not simply be encountered randomly.

“I’ll observe her for a little longer before I continue…”

Among the two people, one of them dug while the other watched as time passed slowly.

Tesna’s older brother came over to look a few more times. His anxiousness grew stronger every time.

Other than him, no one else from their household came over to show concern. Tesna was initially already sidelined from her entire household. Now, there were people who asked about the reason for her stupid actions as well. Apparently, her reasoning for this was to become an apprentice? She had coincidentally encountered a supposed battle skill powerhouse who simply told her to do this. However, no one had expected that this girl would actually believe his words.

The young ladies in her household sneered and said that she was stupid. She actually believed that a person whom she randomly met was a powerhouse? Even if he was a powerhouse, how powerful could he actually be if he was merely one who practiced battle skills? Could he be stronger than a Mech Pilot? Of course not.

In order to go this far to learn battle skills, the word ‘stupid’ was not an adjective that could describe her accurately.

However, this was not the only stupid thing that Tesna had done and everyone had gotten used to it. Meanwhile, the core of their clan named Dosrin was a member of their household whose Willpower had reached level three. Moreover, he was about to get married and everyone was busy planning this elegant and expensive wedding. Therefore, a normal person like Tesna without any natural endowments had been sidelined in her household long ago. Her father was incapable while her mother did not acknowledge her at all. If it was not for her older brother who took care of her, her share of the monthly allowance would have been taken away long ago.

On the second day, Garen walked over slowly from afar and stood beside Tesna to observe her. He watched her dig until she was dripping with fresh blood. Tesna glanced at him before digging even more desperately.

Among the two people, one of them looked on while the other dug. Neither of them opened their mouths to speak.

At noon, the black clouds lessened slightly, allowing faint sunlight to cascade down from the middle of the cloud layers.

A group of young girls who were gorgeously dressed walked over from afar and encircled their surroundings with some cash. They stood far away and looked at Garen and Tesna who was standing and digging respectively.

They clearly came to amuse themselves at this strange sight.

“Is that the combat master who told her to dig the ground? He doesn’t look too bad. It’s a shame that he’s crazy though.”

“When crazy meets insanity. Isn’t that a good thing? Two people who want to pass on the extinct battle skills. What a coincidence that it’s the most cliched scene right out of a novel. I think Tesna has definitely read too many novels.”

“Her fingers are going to be wrecked soon. Nonetheless, Tesna’s perseverance is not bad,” there were some people who were sure of their opinions of her.

“Perseverance? Can an insane person persevere?! I’m suspicious that this girl might not have pain receptors. I feel pain when I look at her so how could she endure it for so long? Previously, she practiced her battle skills desperately as if she was crazed as well. In the end, her body was almost wrecked by the training. If her older brother hadn’t discovered this, she would have died in an unknown place long ago.”

The group chatted and laughed. After observing for some time and sizing Garen up, they could not feel any Willpower from his body at all. Thus, they finally decided that this man was a conman who had tricked her. However, this conman still dared to stand here and watch her. It was highly likely that he was a conman with mental problems.

Crowd mentality was a shared trait among everybody. When they saw that an audience had gathered here, more people joined them quickly to watch the action here.

However, once the novelty had worn off and the weather grew colder, people gradually left when they felt that it was meaningless.

Currently, the bones in Tesna’s fingers were already frozen and frostbitten. She was numb to the pain but continued digging downwards continuously.

“Enough,” Garen finally opened his mouth.

“This pit is enough,” he said lightly.

“Enough?” Tesna was slightly shocked and stopped slowly. She looked at the pit in the ground that was filled with traces of blood and her own two hands that were already completely damaged. Perhaps they would need to be amputated?

This thought stirred in her mind. Would it be worth it? For the sake of battle skills.

However, her question was answered with unprecedented confidence. It was worth it!

This was the only path that allowed her to strengthen herself. It was her only hope as well. Those who had Appraisals and natural endowments would never understand her suffering.

“Now, jump inside and bury yourself there.”

Garen’s following words made her widen her eyes suddenly.

“Of course, you’ve passed the first test. This is the second one. Remember to leave your head out.”

Tesna glanced at Garen before looking at the pit in the ground. She had never expected that the second test would require her to bury herself alive.

Garen’s face was completely expressionless. He merely looked at her flatly.

“Unwilling? Then consider it as if I hadn’t said anything.”

“No,” Tesna jumped into the pit at once and started using her hands to bury herself in the surrounding soil endlessly.

Moments later, coupled with the heavy snowfall that cascaded downwards continuously, she quickly buried herself until her only her two arms were exposed outside. Once she extended her arms into the pit, she stopped moving completely and allowed the heavy snow to gradually bury her.

Soon, the members of her household realized that there were new changes once more. They ran over to observe the couple again.

When they realized that it was a new trick, these people started becoming lively instantly. They pointed from afar as if they were looking at a performing monkey in a circus. They chatted and laughed while eating some snacks that they brought from home.

Tesna was hungry and thirsty while her entire body was purple from the cold. The density of her blood flow had increased while both of her eyes were blinded. Her entire body was exhausted of all strength. She could only instinctively bite the snow beside her mouth and consume it. However, since the temperature of the oral cavity was too low, it took a long time for the snow to melt.

She felt like she might die soon.

However, Garen was still looking at her indifferently on the side while remaining above.

“What if he’s really just tricking me?” This overpowering thought escaped from Tesna’s mind.

“You can choose to give up anytime,” echoed Garen’s voice faintly.

Tesna opened and closed her mouth but could not make a single sound. She was silent. She would fall terribly sick even if she gave up and returned now. Whether or not she would survive was another unknown variable.

It had reached this stage…

“Will she die?” The laughter of the other young ladies who were watching from afar echoed endlessly. During this period which was also a time of war, the deaths of one or two people would not attract any attention at all.

The war made it difficult for Blackboard Region to maintain its basic order of society. Everyone could only rely on their own strength now.

Chapter 1093: Murderous Intent 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Once Tesna had completely buried herself in the freezing ground, Garen raised his head and looked at the heavy snow that was gradually falling from the sky.

“Soon…” His face was expressionless, making it impossible for anyone to guess what he was thinking. He merely stood on the side and quietly waited.

The sky darkened. Once the novelty had worn off, the people who came to watch the hubbub gradually left.

Garen slowly walked away as though he was not concerned about Tesna who was buried underground at all. A short while after he had left, Tesna’s older brother arrived and rushed over madly while trying to unearth the soil. However, his help was defiantly rejected by the weak Tesna.

Right after being dug out, she buried herself again.

Her older brother found it strange that someone who should have been extremely weak, actually possessed the strength to resist him now.

Garen had stopped bothering about the situation over there. Accepting disciples depended on two things. The first criteria was his own mood whilst the second one was whether or not Tesna possessed the qualifications.

Right now, before the Energy Tide exploded, he had to settle his old scores with the Seventh Divine Wind General from the last time.

While walking on the desolate block, Garen’s entire body unconsciously floated. However, no one had so much as noticed his silhouette.

His enormous Willpower had distorted the senses of everyone in his surroundings that could see him.

Garen flew in a perfectly straight manner in the direction of the Polar Region. Below him was Blackboard Region’s prosperous city, tinged with dejectedness. Flying cars would fly past him occasionally but none of the people above him realized that there was another figure soaring in mid-air among them.

Gazing at the enormous metropolis below him, Garen’s mind was gripped by a rush of emotions.

When the Energy Tide arrived, this place, Polar Region, Royal Region, and Maria Region and the other surrounding areas would collapse completely because of this annihilating energy.

This was a major historical event. The Energy Tide would appear naturally and no one could prevent it. Parts of the Red King would come into being while the components of the Forbidden Mech would become reality.

“Perhaps the White King’s subordinates are already hiding in this place?” Garen guessed mentally. “After all, the components of the Red King who is fated to stand beside the White King would not go undiscovered by others.”

He looked down at the endless stretches of city scenery that passed him from below. Perhaps the White King’s underlings were hiding in one of the deeper parts below.

Suddenly, an indistinct signal shot into the sky directly from the ground and was transferred to his mind. It seemed like the signal was released by someone close to him because it was tinged with veneration.

“Oh? I almost forgot that I had this chess piece here…” Garen said as he smiled faintly. He pressed his figure downwards and flew towards a city below him. At the center of the city, styled with yellow and white buildings, a woman with golden shoulder-length curly hair raised her head and blankly looked at the sky.

The woman was very pretty and had light red pupils and porcelain-smooth skin. Skincare during this era was simply too easy, which made it seemingly impossible to see ugly people. Even if their skin was not perfect, they would still be pretty.

“What’s wrong, Commander Inari?” A woman’s voice echoed behind her faintly.

“No… An important matter has suddenly come up. Could I ask you to leave for a while?” Inari reacted instantly and urged her in a somewhat frantic tone.

“… Alright. If that’s the case, we’ll take about this collaboration again when we have the chance,” The other woman left in a slightly dissatisfied manner. When the sound of the door opening and closing echoed behind her, only then did Inari exhale lightly. She then turned around to check if the other party had really left.

Suddenly, a hand extended behind her slowly before stroking her cheek gently.

“Long time no see, Commander Inari. Have you completed my mercenary mission?”

A male voice that spoke in a joking tone echoed behind her.

Inari’s body stiffened. Her Charm Mercenary Troop had disbanded long ago and she had rebuilt a new mercenary troop that was even bigger. Moreover, her current employer was not a normal person like the previous Nonosiva. Instead, he played a major role within the various territories. The source of all this was her own strength characteristics that had a sudden strange improvement. Her physical fitness had increased by three times instantly, allowing a great degree of elevation of her actual combat abilities. They were a level higher than her initial level, which was the key reason she was allowed to improve herself to the next grade so quickly.

“Nonosiva? My lord…?” She decided to add on the honorific title in the end. For unknown reasons, her body was trembling faintly as if she was afraid.

“What are you scared of?” Garen reached his hand out and pinched her face gently. This commander of the mercenary troops whom he had come into contact not long ago now looked somewhat attractive.

“No… It wasn’t my fault… You can’t blame me for the things that happened in that year. I did everything I could but it was useless!” Inari’s body shivered violently. As the host of a parasite, she was the only one who could faintly feel the true extent of Garen’s power through the main body.

The more she was able to sense his power, the stronger the fear in her heart grew.

“It’s none of my business… I tried to stop it but even Julie and the other girls died… I was the only one who escaped by sheer luck…” Inari’s body was slightly cold as she began defending herself continuously.

Garen felt faintly puzzled as he did not know what she was afraid of exactly.

He listened as Inari rambled on endlessly about how this was none of her business while the suspicions that were faintly tinged with worry in his heart grew stronger. He suddenly recalled that incident… Other than to absorb the Energy Tide, the main reason for his return this time, the most important reason nonetheless, was to personally confirm that incident…

“Everything that happened previously, tell me all of it,” he said in a low voice with a hint of Willpower suggestion and intimidation.

“Yes…”

Inari had a shocked expression on her face before her gaze instantly turned dull. Garen’s current suggestions were supported by his Non-falling Level Willpower while Inari’s grade was only of the Resonance New-Moon Level. Therefore, she could not resist him at all. She was instantly hypnotized.

“That year, during the process of the mission, I accidentally discovered that…”

Inari opened her mouth and spoke slowly. While she recounted the events slowly, Garen’s face remained expressionless but his gaze grew colder.

The events were actually extending in the direction that he was most unwilling to see…

“Who’s the person who left earlier?” Garen interrupted her before she had finished speaking.

“That was Britney,” answered Inari dully. “Let her come back.”

Inari did as she was told and began to take out her phone before alerting Britney who had left earlier.

A short while later, the sound of knocking could be heard from the room door again.

“Please come in,” Inari returned to her senses and broke free of Garen’s control. There was an expression of defeat on her face before she determinedly steadied her emotions and answered loudly.

Kachak.

“Mistress Quisman, if you don’t want to complete this business deal, I can find someone else! If you merely want to embarrass and tease me, then I…” Before she had finished speaking, another woman with similar golden-blonde long hair that was tied in a ponytail took large strides and walked in. The words stopped coming out of her mouth instantly when she saw Garen.

“You are?” She furrowed a delicate eyebrow.

“Britney?” Garen turned his head and considered this important person who had helped him previously before abandoning him in the end. This important person from the previous years did not undergo any major changes now. Her clothes were still simple and she wore an inexpensive looking accessory. However, the pearl bracelet that she wore on her wrist actually cost a few hundred thousand Universal Units.

Garen smiled. He was clearly just a minor character that year who was not worthy for Britney to remember.

“My name is Nonosiva Lin. I don’t know if Miss Britney still remembers this name?”

“Nonosiva Lin?” As a Willpower powerhouse, Britney’s memory was naturally powerful. “High-energy fuel powder?” She consciously recalled the business deal that she had profited from previously.

“Yes, that’s it,” Garen laughed.

“You’re still alive?!” Britney was slightly shocked. However, she had already sized up the current Garen and realized that his entire body did not possess the slightest hint of Willpower. It was obvious and likely that he had suffered heavy injuries that year which made it completely impossible for his Willpower to be restored. Her initially somewhat surprised expression returned to its normal state instantly.

“So you’re that student, Nono,” she brushed the strands of golden hair beside her cheeks gracefully. “Regarding the incident that happened to your father and mother that year, I truly regret that.”

“Why should you feel regretful for that?” Garen shook his head. “It doesn’t matter. I’m personally responsible for most of the things that happened in the past.”

“It’s good that you understand,” nodded Britney. If she had not seen Inari’s stance that indicated her intimate relationship with this person, Britney could not be bothered by a guy who had lost his Willpower completely. “Then Inari, Mistress Quisman, make a decision. This business is very important to me and you should know that.”

“The importance is relative,” Inari glanced at Garen before quickly standing in an elegant stance and replying. “However, my conditions have not changed. You should already know that I’ve already made a huge concession.”

Garen stood on the side quietly and watched the two women haggle. Finally, Inari reached an agreement because she was feeling impatient due to Garen’s presence. Britney instantly revealed a victorious smile and turned around while preparing to leave.

“That’s right, Lady Britney. You said earlier that you felt remorseful over the incident with my parents that year? I deserve the punishment for what I did but what does that have to do with my parents?” Garen opened his mouth and asked as Britney was about to leave.

Britney had just turned around, but her footsteps stopped suddenly. She turned back and looked at Garen suspiciously. Then, she glanced at Inari whose face was filled with dread.

“During the previous battle that caused the fall of the Black Flood Party Leader, your teacher and I were assigned to defend the battleship. However, we never expected that the abnormal energy would produce an earthquake. Issues had even occurred within the safest underground air defense facilities. This was something that we could not even begin to imagine. It was an unexpected accident,” she said as she furrowed her eyebrows.

“Therefore, I apologize for the death of your family members. However, frankly speaking, this was not our fault,” said Britney while furrowing her eyebrows. “We did everything we had to do.”

Garen’s expression was completely dazed.

Britney’s last sentence instantly and finally exposed the suspicions that were in his heart all this while. The things that Britney said after that could not be heard clearly by him anymore. That final sentence about the death of his family… This simple string of words repeated endlessly in his brain like the constant violent rumble of an echo in a canyon.

Britney’s eyebrows were knitted even closer together now. She stared quietly at Nonosiva Lin who appeared taken aback. She had always felt that something was slightly amiss with this person.

“I remember now. When your incident caused a stir within the region last time, the previous Black Flood Party prodigy was encircled before he went missing and his whereabouts became unknown. After that, the verdict was reversed when it was proven that you were encircled and wrongly accused by an undiscovered traitor,” she said indifferently. “Alright, I’ll be leaving first if that’s all.”

Britney did not wish to waste her time on an unimportant individual. The previous skills had lost their novelty long ago while the military no longer limited the high-energy fuel powder. The market was much bigger than before and high-level skills like these were everywhere now. The military had lifted the restriction for maximum productive forces. The current issue that they were facing now did not involve skills, but instead was the lack of resources.

The sound of Britney leaving roused Garen instantly.

His expression was calm but the strange emotion that glimmered in his eyes clearly showed that he was not as relaxed as his face might have suggested.

“Would it have been possible for that earthquake to keep the Genetic Organization in check?” He opened his mouth suddenly and spoke in a low voice.

Inari nodded frantically like a little bird that was pecking at rice. She was too afraid to show a hint of opposing him. She was perhaps the only person in the entire Blackboard Region who clearly knew the intimidation of the man who was before her eyes.

Chapter 1094: Murderous Intent 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Near Blackboard Region was another similar graveyard. A group of people dressed in luxurious black clothes was standing in front of a few burial grounds.

Regardless if they were men or women, the entire group were dressed in clothes that were fully black. A few women in the group wore black gauze hats to indicate that they were mourning. Clearly, there had been deaths in their families.

One of the women who had golden curly hair also had beautiful features that even the black gauze hat could not hide. She also had a seductive and curvaceous figure that would occasionally cause her surrounding subordinates to secretly cast their gazes at her.

Garen stood in front of the graveyard and allowed his Willpower to seep underground instantly. He could immediately detect that there were three badly rotted corpses buried deep underground. Two of them were a middle-aged man and woman respectively, while the last skeleton belonged to a young girl.

As his Willpower wrapped them, three thin strands of hair that belonged to each of these people slowly bore through the soil. The hairs were still undamaged and did not seem to have any signs of decay.

After crouching down, Garen reached his hand out and grabbed the three strands of hair. At the same time, he plucked a strand of his own hair and passed it to the two laboratory staff in black clothes behind him.

Various expensive testing equipment had already been set up on the ground behind him. A few specialized individuals used gloves to separate the hairs into four different containers. Next, they began the delicate gene examination procedure.

Within ten short minutes, the results of the test were released.

“Mistress, My Lord,” said the laboratory staff quietly. “From the results of the genetic correspondence degree, the three corpses that were buried here really belonged to your late relatives. There’s no doubt about it.”

“Are you sure?”

It seemed as if the air had suddenly become much colder.

The laboratory staff felt slight indescribable chills in his heart. However, since he was completely unable to decipher them clearly, he merely nodded his head firmly.

“I’m very sure. Any laboratory organization would presumably give you these results easily. There are no uncertainties at all.”

The chilly winds grew colder.

Garen’s expression became colder. Although he was not emotionally attached to the birth parents of this physical body, he had previously promised Nonosiva that he would take care of them. However, he was unable to do it now.

He waved his hand. “All of you can leave first.”

Inari nodded and quietly left with the other laboratory staff. It was obvious that Garen was in an extremely gloomy mood.

Garen took a white, palm-sized computer-like thing. This was Scarlet Snow Sect’s most advanced communication device.

He dialed a number that he had memorized from constant practice before quickly turning off the location and video functions here.

A little while later, he received a response from the other side quickly.

“Is it Garen? Why is your side pitch black? I can’t see anything,” Celine’s voice echoed from the video. She still resembled her previous self with her short green hair and her temperament that hinted of indifference from the way the corner of her mouth was raised slightly. She was dressed in some kind of service-type clothing that was fully white and looked abnormally British-styled.

“My place has been sealed suddenly and the signal here isn’t so good,” Garen answered simply. “How have you been lately? Still good?”

“Still alright. My strength has increased now. However, I still feel that it isn’t so smooth in certain places. Do you still have any of the ores that you gave me previously? The dark red metal ores,” Celine had always been this straightforward with Garen.

“Of course I do. Just send me and tell me how much you need,” Garen laughed. On the surface, he sounded as if he was speaking gently. However, a bone-chilling coldness was seeping through the depths of his gaze. “That’s right, how are my mother and the rest? They’re still well, right? I haven’t returned to see them in so many years and now that I think about it, I haven’t been filial at all. I’m planning to return and visit them. Send me their full address.”

An indifferent look appeared on Celine’s face instantly.

“They just moved houses recently and might not have a confirmed addressed for now. If you’re coming here, it’s best if you inform me first. The Central Star Region isn’t the best place to pass through. I can get you a pass through my teacher’s connections. However, since you’re an Energy Machinist now, this should be easily done. Can you get out of your sealed Stargate now?”

“I can get out because I have a way,” answered Garen while smiling.

“That’s right, your mother wanted to speak to you. You should speak to her yourself. I’ll transfer you and connect you to the call,” a mysterious smile appeared on Celine’s face suddenly before the screen snapped and shut off. It was quickly switched to another place with a little garden in the background.

His mother, Amy Lamda’s warm face appeared in the center of the screen.

“Is that Nono?”

“Yes, it’s me, Mother. Are my younger sister and Father still alright? I’m planning to come home and visit after some time,” replied Garen’s voice in a gentler tone.

“There’s no need. You’re the backbone of our household and your career is important. We’ve been living well so you don’t have to worry about us. However, we haven’t heard from your younger brother all this while. If you hear any news about him soon, remember to inform us immediately. Just knowing that he’s still alive is enough.”

His mother spoke softly and occasionally wiped the tears from her eyes.

Garen chatted to his mother about some of their household matters while listening to her constant compliments about Celine.

While listening to his mother enquire about his well-being through the video, Garen’s consciousness was focused on his mother’s badly rotten corpse below his feet.

An indescribable chill rose from the bottom of Garen’s heart suddenly.

A person who died more than three years ago was actually still chatting and smiling at him through the screen?

In the end, who was real…?

In order to repay Celine’s for her sentiments and for taking care of his family, Garen constantly sent the available resources in his possession to her. These items had traveled to and fro and he was unsure of how many things he had sent. Every time he watched the video calls of his family members assuring him of their safety, he felt that he had treated Nonosiva properly. However, he had never gotten deeper into the matter to get any other probable answers.

“Alright, I still have matters to attend to here. We’ll talk again soon,” after conversing with his ‘mother’ for a while, Garen could not suppress the murderous intent in his heart and disconnected the phone call quickly.

“In the end, I never acknowledged them as my family from the bottom of my heart. This is how this ending has occurred,” Garen knew the source of this in his heart.

Only now did he recall that Celine had almost given up all of her femininity in her sole pursuit of power. She had created a baseline that even he could not see clearly. Despite their deep sentiments throughout the years, had she merely been helping herself without caring about anything else?

The White King’s pawns were still hiding in this region. As the White King who could see the line of destiny and would be able to challenge the Red King in the future, would he allow the events to occur without hesitating at all? This probability could not be imagined at all.

When the Energy Tide appeared, the secret pieces would be present as well. This was because the Red King’s Forbidden components would truly appear when the Energy Tide appeared.

Without suppressing the murderous intent in his heart any longer, Garen turned around and glanced at Inari before his silhouette disappeared in the air instantly. Immediately, everyone could only feel a cold wind soaring into the sky before it dashed away and flew into the distance.

******************

Polar Region — Titan City

Garen floated in the sky quietly. He looked down at the bustling white city.

Titan City, the area with the highest concentration of nobles within Polar Region was also currently the largest and strongest force in the area where White Light was located. Although it was not a metropolis, it was still the most prosperous city in Polar Region. Especially after more than half of Black Flood Party was destroyed, the initial Polar Region surrendered after they were defeated. They were currently already assigned to the White Light Organization as their base.

Numerous Spaceships of different sizes were floating around in the sky above the city while endless streams of cars came and left on the ground. Some Mech groups that were circulating around and patrolling the entire city could be seen occasionally.

The entire Titan City resembled the most accurate precision instrument. It was unusually complicated and magnificent and possessed an atmosphere that was completely different from Blackboard Region’s desolate decadence.

Garen floated in mid-air and extended his hand slowly as if his palm was about to grasp the entire city.

“All creation cannot escape from their destined deaths in the end,” he murmured as the black clouds in the sky circled faster. Countless floating clouds surged frantically while an uncountable amount of cold white gas filled the air and turned into a terrifyingly gigantic palm.

The gigantic hand pressed down slowly towards the sky above Titan City.

“Which senior’s esteemed arrives in my Titan City! I’m White Shark, the City Master. On behalf of Lord Divine Light of Polar Region, I ask you to kindly stop the flames of your fury.” A white Mech with a shark’s head rose into the sky. An imposing Inherited Level air could be felt throughout its entire body. There was a light green crystal that was clearly embedded in the center of its chest. It was obviously of the same style as the previous White Light Mech.

The Energy Fields throughout this Mech’s entire body was condensed in one area. It transformed into a seemingly substantial great white shark that charged into the sky towards the gigantic hand.

“I kindly ask my senior to show mercy!!” yelled the City Master furiously.

Terrible chaos had already appeared throughout the city below them. An abundance of Spaceships and cars were blocked up. Traffic was a mess. Numerous people began to lose their minds while panicking, causing the chaos to worsen. Large crowds of people were squeezed together in the city. Within a few short moments, situations that depicted the downfall of the area appeared within the order of the city.

He looked at the gigantic metropolis below him quietly.

Garen closed both of his eyes.

“Faded… Creation…”

He reached his hand out and clenched it gently.

“Freeze History.”

Bang!!

The enormous hand that was made up of chills suddenly dispersed and turned into numerous shrouds of white gas that dived downwards.

The abundant chills resembled raindrops that poured down directly. Everything they touched was quickly covered in a light layer of white frost before completely turning into solid ice.

The white chills that filled the sky like rain brushed past the side of the Shark Mech’s body. It was useless no matter how much it struggled.

Ahh!!!!

The Shark Mech charged at Garen frantically. He used both of his hands to take out a gigantic sickle that was made by being folded. It drew a crescent-like white light in mid-air.

Clang!

The gigantic sickle that was over ten meters long was blocked by a single index finger that Garen held up. His terrifying momentum made it seem as if he appeared out of thin air before disappearing. It did not adhere to the laws of physics at all.

“H… How!!”

As countless frozen layers extended towards the Shark Mech’s body from the sickle quickly, his last words escaped from his mouth after his final struggle. His entire body was completely frozen into an ice block before it fell down from the high altitude.

“Within three days, give me the traitors of Black Flood Party. Just like this city, those who disobey orders will fall into eternal sleep,” Garen’s silhouette became blurry within the high altitude. However, his low but clear voice was transmitted across the screens of the monitoring forces without any omissions.

Crack!

After some distortions, Garen disappeared in mid-air. The previously prosperous city did not even have a moment to reflect before it was completely frozen in ice.

*******************

The faraway capital of the Polar Region.

Inside an open and spacious gloomy meeting room.

The leaders who were seated at a round table looked at the city that was completely frozen on screen silently.

Both eyes of the white-haired man who sat at the host’s seat were gloomy while all ten of his fingers were interlaced on the table. He wore a black suit that was rimmed with silver stripes.

“A degree of this sort…” He opened his mouth slowly while his hoarse voice escaped.

Chapter 1095: Exact Information 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I need all of you to give me an emergency plan,” said the man who was seated at the host’s seat in a low voice. “That was a city. Titan City was one of our most important bases! We can’t let it just freeze and fall into such a situation!”

This man was the First Elder of the previous White Light Organization and the person who destroyed Blackboard Region in revenge. He had attacked Polar Region and caused its downfall before becoming the newly appointed leader there.

Those present were not Polar Region’s original imperial kinsmen or great nobles. Instead, they were this man’s previous underlings and a few of Black Flood Party’s subordinates that defected over.

Those from Black Flood Party were currently the most embarrassed ones here. The other people cast their gazes towards the both of them, consciously and unconsciously.

“Ladies and gentlemen of Black Flood Party, tell me, how did this person come after all?” said one of the imperial members of Polar Region calmly. “An individual with powers like that would already be considered as a Non-falling Level powerhouse. I wouldn’t believe it if all of you did not know how a powerhouse of this degree was provoked.”

“Indeed, even if First Elder wanted to protect you, he would first need to know the entire process clearly,” said another person while smiling and narrowing his eyes. “That was a Non-falling Level, a powerhouse that was on par with the Black Flood Party Master from those days!”

The gazes of all the elders were focused on those from Black Flood Party.

The face of the Fourth Divine Wind General who acted as a representative turned cold and stern as he sat up straighter in his seat but did not speak. Beside him was a young woman who had long red hair.

The silence of Black Flood Party allowed the others to rejoice in their misfortune.

“Alright, alright. We’ll discuss this matter further. What’s going on?” The gaze of the man who was also the leader fell on the Fourth Divine Wind General.

The Divine Wind General cleared his throat and looked at his surroundings while his face remained expressionless.

“Respected Lord Divine Light, we’ve never seen this person before and we would never dare to lie to you about this matter,” The Fourth Divine Wind General could ignore the others but would naturally not treat his own leader the same way. He stood up and answered him respectfully.

“It would be impossible for a Non-falling Level powerhouse to just appear suddenly, right?” Divine Light was faintly annoyed.

“As I see it, this isn’t the time to debate the origins of this person. Instead, we should be defending the reputation of our Polar Region. If a larger region was frightened into submission by a terrorist that appeared suddenly, the other regions would laugh at them as if they were a joke!” said one of the old people dejectedly.

“We must release a letter to our allies about the terrorist attack immediately! Inform the other regions to unite with us as allies as well! Titan City was a key trade city that we used to import Star Core fragments! We will not tolerate losing it!” said someone resolutely.

After a temporary period of shock, everyone realized that the person was actually very aggressive. He did not care about the millions of people who died within the entire city. They could simply treat him as the biggest mutated organism threat and handle him in that manner before releasing an urgent announcement to all of the powerhouses within the other regions of the alliance.

“As a single person, even if he becomes any stronger, could he be stronger than all of us?” sneered one of the leaders.

“Although a single Non-falling Level is not enough to scare us, I personally cannot set out easily. Looks like I can only trouble all of you now.”

Once Divine Light had gotten his great revenge against Blackboard Region, his mental state had calmed down greatly. He was rather unperturbed now.

“I’m guessing that this person probably took the opportunity that arose because of the weather changes. He could only increase his strength when his frost abilities and powers increased. In reality, his strength is probably not this powerful. After all, if it was really strong enough, he would have emerged long ago instead of purposely waiting until now,” said one of the elders calmly.

“That’s reasonable.”

“Then move out twelve Great Light Mechs to prevent a diversion from occurring. I’ll oversee the metropolis while the rest of you can go straight to Egret together,” Divine Light took a pure white disc out and passed it to one of the leaders who was standing up.

“This disc contains half of my power within a single move. I’ll pass it to you to handle it,” as the peak Non-falling Level powerhouse, Divine Light had previously attacked and killed two Non-falling Levels including the Black Flood Party Master and Blackboard Academy’s dean. As for Non-falling Levels who had yet to reach their limits, he was naturally, completely unconcerned about them.

“At the same time, move upwards towards the headquarters and inquire about the information regarding that man,” the headquarters that he was talking about referred to the information headquarters of the artificial intelligence manufacturing alliance between Maria Region and Royal Region. Various information from all aspects was collected there.

“Don’t worry, leave it to us,” the young person who had taken the disc opened his mouth and exposed his white teeth.

************************

If the power of the Non-falling Level separated itself and coordinated with the snowflakes and cold air in the sky, it would form a terrifying ending that would affect people greatly.

Titan City was frozen and the solid ice there could not be broken. If it was struck or broken, the people inside would crack completely along with the ice.

Garen had vented briefly to slightly relieve the murderous intent in his heart. He was currently in the radiation zone between Polar Region and Blackboard Region. He was waiting on an overgrown grassy plain.

The Seventh Ruins from earlier that were both mysterious and strange were far away in front of him. He had entered previously and was almost unable to exit.

While looking at it from afar, the Seventh Ruins was still the same as before. They were terribly abandoned and dilapidated while the insides were filled with stage props and what seemed like factory machinery that were jumbled together. An indescribably uncomfortable feeling wafted in the air.

Garen did not appear but was instead concealing himself in the air. He used optics to hide his body and isolation devices that were made of qi wave forces to shroud himself completely. He had specially prepared these things when he came back this time in order to wait for the moment when Clint and the others would return.

“Master, Bamente has been found. Should I take you there immediately?” Turing’s voice echoed beside him.

“Let’s go.”

Garen threw a little black ball out of his hand in passing and allowed it to fall on the floor freely and sink into the soil on the ground. It burrowed into the deepest part of the soil on its own.

Only then did he turn around and leave.

Celine had lied to him. Bamente had attempted to assassinate him previously but was inflicted with heavy injuries by the Nine-Headed Dragon’s soul that rebounded automatically. He definitely needed to get his revenge.

It was fortunate that the matters here were preparing to be completed. The free time that he had now was coincidentally enough for him to settle all of his previous scores.

“There’s probably some time before the explosion of the Energy Tide anyway..?”

A faint blue light appeared in both of Garen’s eyes.

He would not go and meet Celine for now. He needed to wait until her address was fully determined before he could deal with her. When he thought about it now, she was probably the one who had taken away all of his previous resources.

Throughout the numerous worlds he had experienced consecutively, she was the best liar he had ever seen.

While following Turing’s directions, Garen passed through the radiation zone quickly and silently entered the protective Light Screen to return to Blackboard Region.

He flew towards the mountainous area in the open country with ease. A large white house that was built on the top of the mountain appeared within his field of vision quickly.

There were many guards placed around the house. They held firearms and wore Miniature Mechs. They looked like they performed their garrison duties strictly.

Garen attracted their attention instantly when he flew closer. It seemed like they had detected him by using certain devices. However, it was important to note that Garen was already using the most advanced devices to conceal himself.

************

Within a garden in the interior of a big house, Bamente was currently following a woman from behind with an expression of flattery on his face. He was talking about something while smiling.

The woman’s figure-hugging black dress revealed her beautiful figure. Both of her eyes were elegant and shaped like almonds. She was a rare beauty.

“You can relax. The materials that I promised you will be sent as soon as possible. However, the medicinal liquid that you blended must be handed over on time as well.”

“Of course, of course. Milady’s personal arrival is an honor for my humble self, Bamente. To be able to guide milady and take milady sightseeing around Blackboard Region is a great opportunity that many people could not even dream of,” replied Bamente while smiling happily.

“It’s good that you’re aware of that. If you treat me well, you will reap the benefits; if you treat me badly, you already know the conclusion of that,” sneered the woman.

“Understood, understood,” Bamente answered frantically. “The current Mech competition between the Alliance of the Three Territories…” Before he could finish speaking, he suddenly felt an abnormal shroud of qi that penetrated the defensive layer of his house before shooting directly towards the two people.

Suddenly, he sensed a deep threat that resembled an extremely terrifying and earth-shattering murderous intent that was surging towards himself violently.

Within his field of vision, a ray of white light appeared in the faraway sky instantly before it charged directly at him.

Shh… The white light produced sharp whistling noises that caused intense pain throughout his eardrums.

However, he had no time to think now. He jerked his hand quickly and threw out two machine boxes before two ferocious black beasts pounced towards the white light from the inside.

Roar!!

The species of these two beasts could not be determined clearly. The white light penetrated them easily moments after they pounced forward. The speed of the white light did not decelerate and charged directly towards Bamente.

Garen remained within the white light with a calm expression on his face. To his current self, killing a mere Biochemist like Bamente was as simple as breathing. His counterattacks were weaker than paper and without having to break it on his own, they collapsed naturally after being suppressed by the Energy Field around his body.

“Save me!!” Bamente yelled loudly with a defeated look on his face.

“How dare you!!” The sound of a woman’s voice that was tinged with anger echoed beside his body. Simultaneously, a dark red steel wheel that was one step faster than sound and had sharp saw-like edges attempted to directly slice Garen’s neck instantly.

Garen simply extended his fingertips towards the wheel.

Boom!!!!

Countless rays of red light spewed around before the entire house and garden were instantly shrouded in violent red. All the flowers and plants wilted rapidly before the red light attacked and tainted the Miniature Mechs who had entered the house. It immediately flung these people out brutally before they were corroded by the red light in mid-air until not a single sound was left.

“Eh?” Garen exclaimed softly and realized once again that he had already landed gently on the top of the enclosing wall. He looked down at the woman with the cold face below him and Bamente who was hiding behind her.

When he extended his hand and touched the wheel, a mysterious force attempted to teleport him to another area. Fortunately, he had controlled the forces to evade this transference and float away gently to land on top of the nearby enclosing wall.

“Somewhat interesting,” his gaze stared at the red wheel in the woman’s hand while his interest towards the other party was aroused.

“You dare attack your Princess’s servant. Bearers!! Take this fellow who forced his way in and disturbed the interest of the palace.”

Their surroundings were completely silent while Garen looked at this woman curiously.

“Your Vitality is very interesting,” he stroked his chin while his interest in her increased. “Initially, I merely came here to settle some minor matters. I never expected to gain surprise rewards as well. Not bad, not bad…”

His voice was still echoing in the sky when Garen’s physical body had already turned into white light that charged towards both of them immediately.

Chapter 1096: Exact Information 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Protect the princess!!”

Numerous hoarse and exhausted voices could be heard in the dark.

A crashing noise could be heard within the interior of the house when a figure broke the door down and exited. It produced great momentum that violently punched Garen who was in mid-air. This incident was purely produced by a strength that had reached its limit and was not mixed with other impurities.

Clang!!

Garen simply touched its fist before it was instantly sent flying backward as if it was hit by a bomb. It exploded into a pool of blood before he had even landed on the ground.

“He’s an Energy Machinist!! Stop him!”

“Red Net!!” An elderly voice echoed throughout the sky.

Layers of complicated red Energy Barriers appeared between the woman and Garen out of thin air.

Garen extended his hand as if he could not see the barrier at all. There was a humming noise before more than ten layers of these barriers were destroyed instantly as if they were merely bundles of paper!

Garen’s right hand penetrated them before he clawed at the woman’s neck.

At this moment, a red laser that descended from the sky fell down suddenly.

Shh!!!

The laser that was as large as a column instantly illuminated the entire night sky completely. It was a terrifying destruction beam that was shot out at the base of an enormous black Battleship. It was an energy bomb that was specially used to attack enemy Battleships!! Apparently, someone was using it as a weapon to attack human enemies now. Its degree of precision was simply astonishing!

The light beam that connected the sky to the earth descended on the ground before everything was completely covered in crimson light.

It happened the moment the light beam landed on the ground.

There was a dull thunderous noise before a red laser that was an even scarier light beam rose into the sky and struck the black Battleship violently.

It seemed as though the middle section of the Battleship was struck by a gigantic red rod firmly. It was hit lightly at first before a sudden explosion followed and turned it into countless fragments that glided before violently smashing against the ground.

Garen discarded the ice mirror in his hand.

“Tch tch, how dangerous. It almost hit me…”

He seized the woman’s neck with one hand and simply flung her as if she was nothing more than a light item. He threw her in the opposite direction. While looking at the enormous black Battleship that was quickly falling, many people on it were jumping off and escaping frantically. They resembled parachutes that were descending from the sky.

“Young man! Do you know the honorable position of the person whom you are holding hostage now?” An elderly man with a red beard appeared before Garen out of thin air. He stood on the ruins in his black clothes that gave off a mysterious air.

“If you dare touch a single fine hair on my body, I will slaughter your entire family!!” cursed the woman in his hands venomously like a caught beast that was furious.

Boom!!!

A shroud of substantial-like chills floated beside Garen’s body. It was actually Turing, a large and fierce Two-Headed Wolf who was currently rushing one step behind him. The terrifying Non-falling Light around his entire body covered the entire courtyard. The old man was about to open his mouth and speak but was instantly suppressed by a heavy pressure that made it difficult for him to breathe. He could not make even a single sound. His face became extremely contorted instantly.

“My Lord, these people actually dared to threaten your unparalleled holy self. You should just let your subordinates eat them so that they can be turned into nutrients for the earth,” said Turing while complimenting him loudly. He stared at the woman in Garen’s hands with a gaze of unimaginable greed and desire. She seemed like an unusual delicacy that had attracted him the most.

“We’re members of the Crimson Court! As a Non-falling Level powerhouse, Your Highness should know this name, right?!” The old man exerted all of his strength but could barely make a few noises. “Please acknowledge us on behalf of the reputation of the Red Emperor…”

“Let him kill me because my father will avenge me! Let him kill me!” The woman in black roared loudly. “He actually dared to put this imperial court in such a difficult position…!”

“Crimson Court?” Garen’s eyebrows were knitted together tightly. He realized the origins of the other party immediately. “All of you are Biochemists?” He recalled the identity of the other person instantly. Crimson Court was the single largest Biochemist organization. Since Bamente was a Biochemist, it was normal for him to establish connections with these people.

He looked at Bamente who was at the side who had collapsed on the ground from fear. He had a terribly scared expression on his face while small parts of both of his legs were burnt and damaged by the red laser that descended from the sky earlier. He could not even stand properly.

“How interesting… Even Biochemists decided to join this grand meeting, huh?” A strange smile appeared on Garen’s face.

Crimson Court was a force that would be recaptured by Clint sometime in the future. Nonetheless, he never expected to actually encounter it beforehand. The princess in his hands right now would probably become the queen next time after becoming Clint’s accidental wife in the future. However, she would become much more mature then, unlike her current self who was still not wise yet.

“In that case, this makes it very difficult for me…”

In order to avoid influencing major forces, despite being prepared to kill this woman originally, Garen realized that it was seemingly not permissible now. This was the wife of the future Red King and it would be bad if the major forces of history were affected if she was killed.

The princess in his hands continued to curse loudly. Various unpleasant words melded with the noises. Her Vitality made her immune from the effects of all energy-type suppressions. Only substantial physical attacks could be used against her.

Her Vitality was clearly unnatural. Instead, it was adjusted by the Biochemists on their own.

“If I can’t kill her, then…”

Bang!!

Garen lifted the princess in his hands before smashing her against the ground violently.

Cement cracked and sputtered about while large amounts of rocks were smashed until they were sent flying in all four directions.

Bang bang bang!!

Again and again, Garen dragged the princess and smashed her against the places that were especially solid in a series of frenzied collisions.

The courtyard that was initially terribly damaged by the red light’s attacks finally collapsed after being smashed completely now.

The enclosing wall broke and collapsed before the ground was filled with potholes.

“I swear!! Swear…!” Bang!!

“I will definitely…!!” Bang!!

“Kill…” Bang!!

“You…!” Bang!!!

“Ahh!!!!” Boom!!!

Countless broken stones and soil whooped down like raindrops that sprinkled around. The old man clenched his fist in pain but was suppressed by the Non-falling Light that made him unable to move at all. He could only stare at Garen who was torturing the princess mercilessly.

The noises ceased abruptly.

Everything became completely quiet.

The princess’s neck was twisted towards one side and no one knew if she were still alive or not.

Nonetheless, Garen felt as if his body and mind were truly more relaxed now. He lifted the princess in his hands like a broken rag doll and walked before Bamente who was completely dazed and paralyzed on the floor in fright.

“You’re… the one from that day?!!” Bamente finally recognized Garen. He pointed a finger at him while his voice was already stammering, making him unable to speak clearly.

“You’ve finally recognized me,” Garen smiled. “I came to settle our previous matters.”

The pupils in Bamente’s eyes shrunk.

“That… That has nothing to do with me… I was merely doing a business deal with them. It had nothing to do with me!! It was Ice Dragon! It was him! It was Fila!! They were the ones who made a deal with me and told me to kill you! No…! No! Don’t kill me!!! Don’t!!”

Crack!

Garen steppes on his chest with one foot and broke it immediately. It was direct and efficient.

“No… It wasn’t my… fault…!” Bamente widened his eyes and died with everlasting regret. His head was slanted towards one side before he was finally unable to speak anymore.

“Thus, another one ends,” Garen exhaled. He recalled his own state when this man had plotted against him in the hospital previously. Fila… Seventh Divine Wind General!

These two people were the true ringleaders.

“Let’s go, Turing.”

He turned around and walked towards the outside. The Two-Headed Werewolf responded quietly in a somewhat unhappy tone but followed behind Garen nonetheless.

“That’s right, I’ll return this to you,” Garen suddenly remembered the person that he was still carrying in his arms. He simply threw her at the old man. “You don’t have to thank me.”

The old man caught the princess frantically before checking her briefly. Although she was not in life-threatening danger, her entire body was simply too horrible to look at. The old man was furious to the point where he nearly spat out blood when he saw Garen whose back was facing him in a completely defenseless manner. He wanted to attack him instinctively but each movement caused him to spit out fresh blood instantly.

“I…” He felt as if his internal organs were being sliced by blades as the aches were difficult to endure. It was clear that he had unknowingly fallen victim to Garen’s plot during the confrontation earlier.

“Your Highness! The misdeeds of this day will surely be avenged in the future! State your name if you dare!” he yelled loudly while exerting all of his strength.

No one replied him. Garen had teleported away the moment he exited because he could not be bothered with this man’s nonsense. He was merely an Inherited Level.

******************

The snowfall from the sky was getting heavier now.

Some places were already covered in thick layers of snow. While walking on the ground, there were places that were deep enough to make people sink into knee-deep snow in one step.

Garen and Turing stood on the cliff at the peak of the mountain range. They looked down at the enormous white city in depression. This city was slightly larger than Titan City. Fila and the Seventh Divine Wind General stayed here in Polar City, the capital of Polar Region after they deserted.

“There are Non-falling Level powerhouses here…” Garen gasped in admiration. “It’s also the place where the Mother Planet’s highest leveled forces can be found.”

Fila and the Seventh Divine Wind General were inside this place.

When he recalled the miserable condition he had suffered when the Willpower throughout his entire body was sealed that year, if the Sixth Divine Wind General had not saved him, he would probably have been destroyed instantly.

“I cannot wait to return the great present that you gave me that year…” Garen glanced at the vast city below him. His gaze was calm but no one knew what he was thinking about.

“My friend arrived at my Polar Region but did not inform me, the master. Is this a lack of courtesy?” Suddenly, a calm male voice echoed behind Garen.

Garen turned his head and saw a person who was walking forward slowly. However, his figure seemed as if it had leaped across a large distance in a split second. He was able to appear a few meters in front of him quickly from a place that was a hundred meters further previously.

Mysterious power and influence wafted throughout this person’s entire body. His Non-falling Light was as spotlessly white as jade. It felt completely different from Garen’s whiteness that seeped with hints of gloominess.

While looking at the forces of this person’s body, he noticed that he was a Non-falling Level too. As a Non-falling Level, he could already fuse his Exclusive Mech with parts of his own body. He could even split up and match his Mech once again if he was strong enough to form something like spatial equipment that could fuse with his own body completely.

His appearance looked similar to that of a normal person. However, he possessed terrifying power in reality.

“Who are you?” The moment Garen turned around, he suddenly felt the energy of the blood bead that remained inside his body jumping violently.

The moment the energy started jumping, the expression on the other party’s face changed radically while he looked at him in slight disbelief.

“I never thought that…” All of the Non-falling Light throughout the man’s body shrunk suddenly before he took a non-defensive stance strangely.

He waved his hand and sprinkled a large amount of radiance before completely sealing their entire surroundings.

Pop.

This Non-falling Level City Master who was also Polar Region’s current controller had actually knelt down on one knee before Garen!

“Lord Emissary has graced us with his presence personally but I was unable to respectfully welcome him in the first moment! May you pardon my offenses!!” he said loudly and respectfully, in fear and trepidation.

“Emissary?” Garen’s mind was slightly shocked.

His other identity was of the Bodysnatcher Jeros. Meanwhile, in the current Polar Region, the great leader of the previous White Light terrorist organization was actually referring to him as his lord.

Within an instant, all of the connections linked together.

“Carthage… Chinande… These are truly great efforts…” While looking at Divine Light who was kneeling on a single knee before him, Garen smiled coldly in his heart.

Chapter 1097: Clash 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

If Garen’s memory served him right, the White Light Organization had been swept off the Blackboard Region many years ago. He didn’t expect their leader to be part of Carthage’s future plan.

Judging from the looks of it, the reason the White Light was looking for Forbidden Mech’s parts was clearly aimed towards Red Moon.

“The White Light doesn’t feel like an organization that has just been formed. It’s set to target Red Moon the moment they appear. Perhaps they’ve investigated Red Moon’s part from the very beginning…” Garen linked the whole situation in an instant.

He looked at Divine Light who had one knee on the ground as he pondered how long White King had been planning all of these since everything had been set up a long time ago.

Now that he thought about it, the draughtsman who allied with the Red Moon the Red King was most likely this man in front of him…

“Cut the nonsense. I want to meet the people who betrayed the Black Flood Party back in the days. Since you’ve participated in this plan, I may spare your lives if you hand all of them over to me,” Garen replied calmly.

Sweat started to appear on Divine Light’s head, who was still kneeling down with one knee.

“The Headquarter is the one who gives me everything I have now so it’s natural that I only listen to the Lord Emissary. However…”

“However?”

Divine Light raised his head. “However, may Lord Emissary tell me your respected name? So that I can inform Lord Puppeteer with minimal issue.”

The Puppeteer?

Garen was offended as he had become an insider by following Carthage. However, what about the Puppeteer? It is very possible that he is in charge of this mother planet or perhaps it is just Carthage of the Scarlet Snow Sect’s identity.

“My name is Jeros and are you oppressing me by using the Puppeteer’s name?!” Before Garen could react, Turing appeared beside Garen and released the Non-falling Light onto Divine Light.

“I do not dare…” Divine Light immediately lowered his head.

Garen started to lose his patience as the amount of time wasted had exceeded his expectation.

“I’ll give you ten minutes. You shall perish if you don’t hand over your men,” he set his gaze onto the Polar Region. From where he stood, the whole city was within his view.

“Lord, are you not afraid of ruining the Headquarter’s plan?” Divine Light gritted his teeth as he spoke with his head down.

“Plan?”

Garen glared at him.

Pew!!

A line of white gas was shot directly towards the Divine Light’s face.

Divine Light reached out his hand as he attempted to grab it by instantly gathering a huge amount of Willpower on his palm. However, the white gas unexpectedly took a turn and winded across his palm and went directly towards the back of his head.

Clang!!

A big, white, metal bell shape appeared and surrounded Divine Light.

A high-intensity noise reverberated as the white gas clashed onto the bell and cracks could be seen propagating on the surface of the white bell.

“Lord Emissary!” He shouted anxiously. “Aren’t you scared of the Puppeteer questioning you?!” He was shocked and angry as he didn’t expect Garen to attack at all.

He then squeezed a small capsule with his finger.

An invisible force imploded the space dimension was connected to another region which was very far away.

Garen didn’t seem to realize it as he stared calmly at the man in front of him.

“Question me? I, Jeros, have no need to explain to anybody…”

He reached out his hand and covered a huge distance at lightning speed as he grabbed onto Divine Light’s head.

Ahh!!

Divine Light struggled as their Non-falling Light Energy Field clashed and abraded against each other. As a huge amount of extremely cold white gas propagated towards Divine Light from Garen’s hand, Divine Light’s struggle reduced gradually as he started to freeze by the absolute coolness.

Sizzle…

A huge amount of chill started to engulf Divine Light’s body except for his head.

They were both Non-Falling Level but the instantaneous strength of the Energy Field from the Scarlet Snow’s Ice Armor was Level Eight. Divine Light was completely defenseless when he faced against the absolute chill that was one level above him.

Layers of silver and white metal sheets started to appear on his body. It was the Mech that had been fused within him trying to break through but to no avail. The chill kept invading his body and even his soul.

Cracking sound could be heard as he froze. The layer of ice turned thicker over time and Divine Light’s consciousness started to fade away as his gaze became muddy.

Garen mimicked Jeros’ personality according to his memories as he revealed an evil and cunning smile.

“Those who defy me must die…!”

Boom!!

A white humanoid figure collided into Garen from the left. However, his Energy Field blocked the attack as he levitated in the middle of the air.

The huge force kept fighting against Garen’s Defensive Field as white debris rained down to the ground.

This person had a pair of eyes which were blue and had no pupils. It’s as if it was purely giving off a blue shine. His attire was all black and his hair was very similar to the mythical Medusa as they were all made from silver-white mechanical poisonous snakes that kept wiggling about on their own.

“Jeros… This is my territory!” The man with snakes as hairs spoke with a metallic, gender-neutral voice that was slightly echoic and deep-toned.

“Scram back to your Planet Dragon Emperor!!”

“Scram?!” Garen revealed an even more sinister smile. “You’re telling me to scram?!”

In that instant, he released a punch at lightning speed as his fist was gathered with an intense Energy Field and the punch landed flat on the face of the man who had snakes as his hair.

Kaboom!!

The thud similar to of a thunder could be heard as a huge shockwave spread across the air in all direction. As the Snake Hair Man received the punched straight in his face, his head sunk in and an overwhelming momentum followed afterward, sending him flying away as if he was a rocket. He then crashed onto the surface of the earth far away.

“Jeros!! Don’t you dare go across the line!!” Surprisingly, the Snake Hair Man didn’t die as he floated out from the surface crater as if nothing had happened to him. His head that had sunk in swiftly returned back to normal as he shouted at Garen with extreme anger.

“Is that Dazzling Silver Metal? Or is it Recovery Metal? The components you have on your body are good stuff…” Garen was shocked before he revealed an even more excited expression. “Coincidentally, I require these metals to enhance my Nine-Level Tempered Body Technique. I’m having trouble finding them and I didn’t expect them to appear right in front of my eyes!”

“Don’t assume that I’m afraid of you! Jeros, if you act out of line again I will report it to the Headquarter!” The Snake Hair Man shouted as he warned but it was rather outwardly strong and inwardly weak.

He took a step back and seemed to be preparing to find an escape route…

“Report? Go ahead,” Garen didn’t care at all.

If he could enhance his Nine-Level Tempered Body Technique, the technique could provide even more Vitality to his current physical attribute even though his Vitality could no longer be increased due to his Soul Limit. However, he could produce a layer of mysterious energy field around his body after learning this Tempered Body Technique. This layer of energy field was similar to being covered by a layer of crystal and it was able to provide extreme physical attributes.

This was also a technique that used external energy to enhance one’s body.

“Freeze!”

Turing appeared behind the Snake Hair Man out of nowhere and instantly restrained him with the power of the Non-falling Light.

In that instant, Garen’s chill propagated and towards him and completely froze him, locking him in a solid chunk of ice in a blink of an eye.

Crack crack…

The ice sealed up at the top, leaving no gap at all.

“There’s a hundred and thirty-nine types of metal. This robot is definitely valuable… The core is made out of the Dazzling Silver Metal and Shooting Zero’s Crystal which are just right to increase two levels to my Tempered Body Technique…”

He stared at the Snake Hair Man in the ice as he smiled. Living beings who were trapped within the frozen ice were still conscious but they were unable to move. It was very clear that fear and anger could be clearly seen in the Snake Hair Man’s gaze.

Garen’s main objective to return this time around was because of the Energy Tide and his secondary objective was to take revenge on his past grudges.

His Scarlet Snow Technique no longer had any bottlenecking ever since his Scarlet Snow Technique was used concurrently with the Scarlet Snow’s Ice Armor. He could improve his strength in a very short amount of time as long as he had enough energy to consume. However, the troublesome part was that it required an extremely large amount of energy. He might not even be able to meet the Scarlet Snow Sect Grade Eighteen’s requirement even if absorbed all the energy from a planet.

Furthermore, it required time for him to digest all of the energy from the Energy Ores. He would require at least ten years or more to completely absorb the Energy Ores even if his Peacock Technique had reached its peak. Even then, he would most likely not be able to accumulate the requirement as well.

Hence, Garen had seen the general event that he set his eyes on, the Energy Tide.

This natural tidal wave of pure energy was the easiest thing for him to absorb. It could then be converted into pure energy within the shortest time and swiftly enhance the Scarlet Snow Technique’s Grade.

However, such tidal explosion could only be activated under some special circumstances.

This activation was not in the hand of the humans and could only be chanced upon. Among all of the general timeline that he had seen, it had only activated once when Clint was traveling between the Four-Star Alliance and Mother Planet.

This was Garen’s true final objective.

He could use the energy from the tide to push his Scarlet Snow Technique to its maximum potential. At the same time, he could gather Soul Seeds and increase the upper limit of his Soul Limit.

The Energy Tide would last for a few days once it activated. Garen had prepared himself as he had already inherited countless of experience from the ancestors. With these energies and the height of Secret Technique that he had achieved, he would be able to condense multiple Soul Seeds of different Secret Techniques without any constraints in a very amount of time. This theory would definitely work!

In the past, he was not able to see the patterns in condensing the Soul Seeds. Practically, it would be possible for one to reach the realm of Soul Seed if he were to master the Secret Techniques, condense the experience and inspiration and merge them with the techniques. It was one of the most basic rules to condense a Secret Technique and inspire. Once it had been condensed, it would be able to guide every cell in one’s body to change according to the rule and achieve a higher physical limit.

This was the truth of the Soul Seed increasing the Soul Limits.

Garen gained a lot of senses as he inherited a huge amount of Secret Technique experience.

The Living Secret Technique was not necessarily required. As long as it was a top end Secret Technique that didn’t possess incredible power, one would be able to condense a Soul Seed with enough energy and basic inspiration.

Boom!

The Snake Hair Man’s body broke down as it disintegrated into metal debris. The metals were many colors and were mixed together in a very messy manner.

Garen then separated two metals out from the rest with one of his hands and started to compute at high speed via his Energy Machine Imprint as he gently inhaled with his mouth.

Hiss…

The metals, one black and the other white, turned into liquid as they flowed into his mouth like a river stream.

“As long as the Tempered Body Technique is enhanced, my body’s resistance would enhance as well. I would be able to counter the negative effects of the Destructive Impact Fists once it has reached a higher level!” This was one of the main reasons he had chosen these two Secret Techniques back then as they could support each other.

Garen stood at the peak of the mountain. Divine Light was completely frozen inside the ice and could not move an inch. On the other hand, the Hair Snake Man was completely disintegrated by Garen into a huge amount of rare metals. He had picked out a portion of it for collections and the remaining metals were completely devoured by his Peacock Technique which had turned into the essence of Cold Energy to supply his consumption.

Unfortunately, not all of the metals were considered high energy materials. Although some of the metals seemed very valuable, it didn’t possess much energy. Hence, the metals and the Energy Furnace inside the Hair Snake Man’s body were not able to give Garen a lot of Cold Energy. It was only equivalent to devouring a mountain of high energy mine. Furthermore, he required some time to completely digest them.

Garen stood at the pinnacle of the mountain and waited quietly as he finished absorbing the metals.

He closed his eyes as black halo started to illuminate around his body.

Soon, a layer of black film flashed across his entire body. Then, a translucent white layer flashed across his body as well.

These two metals soon managed to push the Nine-Level Tempered Body Technique to the second level.

Garen, who once practiced the Divine Statue Technique was very familiar with the sensation of his body being enhanced in a strange and miraculous manner. Hence, he was able to get used to it very quickly. Afterall, what the Nine-level Tempered Body Technique lacked was material and time instead of the difficulty in mastering the technique.

It was similar to the Ice Coffin as it was a technique that required hard work and patience.

However, Garen would only require tens of Potential Points and the problem would be completely solved.

Garen’s Potential Points broke into the thousand as he had absorbed a huge amount of Holy Tree Branches from the Business Alliance. Hence, he no longer needed to spend them sparingly like he used to in the past.

The second level of the Tempered Body Technique had been achieved within minutes with the help of the ingredients and potential points.

Garen opened his eyes as he was able to feel a thin layer of film that seemed to be protecting his body and ensuring it would not come in contact with the external world. Despite that, it was very mysterious as it didn’t affect his senses in the least. His body’s defense was enhanced dramatically and this ability seemed to derive from his own Vitality.

Chapter 1098: Clash 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s naturally gifted Vitality was so high that no one would be able to compete with him based on his strength alone. Afterall, Potential Points were used to enhance this aspect of his body.

One could only wonder how tough his body could be when the layer of thin film that was derived from his body was applied to his already strong body.

He reached out his hand and covered his palm with the Non-falling Light as he shaped his palm into a hand knife. Then, he attempted to injure himself.

Thud!!

A deep thud could be heard as the hand knife landed on his chest.

He was completely unharmed even without the use of his Energy Field to defend himself.

Ecstasy could be seen in his eyes as he slowly increased his strength.

Two times!

Thud!!

He hit himself onto his chest without mercy.

Nothing happened again.

Three times… Five times… Ten times…

Garen managed to feel some pain only after he increased his attack by ten times. It seemed that the layer of film was not able to completely filter out the strength and allowed some energy to pass through it and injure his skin.

“This is amazing! It has reached the realm of not injuring oneself at only level two. Despite the fact that I have an extremely high Vitality, it is still very powerful.”

Garen’s Vitality was extremely high to begin with. The Tempered Body Technique utilized the practitioner’s Vitality as its foundation to enhance his body. Hence, it was extremely beneficial towards people who possessed incredibly high innate Strength and Vitality.

However, the limit for everyone in the world was twenty points of Vitality. It was the limit that no one could exceed. However, Garen was different. He who had forty points worth of Vitality had far surpassed the realm of a typical person and was way beyond the species’ genetic upper limit.

Furthermore, no one would attempt to learn this Secret Technique after reaching the top. While the Nine-Level Tempered Body Technique wasn’t considered hard to practice, it would require at least ten years to reach level one. One would never be able to reach the entry level if they didn’t start at a very young age.

Garen, too, would not be able to learn this technique if he wasn’t gifted with Potential Points as he had already passed the age of learning it.

“The Predecessor’s wisdom is really incredible,” even he was not sure of the theory towards this Secret Technique’s defense.

“My body’s defense and toughness should be in between sixty to seventy points,” Garen looked at his Status Pane.

As expected, there were new changes towards the Nine-Level Tempered Body Technique.

Energy Machinist’s Secret Method — Nine-Level Tempered Body Technique: Level Two. Increases Vitality by 8 points. (Increment rate at the current Vitality 40*20%).

At the same time, his Attribute Pane had been updated as well. However, it wasn’t as much of an improvement as he had expected.

‘Nonosiva. Lin — Strength 40, Agility 40, Vitality 40 (+8), Intelligence 35, Potential 113082%. Soul Limit 40.’

He didn’t think much of it as everything was already prepared. The strongest man in Polar City had already been frozen beside him and the huge city in front of him was completely defenseless against him.

It was only then that Garen set his sight on the entire Polar City.

Turing had already taken off the Space Equipment from the already frozen Divine Light and presented it in front of Garen.

“Master, there seem to be good items inside them.”

Garen took possession of the items, which were a ring and a pair of spectacles.

He used his Willpower to look inside to find that they were filled with a lot of items. There were big chunks of Mastery Energy Ore’s Essence and a huge variety of exotic and strange looking Mech’s Parts and weapons. Furthermore, there were a lot of used Data Disks and living necessities.

“Let’s wrap everything up. We don’t have time to waste here.”

Garen reached out his hand and black clouds started to gather in the sky similar to what had happened in the Titan City.

A huge amount of white gas gathered on his palm to the point where it seemed like his arm was giving off smoke.

He then virtually gripped the Polar City from afar.

Sizzle…

In an instant, a huge arm made out of white gas appeared out of the black whirling cloud in the sky as it moved downwards.

“Everything shall end with the thirty-second ancestor’s ultimate technique…” Garen closed his palm gently. “Freeze History!”

Boom!!

The humongous arm shattered as it turned into countless of white Cold Energy. It dispersed into white raindrops as it poured.

Toot…!

A harsh alarm rang.

Garen realized something strange had happened as the white gas was obstructed by a layer of white light curtain which had the pattern of a snake on it.

A cluster of white dots swarmed out of Polar City as if Garen had disturbed a hornet’s nest. Those white dots were Pilots piloting the Shining Mech and they were flying towards him.

“Kill the invader!!”

An ice-cold electronic voice could be heard from the sky above the city.

They had no intention of negotiating with him as they outright announced to kill him off.

The cluster of white Mechs combined their Willpower as they headed towards Garen who was at the peak of the mountain.

White laser beams and cannons reached him first before the Mech had even arrived.

Boom!!

There was a series of explosions as the mountain Garen stood on was completely obliterated. Snow and fire mixed together as the dirt and debris soared high up in the sky from the explosion, forming a grey dusty pillar.

Communication via radio waves was sent and exchanged across the sky.

“Let’s bind him first while waiting for the support from the High Energy Orbital Cannon. Battleship Cannon is charging!”

“The opponent is a highly dangerous living being. It’s at least Level Five and above!”

“Be wary of your perimeter and maintain your distance!”

“Captain Great Light will soon arrive. Keep it up, everyone!”

“Prepare the Death Cannon!”

In an instant, a blinding black light was shot down from the sky. It was shot at Garen’s surrounding area and had completely covered the entire circular area up to hundreds of meters.

The mountain peak had collapsed!

The mountain’s height had been halved as it was struck by the cannon which was shot from a few thousand meters high. At the same time, the mountain peak was shattered into three large pieces as they glided down to its surrounding. The Pilots in the sky continued shooting these pieces into smaller debris as they were in the midst of breaking apart.

The Powerhouses that were in the city had started to appear in their own Mech as they floated in the sky, looking at Garen’s general direction.

“The city’s defense that could sustain an attack from the Non-Falling Level was broken by that attack just now! The enemy is a Non-Falling Level!” An old man said softly. He was operating a Great Light Mech and there were at least ten other operating the same Mech as him.

On the other hand, the people from the Black Flood Party were beside them in their own Mechs. Their Mechs were of different designs but all of them had one common point. Their Mechs’ shell was reflective, like a mirror.

It was the Mech material unique to the Divine Wind General.

The Forth Divine Wind General, Seventh Divine Wind General and two other traitorous powerhouses were grouped together in their Mechs.

Finally, the last crowd was a group which consisted of Ice Dragon, Fila and three other Inherited Level Mechs.

Surprisingly, Fila managed to rise to Inherited Level in a very short amount of time. It was very obvious that he did not rely on his own strength.

At this point in time, everyone gave all of their attention towards the ruined mountain.

“Can anyone analyze the situation inside?”

The highest ranked old man whispered.

“It’s very difficult. The radiation fluctuation is too great and causes too much instrument interference,” a Great Light Mech behind the old man responded softly.

The old man frowned as he glanced at the people from the Black Flood Party.

“The opponent has said that they’re here for you people. Don’t you guys have anything to say since you’re the root to this problem!?” He had always looked down on these characters who betrayed their own organization. Humans always had some bad habits deep-rooted in them and they would feel much less guilty compared to the first time they committed such act. In short, if they had done it once, they were more like to commit the second time or more.

This was the reason why he had never trusted the people from the Black Flood Party.

“White Whale, we’re victims in this matter as well. Although the opponent seems to be coming after us, I’m sure he’s also… hehe,” The Forth Divine Wind General spoke as he tried to come up with an excuse. “Furthermore, there’s no use in saying all these things since we’ve already opened fire. Are you hoping that the opponent will stop attacking and call for a truce after receiving a barrage of attacks?”

The Seventh Divine Wind General levitated silently behind him. His lifestyle in the Polar Region was worse than Blackboard Region. He already regretted early on but he could only walk down the path of darkness as he, unfortunately, could no longer turn back.

“Why hasn’t the Chief Leader arrived yet despite the situation?” One man asked.

“Perhaps he had gone to some other place and couldn’t get back in time,” the old man frowned. “Doesn’t matter. Regardless if the opponent is a Non-Falling Level or not, he is of no threat to us since he had to spread his strength over a wide area. Each of his white gas at most has the power of a Level Four. We are fine as long as we don’t let him destroy us one by one.”

“You’re right. We should be able to last until the Chief Leader returns,” one of the men agreed.

Then, an extremely frightening aura suddenly appeared above everyone.

Another giant arm which spanned thousands of meters wide appeared once more!!

The giant arm which was made out of an enormous amount of white gas struck downward.

Boom!!

The shockwave instantly deafened each and every one of the commoner’s ears within the city as blood started to flow out from their ears.

The snake patterned film could not last for even one second as it shattered, giving off a huge shockwave.

A humanoid figure in white robe could be seen above the giant arm as he levitated silently. The wind fluttered his robe as it kept moving to the left.

A bright, silver V-shaped imprint could be clearly seen on the white-robed man’s forehead. The imprint gave off an eye-catching halo as if it was the only light source among the black clouds.

“Freeze… History!”

Everyone could clearly hear him speaking in a very cold tone.

The giant arm then continued striking down!

***************

Underneath the Polar City.

A humanoid shadow was sitting on his knees deep inside a dark palace.

As the intense Ice Energy’s ripple came from above, the human figure slowly opened his eyes and they were shining in purple.

“Jeros! You’ve crossed the line!!”

A deep roar rang within the humanoid’s body as if there were countless bells ringing in unison.

He then raised his right hand and moved it towards his head.

In an instant, an endless amount of black and purple shadows gathered chaotically to his palm, as if the materials’ energy was instantly condensed into his arm.

Kaboom!!

The surface of the Polar City had been completely destroyed.

The surface cracked open as a giant black metallic arm which spanned thousands of meters wide surfaced and went towards the arm in the sky.

Countless of buildings collapsed as the huge arm appeared. Many people were crying and screaming in fear. Turbulent airflows were induced as the dust surrounded the black arm.

Two equally huge arms collided with each other.

In that instant, the world stopped moving.

Chapter 1099: War 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The black metallic giant arm shattered the white gas giant arm instantly.

The white gas collapsed and dispersed away as it flowed around the black metallic giant arm. It tried to freeze the arm but was obstructed by a thin layer of black halo.

Hoo… Foom!!

The black hand kept rising up and the gigantic black body was slowly surfacing from the ground.

The earth cracked open, a huge pitch black body which had sharp barbs all over his body as if it was wearing a hedgehog-like armor appeared.

Roar!!!

The giant humanoid shouted angrily at the sky. It was pitch black from head to toe and there was not a single contour on its face except for a big black mouth. Inside it was filled with countless of sharp fangs.

An abundant amount of dirt and bricks were brought up along with the giant humanoid as it poured down on the entire city. Dust spread about everywhere around his leg.

The giant humanoid was as big as the Polar City and the city trembled and was an inch closer to collapsing as the humanoid performed an action.

Countless white clouds of gas started to gather in the sky, forming a vague shape of a flying bird.

Shing!

A huge amount of ice crystal feathers appeared behind the big white bird. From afar, one could see that these ice crystals had formed into an extremely huge peacock which spanned tens of thousands of meters apart!

Chii!!!

A frightening cry similar to a kid’s cry came from the sky.

The white Icy Crystal Peacock that was as big as the black giant humanoid had materialized.

Two humongous creatures, the peacock flew in the air whereas the giant humanoid stood on the ground. The former was white while the latter was black as the area had been divided into their respective colors.

Many people had died in the Polar City but no one cared about it as even the Great Light Mechs could do nothing but to run away. If they were not careful, they would be frozen if they came in contact with the white gas that they were defenseless against.

The entire Polar City had completely collapsed the moment the black giant humanoid appeared.

A group of White Light’s best powerhouses retreated at full speed under the protection of the Bodyguard Mech around the city. The Mechs would need a few seconds of focusing their attacks to disintegrate the white gas.

The entire sky was filled with these white gas filled with Cold Energy as they kept flying about like a living being.

At the center of a protected area, the leaders moved about carefully as they looked around their surrounding for any incoming white gas.

Boom!

The Icy Crystal Peacock spanned open one of its wings as it hit against the few thousand meters tall building beside it. The wing, which was much wider than the building, froze the entire upper portion of the building in an instant the moment it came in contact with it. Those people who were still at the top and had yet escaped from the building were instantly turned into frozen corpses.

The black humanoid entangled itself with the Ice Crystal Peacock as these two gigantic creatures tumbled crazily within the Polar City. The peacock used its sharp beak to peck countless of holes to the humanoid body with each hole spanning hundreds of meters wide.

On the other hand, the black giant humanoid tore apart a huge amount of the peacock’s ice crystal feathers.

The entire city and Space trembled as the two creatures battled.

The Chief Leader was nowhere to be seen and White Whale, the temporary leader could barely evade from the incoming big Ice Crystal Feathers. The team had already successfully escaped out of the Polar City as he turned his head back to look at the city. The big city was completely thrown into chaos and at least a third of the surface was covered in an ocean of ice.

The snow falling from the sky was getting stronger and stronger…

“This… is more than just Non-falling Level…” White Whale’s voice was trembling.

These monsters no longer relied on battle skills or any techniques during their battles but a primitive brawl. These two monsters were the physical manifestations of the two powerhouses’ killing intent from their deepest core.

These creatures were not controlled by them. Instead, they were shaped and moved by their own respective auras. This manifestation represented the winning and losing situation between the two.

Those were the scattered forces from their killing intent manifesting into a physical body outside of their bodies.

“What is going on!!??” White Whale had managed to slightly calm down as his heart was beating furiously. He felt at ease after he believed that he was far enough from the battle.

“Can anyone tell me what that humanoid which appeared from underneath our Polar City is?!” One of the leaders spoke with an icy breath.

“Carmen had disappeared!”

“He went to save his daughter.”

“To head back into the center of such situation…” That man kept quiet before he even finished his sentence. He would die in the mess if he were to be careless.

“Is that black humanoid our Chief Leader!?” Fila spoke while levitating beside the Ice Dragon. He panted as the side of his Mech was frozen. Half of the engines behind his body was shooting off the particle beam and he seemed to be moderately injured.

“What should we do next?!” The Fourth Divine General looked at White Whale, who was the leader of the team.

“We can’t act hastily before confirming the identity of the black humanoid!” White Whale said confidently. “Our current forces are weak and will amount to nothing in this battle. We may even burden the black humanoid even further as well. We can only play by the ear!”

“If we gather all of the Satellite Orbital Cannon at maximum power…” One of the men suggested.

White Whale pondered for a moment. The Overhead Control Terminal was still functional and the hidden control point was not far away from the nearby town.

“I hereby order everyone to make preparation. We will fire once we have a general understanding of the situation!”

“Understood!”

He then issued a series of commands to calm the surrounding survivors, soldiers and Mechs and regroup them.

However, not many Mechs were willing to stay behind to fight an unbeatable monster in this chaos because their morale was instantly shattered.

The group worked hard but could only gather a small number of Mechs.

The Fourth Divine General brought the Seventh along as they occasionally looked at the Ice Crystal Peacock that was still wrecking havoc. All his thought was about who he had offended to the point the person would send out such a monster to threaten the Polar City to hand over them to him.

He was not aware of the overall situation but the slightly more sensitive Seventh Divine General felt that the surrounding leaders had quietly surrounded the people from the Black Flood Party. He could sense danger approaching from their anxious gaze.

This monster came for them. Perhaps they were able to calm the giant peacock’s anger if they handed the traitorous Black Flood Party to them.

“Watch out!” He pushed the Fourth Divine General away from a black sharp knife ambushing from his back.

“You!” The Fourth’s expression turned gloomy. He felt fortunate that the seventh pushed him away or he would be in deep trouble.

Two people brought along a few traitors that were under the Divine Wind Generals closer and the Divine Wind Generals had finally realized that they were surrounded. The surrounding Mechs gave off an ill posture and seemed to about to lay their hands on them.

White Whale was standing nearby. He, who was operating a Whale Head Mech didn’t say a word.

“White Whale, what is the meaning of this?” The Fourth scoffed softly.

“What do you mean?” Icy Dragon appeared beside White Whale and a rather crazy tone came from within the Mech. “It’s obvious that we are making you people as the bait to send it to that monstrous peacock. We have come up with a plan. You guys will pretend that you’ve been captured by us. We will then send you to that monster and you can probably fight back at a key moment and kill it off.”

“What kind of joke is that!” The Seventh shouted in anger. “Do you think we can still survive against that monster of such level? Why don’t you be part of your own plan!?”

Icy Dragon smirked as he put out both of his hands and shrugged. “I can’t do anything about it. He’s not after me…”

Shing.

A big broadsword was unsheathed and pointed at the bottom right direction.

“Hence, for the sake of everyone’s safety…”

“We wish you dead…” Suddenly, a white figure appeared behind the Fourth Divine Wind General. It was a White Mech with sharp streamline. It had two spears forming an X shape behind its back. The spears gave off a white glow in an instant as it formed into a cross.

Clank!

The frictional noise could be heard as the metal spear pierced into the Mech.

The Fourth Divine Wind General blocked the spears with his hands at lightning speed but he was still not able to evade the critical hit to his head.

Both Mechs stopped moving as the Fourth Divine Wind General’s right arm broke apart. His hand was decapitated by the Double Spear Mech.

“Light Wielder… What is the meaning of this!?” The Seventh Divine Wind General took a few steps back in fear as he stared at the Double Spear Mech without any sign of fighting back.

“What!? Can’t you see! He’s trying to send us to the enemy!!” The Fourth Divine Wind General’s angry voice came from within the cockpit.

“Since the Chief Leader is absent, the next in command will be White Whale,” the cold female tone coming from the inside of the Double Spear Mech was showing sign of fanaticism.

“Since you want us to die! I’ll make sure no one else lives!” One of the Divine Wind General’s underlying Mech shouted as the shells of the Mech opened up, revealing a huge amount of densely packed Highly Condensed Nuclear Bomb.

Gasp…

The surrounding Mechs gasped as they inhaled a breath of cold air.

No one could defend against the explosion from so many Highly Condensed Nuclear Bomb. At least half of the people there had to die!

“Looks like you people are well prepared…” White Whale said calmly. He would only sustain a minor injury for these bombs, hence he’s not too worried about it.

“It was just a precaution but I never thought that… Hehe,” The Fourth Divine General smirked.

The cold wind whistled as the situation had come to a stalemate. No one dared to attack first as both parties did not wish to perish together.

Clap… Clap… Clap…

Suddenly a clear clap could be heard from afar.

A tall figure which was at least two meters approached them slowly from the blizzard underneath the black clouds.

“It’s a brilliant plan,” a deep male voice could be heard. Everyone could clearly see the person’s face as the figure approached closer.

It was a humanoid giant wolf with two heads!

It was even wearing a white body-tight battle suit unique to the human. Its muscular contour could be clearly seen on the surface of the attire. His black long hair, which looked like a lion’s mane, was fluttering to the back as the chilly wind blew against him.

“Unfortunately, the Supreme Leader has given his order,” the dual-headed wolf said with a very stern face. “Everyone here shall return and be one with the universe…”

He then revealed a ferocious smile. “No one is exempted from this.”

Chapter 1100: War 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The air current flowed violently.

In the sky on top of the Polar City Ruins.

Garen, wearing a white robe, floated in the air, and a gigantic black Humanoid Mech was right in front of him.

Compared to the black Mech’s huge figure, the size of Garen’s body was not even the size of the Mech’s finger, yet it seemed as though the both of them were facing each other calmly.

The hem of the white robe started making a flapping sound as it was being blown by the wind. The robe continuously raised and fall.

Garen squinted his eyes slightly and stared at the huge black Humanoid Mech in front of him.

Two terrifying Qi’s Dynamics were bursting out of both of them, forming two huge monsters which were fighting with each other. There was a war between the Qi’s Dynamic of the White Ice Crystal Peacock and the Black Giant Human Figure.

“Puppet Master… fulfill my request. Otherwise, you will fall here today,” Garen said calmly.

“Jeros, there’s no use talking big! After today, I will report to the headquarters, and your intention to interrupt with the plan will be stopped!” The huge, sharp mouth of the Black Giant Human Figure said in a deep voice. He was being pushed to the edge; if he gave in, he would no longer have a place in this Star Region.

“The headquarters?” Garen had a sarcastic look on his face. “If that’s the case, then don’t put the blame on me!”

Suddenly, a large number of ice crystals gathered around his body, and numerous ice crystals started overlapping. Soon, the ice crystals quickly covered his entire body. The countless amount of ice crystals caused Garen’s figure to grow bigger and larger.

His body grew rapidly, and in less than a minute, he transformed from a tiny human figure to a giant ice crystal armor human figure like the black Humanoid Mech.

Numerous layers of ice-crystal wings extended from Garen’s back, and he was dressed in an extremely heavy, magnificent armor. The ferocious ice helmet covered his head completely, and his facial expressions could not be seen.

He wore the Scarlet Snow Ice Armor, which contained the greatest essence of the Scarlet Snow Sect.

Garen’s aura instantly increased to Level Nine.

“No… It’s impossible! How can your strength be restored so quickly!” The black human figure had an unbelievable look on its face.

“Nothing is impossible,” Garen sneered coldly.

“Spiral!”

He held his right hand up.

A massive White Gas Tornado was formed with his fingers as the base. It spun wildly into the sky and drove along the black clouds in the sky.

The tornado was black at the bottom and white at the top. In addition to that, numerous ice crystal fragments were gradually being added to the center.

“Star Core Resonance!” The black human figure spread out his arms in a frenzy, and numerous black threads were shot out of his ten sharp claw-like fingers. An overwhelming amount of black threads headed toward Garen.

The black threads cut through space and created multiple space crevices. Some of it swept through the ground and left trails of rotting-like marks.

“Resonance Sword!” The black human figure put its hands together. A giant black sword flew out of his hands, rushing toward Garen at a terrifying speed which was faster than the speed of light.

The moment the sword appeared, it seemed as though a large amount of power was being drawn from all the Planets of the Mother Planet, gathering on the sword.

“Star Core Resonance!” Garen held up the tornado. The black, white tornado was frozen into an extremely huge icicle and swung downwards heavily.

At the same time, a Level Nine power was suddenly activated. It drew and gathered the power of the entire Star Core of the Planet.

This was the unique power of a Level Nine powerhouse; it enabled them to draw the powers from the Planet’s Star Core for their own use.

This was the greatest, yet the most horrifying power. Being able to create and destroy all things.

Volcanoes, earthquakes, windstorms, tsunami, he was the root of all disasters, and also the core of all living things.

By activating the Star Core Resonance, its greatest feature will naturally be emanated.

The greatest feature of a Level Nine expert was their explosive ability.

A horrifying gravity started spreading rapidly by breaking out of Garen’s and the black humanoid mech’s body. It formed an invisible corrugation on all four sides, and everything that was affected disintegrated into powder-like particles.

This was the result of a physical structure being torn apart and at the same time being subjected to a tremendous force.

The most natural manifestation of a Level Nine expert was the ability to control gravity at the strength of ten thousand folds. Usually, Level Nine Experts would restrain their natural gravity from releasing. However, during an all-out fight, they could no longer suppress this terrifying power. Therefore, by releasing their aura naturally, it would absolutely cause damage to the planet.

This was the difference in the Levels.

Those above the Non-Falling Level would naturally form a Battle Territory, and those who were not at the same level will not be allowed to enter.

The black and white ice tornado swung down heavily. Although it seemed to be moving slowly, in the eyes of the outsiders, it happened instantly, like a lightning and a flint.

The black sword and tornado collided. Oddly, the black sword was distorted, turned into another direction and going straight toward Garen.

The ice pillar tornado exuded a horrifying chill, instantly turned into a huge Ice Crystal Peacock, and brutally pecked on the black sword that was about fly right beside it.

Bang!!

An unbelievably sharp sound wave burst out in all directions.

The Polar City crumbled instantaneously. The earth quickly collapsed under the influence of the ten thousand folds of gravity, gradually turning into an empty black abyss.

The two-headed monsters were still fighting in mid-air. The surrounding mountains and clouds were completely shredded.

The dark clouds in the air dispersed off, and a gigantic empty hole could be seen. A light pillar with golden sunlight fell from the sky and shone on the two-headed monsters. On the contrary, it exuded a strong and dazzling radiance, as though a battle between Gods in mythology was taking place.

The Ice Crystal Peacock screamed loudly and the black human figure growled furiously.

Space was vibrating, and numerous glass-like cracks covered the surrounding space within thousands of kilometers. Cracks appeared on the space structure as it could not withstand such a huge amount of gravitational force and powerful vibration.

The power of the Star Core was being constantly drawn by the two of them and gathered onto their respective weapons, turning into sparkling silver-colored lights. It was a thick, mercury-like energy fluid which was able to reflect a rainbow-like ray under the sun.

The ice pillar tornado and the black sword collided with each other violently, and each collision caused a horrible space vibration.

At this moment, all the people on the Mother Planet was aware that the earth was shaking, which was an unstable vibration caused by the power of the Star Core being excessively extracted.

Thousands of kilometers away from the battlefield, the area above the edge of the space cracks, Turing and the White Light General of the Polar Region were fighting. A piercingly cold chill poured out frenziedly, driving the entire area into a complete World of Ice.

However, the moment when the Star Core quivered, the people here instantly felt it.

“This is bad! The Mother Star can no longer withstand a battle with this level of intensity!” Turing stopped suddenly, recalling the thing that Garen had mentioned to him previously, and his facial expression instantly became serious.

The power of the two experts who had completely reached Level Nine was so terrifying that the entire Mother Planet could feel the turmoil of their battle.

“One Time Fist Pressure!”

At the core of the battlefield.

The ice crystal wings on Garen’s back flapped violently and instantly rushed toward the Black Figure.

The brief force field gathered by the punch had increased by a fold once again!

“Destructive Siphon!” The black human figure spouted a large amount of rainbow-like destructive beams, intending to interrupt Garen.

Boom!

Holes appeared through the rainbow-like beams after being punched through.

Garen had a nasty grin on his face while he rushed towards the gigantic human figure.

“Do you want to destroy the Mother Planet?!” The black human figure growled. He did not expect Garen to be able to release such a horrifying power. Along with a trace of fear, he insanely drove all the power from his body.

“I am the Grand Duke of Destruction of Finite! You cannot kill me!!”

Garen ignored him. His felt his fist pressure getting a little sluggish, so he instantly mustered up all the power in his body.

“Triple Fist Pressure!”

He growled, and the power in his body increased by three times that of the original.

“Ultimate Termination!” The black human figure knew that he could not beat his opponent, so he used the backup plan that he had prepared beforehand.

A black hole suddenly appeared at the center of the huge human figure, and a large number of black tentacles appeared from the inside of the black hole. The tentacles, resembling that of an octopus, sprayed a large amount of ink-like poisonous fog towards Garen like a tide.

“It’s useless!” The force field surrounding Garen had gotten to an unimaginably strong level. The poisonous fog and the force field were fighting against each other. Then, the fog instantly passed through Garen, falling directly behind him. This had completely destroyed the black humanoid mech’s plan to escape.

Garen had transformed into his strongest form by having his attribute increased by three times as well as by wearing the Scarlet Snow Ice Armor. At this point, he no longer needed to wear the armor to reach Level Nine. Instead, there was no difference between him and an actual Level Nine. He was able to fully exert this level of power. A physical body with an attribute of 120 points was incredibly powerful, yet it also brought about an incomparably huge burden.

Garen wore the Scarlet Snow Ice Armor to increase his strength. Even though he had only increased his attributes by three times, the piercing pain that he felt was beyond his imagination. Apparently, his body could not withstand it.

This was an increase based on the strength of a Level Nine. After all, it was not the same as the Non-Falling Level. However, the black human figure was doing worse than him, as he was about to collapse.

The power of the Grand Duke of Destruction was still slightly below that of a Level Nine, and he could temporarily only rely on secret techniques to break through this level.

After a few collision, he could no longer withstand it. By drawing the power of the Star Core, the power itself would impose a huge burden on one’s body. It was already horrifying to be able to temporarily launch a Star Core attack. However, he did not expect Garen to be fully stable in this state, being able to fight up until this point. Even the Mother Planet could no longer withstand the battle between the two of them.

The Planet was trembling with fear. The Star Core was the source of innumerable lives, and it also gathered the consciousness of countless lives together. Now that it was on the verge of destruction, all living things could instinctively feel an upcoming destruction from the Star Core.

A fear that erupted from the depths of one’s heart continuously moved toward his entire heart.

The Grand Duke of Destruction’s huge body began collapsing bit by bit.

A human figure surrounded by a purple and black energy flow was covered in countless wounds, and white-colored blood slowly flowed out of them.

Boom!

The entire black human figure exploded into pieces.

The Grand Duke of Destruction flew out along with the explosion, falling into the dark abyss below.

“You can’t kill…me!!” he yelled painfully at the end.

Sss.

Garen’s figure, which was also covered in blood, appeared beside him. With a ‘clap’ sound, he held the Duke’s head in his hands.

“How dare you defy the Great Jeros?” He brought the black figure right in front of him and said with Jeros’ ferocious evil smile.

“Are the Wraith Royalties trying to start a fight with the Finite People?! You can’t kill me!” The Grand Duke of Destruction struggled, using both of his hands to grab Garen’s hands.

“I hate when people threaten me…” The evil look on Garen’s face got deeper.

He did not expect Jeros to be someone from the Wraith Royalty. Therefore, he immediately raised his vigilance regarding his involvement in this matter.

If he was able to get enough detailed information from this person’s head… he suddenly got an idea in his mind.

Chapter 1101: Captive 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Wraith Royalty was one of the two most powerful races in the universe. The first was the Finite People, and the Wraith Royalty came second. They were born with extremely strong and gifted bodies. They had an invincible body and were able to reach the Inherited Level as soon as they become an adult. However, they had an extremely low fertility rate.

Garen knew a part of the information from this area. He initially thought that Jeros only had an odd appearance, but he did not expect him to have such a huge background.

“No! Don’t kill me!” The Grand Duke of Destruction was still screaming in Garen’s hand.

However, it was to no avail. Simply by comparing their physical strength, all his energy combined could not even compare to one of Garen’s arms.

Garen suddenly punched the Grand Duke of Destruction in the head.

Bang!

After punching the Grand Duke of Destruction with a punch that could turn an ordinary energy machinist head into a bloody mess, the Duke’s whole body was completely covered by numerous frosts. He was instantly frozen within the firm, and he could no longer move again.

The battle was over, but the Star Core of the Planet was still trembling slightly.

“It’s time to go see Turing…”

Garen looked around at his surroundings; he did not find any living or intact things around.

He saw a bottomless dark abyss underneath him. In addition to that, there were countless glacier mountains made out of frozen ice and ruins all around him.

After flying through a long distance along the edge of the abyss, Garen vaguely saw Turing quietly standing on an empty snowfield.

Turing was surrounded by multiple people frozen into icicles, most of them were high ranking members of the White Light Organization in the Polar region.

Most importantly, the seventh and the fourth Divine Wind Generals were among them.

Garen looked at Turing and nodded with satisfaction. If it were not for him, these people might have escaped.

“Let’s go. The affected range of this battle is too wide and many people will be alerted.”

“Yes, great master,” Turing bowed respectfully.

The Non-Falling Light around both of them lighted up at the same time, and they directly flew upward along with all the human-shaped icicles. Garen took a black ball out and threw it into the air. Suddenly, the ball swelled, turning into a space jump portal.

The two of them entered the portal one after the other, then the space portal shrunk and disappeared into thin air.

On a satellite revolving around the Mother Planet.

The brown-gray little satellite was like a wasteland, only mud and rocks can be seen on it. Other than that, there were also craters and bulging, densely-packed volcanoes.

A piece of green grassland appeared abruptly among the shadows of a volcano. There was a small wooden house in the middle of the grassland. There was a gentle breeze blowing toward a beautiful woman in a white dress who was sitting in front of the wooden house.

The woman was so cold that it was as though she was not alive. Not a trace of blood was visible on her body. It was as though she was a crystal porcelain doll, as her skin was crystal-clear.

Her gaze was fixed at the direction of the Mother Planet.

On the surface of the deep blue Mother Planet, a wave of transparent ripples caused by an explosion could be seen from afar. It was like a water ripple, slowly spreading toward all sides before gradually fading away. However, it still managed to cover the entire surface of the planet.

“There…” The woman closed the book in her hands. There was a surprised look in her eyes. “It’s the place of the Grand Duke of Destruction…”

“No. 4,” She turned around and looked toward the wooden house.

“Yes,” A group of distorted shadow flew out of the wooden house and floated right in front of the woman.

“How did the parasite of Jeros from the Wraith Family get here? Go deal with him,” The woman said motionlessly. “So that it will not affect our plan.”

“Do I need to kill him?” The shadow asked.

“No,” The woman shook her head slightly. “This is not the right time for us to go against the Wraith Royalties. Isn’t Jeros’ sister looking for him? Tell her about her brother’s news, and open the jump portal for her. She will definitely come over.”

The shadows immediately understood what she meant.

“Indeed. The Wraith Royalties are infamous for being cold towards their relatives. Moreover, they have contributed greatly to this plan. Therefore, if they know that Jeros is trying to ruin the plan, what will his sister do? I’m looking forward to it…” The shadow said in a sarcastic tone.

“What you’re thinking will not happen. Jeros has the best relationship with his sister, just like any other siblings in the human race. They can even share their power and influences by governing the 1600 planets together. Therefore, the highest possibility is that she will bring him away,” The woman answered calmly.

“Of course, if you were to tell his father, then it might end up like what you’ve expected. However, we shouldn’t openly offend the Wraith Royalties right now.”

“Okay then, so be it,” The shadow answered and rushed directly into the sky. It swiftly turned into a black slender beam, flying directly into space. In just a short while, it resembled a fish that had drilled into space and disappeared out of sight. It entered the Negative Space.

The woman calmly put the book down and walked into the wooden house without making any sound.

**********************

In a distant bloody-red planet.

Planet Dragon Emperor.

This was the Planet Region of the Wraith Royalties. As one of the strongest races in the universe, it was located in the middle of the Finite Nebula. The Wraith Royalties had ruthlessly ruled thousands of planets.

In fact, there was only one family in their race; it consisted of five members.

There were only a total of five members in the entire Wraith Royalties.

At the summit of the highest mountain of Planet Dragon Emperor, there was a magnificent, blood-colored palace that was thousands of meters wide.

The bottom of the palace was located at the peak of the mountain, and it looked as though the entire palace was supported by the small, pointy end of the mountain.

In the palace, a glamorous woman wearing a black tight-fitting silk dress was sitting slothfully on the highest throne. The main hall was constantly filled with traces of black blood-colored airstreams. On the heads of these airstreams were human-shaped faces with painful expressions.

The girl was like an elegant noble princess. She gave off a flirtatious yet pure aura, which was oddly contradictory. She had a slim waist, a pair of slender legs, and skin as fair as jade. Moreover, she had a huge chest and a pair of beautiful, watery eyes.

If it were not for the strange surrounding of the hall, just by looking at the woman alone, perhaps anyone would think that she was a noble princess from a certain country. She was elegant and pure, yet the way that she dressed gave off a glamorous feeling.

Contrary to her temperament, the woman who was sitting on the throne changed her slothful posture slightly. She placed her hands on the armrest of her seat and an unimaginably horrifying aura exploded out of her body.

There was a faint, bloody glow in her eyes, but the bloody-red glint disappeared in just a blink of an eye.

“No. 4? What are you doing? What does the woman who claims to be the ruler want?”

The girl instantly changed from a pure and flirtatious girl to a Queen with an overwhelming aura. She lifted her chin slightly as though she had the rights to look at everything in the world from above.

A shadow slowly appeared in the center of the hall. It was No. 4 who rushed over here from the distant Mother Planet.

He understood that the girl had the rights to be looking down at him from above.

The Wraith Royalties were theoretically the most powerful noble race among all the known races in the universe. They were born with a Level Four willpower. Also, as soon as they reached adulthood, they would reach the Inherited Level, no exception.

Just by working a little harder, they could easily reach the Non-Falling Level. Moreover, because of their naturally-gifted abilities, their combat strength was far beyond their peers.

The girl standing right in front of the shadow was known as the strongest genius of the Wraith Royalties, the Fresh Blood Holy Lord.

“Your Highness, Fresh Blood Holy Lord,” No. 4’s respectful voice was heard coming out of the shadows. “Pardon me for coming here abruptly. The reason why I came here is to deliver an extremely important message.”

“An extremely important message?” The girl freshened up slightly. “Tell me about it.”

Numerous black and red airstreams with human faces in the hall began gathering around No. 4. Every one of the airstreams was craving for fresh blood, giving people a ferociously evil feeling.

However, No. 4 did not seem tense. He knew that she would not hurt him. After all, he was the representative of the ruler, which represented the White King’s influences.

“Your Highness has already gotten the highest throne, and the plan that he had planned 10 years ago has been initiated. However, at the most critical moment, your younger brother, Jeros, suddenly appeared where he should not be,” No.4 replied calmly.

“Jeros?” The Fresh Blood Holy Lord frowned slightly.

“Yes,” No. 4 said firmly. “Your Highness, Jeros has captured the Grand Duke of Destruction, who was part of our plan. What is his intention? The ruler sent me to inform you about it. Please take an action as soon as possible.”

The girl frowned slightly and did not respond immediately. Instead, she flicked her fingers lightly.

Oh!

A tiny black light suddenly exploded right in front of her, turning into a clear black mirror.

“The annihilation of Energy Machinist is a definite plan. The Finite government, the Wraith Royalties and the Human Alliance Council play a role in it. My younger brother has always known his boundaries. But, now you are telling me that he caught the Grand Duke of Destruction and intends to sabotage the plan?”

The tone of the Fresh Blood Holy Lord had gradually gotten serious.

No. 4 was not afraid of the Lord’s wrath.

“This is the will of the Ruler. I am only here to convey it.”

He reached out his fingers and suddenly, the black mirror in front of the Fresh Blood Holy Lord suddenly showed the scene when Garen was fighting the Grand Duke of Destruction.

The Fresh Blood Holy Lord watched the scene quietly.

“This is… the Destructive Impact Fist?” She saw through the secret fist technique that Garen was using.

“Yes,” No. 4 said firmly in a low voice.

The atmosphere suddenly got a little tense.

The both of them kept quiet for quite some time.

The airstreams were flying about at a greater speed.

“I will take a trip there in person,” The Fresh Blood Holy Lord seemed to have notice wrong about it.

No. 4 had achieved his goal. He turned into a black shadow, directly flying out of the hall without turning back.

“We’re looking forward to the arrival of your Highness,” The shadow left this sentence before completely disappearing from the hall.

“The Destructive Impact Fist? He actually managed to three times of the original? Wasn’t he against this kind of pure power previously?” She watched the scene on the black mirror repeatedly, and a trace of blood appeared in the eyes of the Fresh Blood Holy Lord.

“Before I challenged the White King, my stupid little brother actually gave me a pleasant surprise…” The indescribable look in the girl’s eyes grew deeper.

*******************

Mother Planet.

The entire Mother Planet was in a mess at that moment.

The Blackboard Region, the Maria Region, the Royal Region, and the rest of the Sect’s representatives from the Academies Union. After keeping a low-profile for some time after the war, everyone finally sent their experts to the Polar City Region to investigate the incident.

Either way, they were the forces of the Mother Planet. This war was an inevitable hurdle for them, and they needed to investigate how it would affect the entire Mother Planet.

A large number of Inherited Level and Non-Falling Level experts arrived at the Polar Region. While they were frightened by the gigantic, endless abyss, Garen and Turing had already captured the Polar City experts to the Radiation Area of the Mother Planet.

Clint and the others would return soon. In other words, the energy tide will erupt soon.

Garen had prepared for everything.

The energy fluctuation caused by the energy tide would not only affect one Planet. Instead, it involved a large amount of energy flow in the entire universe. The moment when the energy bypassed the transmission actuator while moving across the universe, a tide of fluctuation would result. Somehow, this fluctuation just so happened nearby the Mother Planet.

The capital of the Blackboard Region, the Blackboard City.

Black Star Diofie sat on the Dean’s seat exhausted, and he held the staff that his master gave him on the verge of death.

The newly-formed Three Marshals were sitting underneath him.

Red-eyed Medero, Britney, and another bald man.

These Three Marshals were the high-ranking members of the Blackboard Region, which was under the control of the younger generations. Each of them had accepted their Master’s origin and become the top experts in order to support the entire Blackboard Region.

Chapter 1102: Captive 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“The weather is gradually getting worse,” Diofie said with a heavy heart. “The Weather Monitoring Directorate has verified the source of the abnormal snow. It has the same source of energy as the earthquake that erupted previously…”

“The other regions have called. They have also detected that majority of the destructive energy that destroyed the Polar City is related to the fluctuation that started the big snow,” Medero said in a low voice. “Mariana from the Maria Region wants to join forces with us. They also discovered that a huge disaster that affects the entire Planet might occur. However, they could not detect the reason behind it.”

“The Royal Region has also reached the same conclusion. Millions of people from the Titan and Polar City are gone! This kind of power should not exist within the Mother Planet! The people from the Royal Region will most likely bear the huge disaster that will affect the entire planet. The source of this calamity is a power that is beyond our limits.”

“The people from the Central Academy has arrived. There are dozens of top experts who have come along,” Finally, the bald man said in a deep voice.

“What do they want?” Diofie asked wearily.

“Dean, we have no choice. We must eliminate the root of all this,” The bald man raised his voice. “If we do not remove the source, the disaster will gobble us up! Every single one of us!”

Diofie closed his eyes. He was physically and mentally exhausted. An overwhelming pressure was weighing down on him, and he seemed as though he was running out of breath.

“All the evidence is pointing at him. He is the root of everything! As long as we get rid of him, I believe that everything will return to normal,” The bald man said loudly.

Bang!

The door of the battleship conference room pushed open heavily.

“He’s right!”

A tall man in a white shirt walked in along with several people.

The man looked young, but there were traces of maturity and seriousness in his eyes. Clearly, he was much older than he looked.

“I’m Fiery Fear. Before the Central Academy arrived, they have already detected an abnormal high-energy organism entering the Blackboard Region. However, he did not raise any attention. Unfortunately, if we have paid more attention to that person since the beginning, this tragedy might not happen!”

He said with a serious look on his face.

“Thirty million people… were killed in the war, but that person…” He had a genuine painful expression on his face. “This can no longer be treated as a man-made disaster! We must treat him as a natural disaster!”

“Dean Fiery Fear,” Diofie stood up with a respectful look on his face.

“The stability of the Mother Planet is fundamental to everything; it is the foundation of the people! Regardless of the upcoming disaster, or the unbearable sin and blood! The culprit must provide us a justification!” Fiery Fire said in a serious tone. “I have informed the older deans who are living in seclusion. Presumably, all the Non-Falling Levels from each the major states have started gathering… We will definitely be able to win this war!”

Diofie nodded his head earnestly.

*************************

A few days later, in the Blackboard Region.

In an unmanned mountain forest villa.

Garen brought along Turing and forcibly occupied the holiday villa. They made the owner of the villa leave by dropping a hint. They even got rid of the robbers nearby who were about to attack the villa.

The snow in the Blackboard Region was getting heavier.

A thick layer of white snow had accumulated on the ground, and the land turned from a warm season to a winter.

In the study room of the villa.

Garen looked at the girl, Tesna, who was frozen in a block of ice. Although the girl had similar appearance and temperament as the female disciples who was under him previously, her personality was completely different.

This girl had a straightforward and a slightly impulsive personality.

Even after the war had triggered an earthquake, this silly girl insisted on burying herself on the ground.

If it was not for Garen suddenly recalling that a person he was testing was still under the ground, the girl would most probably be frozen to death.

Basically, she had a one-track mind. Describing her in a nice way, she was straightforward. However, to put it in a bad way, she was a fool…

“One of them got away. You did not manage to complete your job…” Garen was sitting in the study room while he looked at Turing who was kneeling in front of him. The huge werewolf was as tall as him even when he was kneeling down.

“I’m incompetent,” Turing said with guilt. “At that time, I was stunned by the vibration of the Star Core. Therefore, that person used the long distance space jump to escape. I shall bear this responsibility! Please punish me, Master!”

“I’ll pass it to you to deal with it,” Garen responded with his eyes closed. He seemed to be too lazy to continue talking, so he waved his hands casually.

He was trying to prepare his body and mind for the energy tide eruption tomorrow.

“I will try my best to catch the last person!” Turing stood up and answered firmly. Then, he strode out of the study room.

The door closed gently.

In a short while, a figure once again pushed the door open. It was not Turing, but the Ice Dragon from the White Light!

An Inherited Level expert dressed in expensive clothing walked into the room with a straight face.

“Are you planning to imprison us here just like that?”

He walked up to Garen, pulled out a chair and sat in front of him. Not a shred of urgency could be seen.

“Why not?” Garen opened his eyes and smiled.

Garen must admit that Ice Dragon was very handsome when he was calm. He also had a great temperament. Yet, why did he put up an upstart act? Clearly, he was someone with a history. Unfortunately, Garen was not interested in knowing his story.

“White Whale and the rest of them sent me to ask you, what are you planning to do to us?” Ice dragon asked casually. He glanced at Garen, a man that he had once met for a short while. At that time, Garen was just at Resonance Level. However, Garen had now reached a terrifying level after only a few decades.

Therefore, he still couldn’t be sure that this Garen was the Resonance Level student with whom he had once fought.

Garen looked at the rumored lunatic who was standing in front of him strangely.

“Do you think that I will kill all of you?”

“Are you not going to?” Ice Dragon raised his brows. “There are 6.8 million people who lived in Titan City, and including the migrants, you have killed tens of millions of people. The tens of millions of people in the Polar City are just like ants that you step under your feet, so why would you hesitate to kill the few of us?”

Garen smiled lightly when he heard a trace of resentment in his voice.

“Would you believe it? An overwhelmingly huge disaster is approaching soon.”

“Isn’t that you?” Ice Dragon said affirmatively.

Garen ignored him.

“This disaster is bound to happen, and everyone with a willpower will be severely injured. The Mother Planet will turn into a mess, and no one will be able to generate willpower ever again. The Mother Planet will be isolated from the rest of the universe, it will become a testing ground for those who are at the top.”

Ice Dragon frowned deeply. “What do you mean by this?”

Garen looked at him.

“The funny thing is, everyone thinks that I’m the culprit of this calamity,” He said with a funny look his face.

“Now they are gathering and planning to execute me together for a disaster that is unrelated to me. Isn’t it funny?”

“I don’t think it’s funny.” Ice Dragon answered lightly. He had struggled through battles all year round for a breakthrough, having a close shave with death multiple times. Unfortunately, due to his limited qualifications, he was only able to reach the peak of the Inherited Level. He was the only one who was not afraid of dying among the high-ranking White Light members who were captured.

“Aren’t you the culprit?”

Garen shook his head without providing any explanation. He knew that explanations will only seem like a cover up to the outsiders.

He had made preparations to absorb the energy tide by covering the three regions with dark clouds. However, he did not expect to be seen as a culprit for drawing the energy tide.

Garen stood up. Even he himself did not know why he did not kill all of them instantly. He was just following his gut.

Other than the Seventh Divine Wind General, Fila was the only one whose whereabouts were unknown. Garen had unfrozen the rest of the people and allowed them to move freely in the villa.

Garen walked toward the window and looked outside through the glass panels. It was still snowing out there. Layers and layers of large snowflakes covered the ground.

The world seemed to have suddenly turned into an icy world, and there were no signs of humans outside. Due to the bad weather and the vibration previously, only those who had a death wish would wander around the wilderness.

“The Polar Region has been completely destroyed. The people from the Blackboard Region, the Maria Region, the Royal Region, as well as the Central Academy, and the experts from other states… All the Non-Falling Levels too, they have all gathered, heading in my direction. Do they think that this is a game? By gathering all the heroes, do they think they can fight against me?” Garen said calmly, with a hint of sarcasm on his face.

“The Mother Planet is not only supported by local forces!” Ice Dragon said calmly.

“Of course, I know. It is also the energy machinists’ territory,” Garen smiled. “What is controlling the Mother Planet? The magnetic field? The Nebula? Or the Black Sword? It should be the Nebula. No… It should not be just a single force, it should be a testing ground which occupied the three major forces…”

Ice Dragon’s pupil shrunk slightly. A testing ground?

It was the first time that he had heard about this secret.

“Okay, it’s time to go and see our beloved Seventh Divine Wind General.” Garen patted the non-existing dust off his body. He wore a robe which was as white a snow, walked out of the study room and walked downstairs.

More than a dozen people were sitting in the hall. All of them were the top high-ranking members of the White Light organization. Light Wielder was the only one who stood among the crowd, and he was the strongest among them. He was a shadow, and his whole body was wrapped around a white robe.

Garen looked at this group of people. He saw how they were alerted and scared. They did not dare look at Garen, instead, they lowered their gazes one after the other.

The distorted seeds that he fed them must have begun to work. After a short while, it will condense into a power that he could use for himself.

For the time being, Garen ignored them and went straight to the basement. Ice Dragon followed behind him closely. Garen did not stop him and allowed him to follow along.

The basement was gloomy and cold. There was a block of ice in the middle, and the Seventh Divine Wind General’s body was frozen still in it. Only his head was exposed in the air.

“Why didn’t you just kill me!?” The Seventh Divine Wind General looked extremely pale, and there was no color in his cheeks. When he saw Garen walking down, he still had a cold look on his face.

“Kill you?” Garen shook his head. “Previously, you punched me and almost completely cut off the relationship between me and the pilot, but you didn’t kill me. Therefore, I will not kill you for the time being.”

“I regret not killing you at that time!!” The Seventh Divine Wind General said ferociously. He knew that he will not be spared, so he had given up completely.

“If I have known that you would have grown this strong, I would have made up my mind and go against Six and kill you. That will save us all these troubles!”

“If you have known? If you have known, you wouldn’t have just reached the Inherited Level,” Garen said sarcastically. “It’s impossible for anyone to predict the future of the people they have met. You should know that only geniuses have this ability…”

There was a profound meaning in his words.

“What is the point in saying all these now? Just kill me,” The Seventh Divine Wind General closed his eyes. “Didn’t you come just for this?”

“Kill you? You’re so useful to me, why should I kill you?” Garen had a strange look on his face. “It’s just that, I wanted to study the ability to retrieve an expert’s memory. Theoretically, parts of an ordinary person’s memory can be replicated. However, it is different for an expert… You can also technically considered as an expert.”

Chapter 1103: Tide 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Four-Star Alliance

“Is it really okay for us to do this?”

Baylon was a little worried as she watched Clint place mushroom-like explosives of various sizes on to the stone wall of the cave.

“Don’t worry… Since White Winter said that it will be alright, then it will definitely be alright,” Clint replied affirmatively.

A boy with fair skin was standing beside them. Even though he was dressed in a gray clothing specifically made for miners, he still gave people a pretty and cute aura. No one could tell that he was a boy. Everyone who had seen him for the first time would think that he was a flat-chested girl.

His skin was so fair that it seemed translucent, and his pair of animal-like ears could vaguely be seen beneath his long white hair. From time to time, his ears would tremble slightly. When he looked at Clint with his big watery eyes, he unconsciously revealed a timidly cute look.

Other than that, he had a pair of perfectly-rounded, slender legs and perky buttocks. He had the ideal figure that many girls longed of, and he had a figure similar to that of Baylon’s.

He was White Winter, a good friend that Clint and the rest of them met in the mining area. Due to this guy’s special vitality, his entire body naturally gave off chill air. Therefore, no one was willing to approach him. Clint saw how he was working extremely slowly, and he could not take it anymore. He thought that a helpless and delicate little girl was doing the same amount of work as a man. Thus, he went forward to offer assistance. He found out that he was a boy only after he had finished helping him. That was how the three of them got to know each other.

“But what if all the mushroom explosives destroy the entire mining area?” Baylon asked helplessly. While Red Moon was taking a rest, she played the role of persuading them. However, she noticed that Clint was gradually being more like Red Moon. Instead of learning to be more cautious, he had become more impulsive and rash.

“White Winter, say something. We won’t need that many explosives to open a path to the secret chamber above, right?” Baylon looked towards White Winter helplessly.

“I… I…” A red flush appeared on White Winter’s cheek; he did not dare look at Clint. His two brown animal-like ears were moving constantly, and he had the look of a naïve young girl.

Baylon helplessly covered her face… Why did it take so long for Lord Red Moon to contact his parts… He needed to return quickly… Clint was getting even more unreliable.

If only her big brother was here… she thought about her brother, Nono once again. Her brother was a genius who seemed to know everything. If her brother was here, then there would definitely not be a problem.

Unfortunately, this was Planet Gideon, it was too far away from the Mother Planet…

“Sigh… Who knows how’s my brother doing now. With his talent, he would definitely be able to break through the Inherited Level…” Baylon thought absentmindedly while she leaned on the stone wall. “At least he won’t be like me, who’s as weak as an ordinary human after losing my mech…”

“After opening the path to the secret chamber, Lord Red Moon will be able to use resonance to draw the parts out. We must hurry. Otherwise, it would be bad if the Spirit King finds out about it!” Finally, Clint placed the last mushroom explosive on top of the stone wall.

After the three of them met, they unexpectedly discovered that the Spirit Mech King was the ruler of the entire mining area. Red Moon’s parts were under his control. After a session of tormenting, deep thoughts, they finally came up with this plan. This would allow Red Moon to enter the secret chamber to draw his parts. Then, everyone would make use of the explosive energy caused by combining the parts to connect to the Negative Space tunnel, which would, in turn, lead them back to the Mother Planet. In just an instant, they could directly jump back to the Mother Planet, and the Spirit King will definitely not be able to catch up.

Without a doubt, the plan was thought out by Red Moon. The three of them did not expect White Winter to be a natural-born strategist. He added on a series of details and a loophole that Red Moon had missed. Baylon and Clint could no longer look at him the same way. With a promise, they recruited him under the category of Star General…

The other Regent Level Star Generals were all extremely strong. However, they were trapped in an extremely distressful situation. Other than empty promises and a close-range training method, the Star Generals had nothing else… they were extremely shabby.

However, White Winter was still very happy. Ever since he was qualified to become Red Moon’s Star General, he had always secretly stared at Clint. He looked like a young girl who was in love.

“Let’s go, we need to go a little further,” Clint asked the both of them to leave the explosion area.

As the three of them walked further away, a layer of faint, black mist suddenly appeared around the mushrooms. The mists entwined together, revealing a sense of unstable, restless movement.

Boom!

A fierce explosion broke out along with a growl, and soon, the entire spirit mining area fell apart. Suddenly, a commotion started among the mining workers who were still mining. A glimpse of happiness flashed through a portion of workers who participated in the plan.

“They must succeed!” A middle-aged man prayed quietly. “You must escape! White Winter, Clint, and Baylon. We will only be rescued if all of you escaped. They must… they must…”

Suddenly, the sky of the entire mining area became darker. A huge, black mech broke out of the ground, flying into the sky and remained floating.

“My secret chamber!! You rats, how dare you!!”

He reached out his huge hands that were about ten meters long before grabbing at the ground tightly.

However, a blinding white beam of light suddenly rushed into the sky, making a huge hole in his palm. The black mech took a few steps backward due to the pain and roared furiously.

“Relic Light! Damn it!”

Soon, a large number of black spirit mechs filled the air, they began hitting against the beam of light fearlessly with long-ranged weapons. A variety of weapons exploded in the beams of light, filling the sky with a colorful, dazzling radiance. In that instance, other than the white beams of light, nothing could be seen clearly. The light bypassed all the barriers, going straight into the sky.

Hiss…

The light pierced through the layers of clouds in the sky, and numerous white clouds orbited around the pillar of light. It was sacred; it seemed as though a holy light shining down from heaven.

“My treasure! No!” The fierce, red eyes on the Spirit King’s helmet shone brightly. However, all he could do was watch as the beam of light leave through the sky. He had no way of stopping it.

***********************

“Hahahaha!! We succeeded!! When I, the Lord, make a plan, there’s no way that it will fail!!” The three of them heard the sound of Red Moon’s boastful laughter ringing in their ears.

Among the white beam of light, a scarlet, gigantic mech was formed. The mech’s head, arms, and legs were covered in ferocious-looking spikes. There was a long, barbed metal tail wagging behind the mech. The tip of the tail was oddly sharp.

“Be careful, I can only form a 1% projection mech for half an hour. The three of you can drive this mech together, but you need to be cautious of the energy consumption. Being injured will consume energy, and using an ultimate skill will also consume energy. If you use up all the energy during a battle, then all of you will be doomed,” Red Moon explained in detail.

“I can’t be bothered with that, can we finally return to the Mother Planet? I can finally take a good rest…” Clint said wearily while he floated in the white light.

“It’s too soon to rest. Let’s get back to the Mother Planet first. Who knows what is happening there right now. We have been out for a few years already.” Baylon said softly.

On the contrary, White Winter was rather sentimental. After all, Planet Gideon was his homeland.

“I miss my sister…” Clint was also a little low-spirited. “I want to eat bread. I wonder if the business of the shop is as good as before…”

“If my brother is here with me…”

“If my brother is here with me…”

Baylon and White Winter said the exact same thing in sync. The both of them instantly stopped and looked at each other strangely. They immediately saw the admiration for their respective elder brothers in each others’ eyes. Due to the similar look in their eyes, they could instantly relate to each other.

The white light wrapped the three of them, and they rapidly flew toward the Negative Space. The Negative Space was different from the Positive Universe as there were bizarre, rainbow-like shadows everywhere. A large amount of light and heat were collected by the Star. Then, it would be condensed to form a huge gravitational force and trails of colorful magnetic fields.

From time to time, nebulous meteorites could be seen exploding out of the celestial bodies.

Instead of attractive forces, the celestial bodies here possessed repulsive forces, and they were shockingly strong. On the contrary, the stars were the smallest among them. The stars resembled light bulbs which had absorbed a large amount of light, heat, and specks of dust in the universe.

“It’s beautiful…” Baylon saw the view through the white light; it was breathtakingly beautiful. “So this is the Negative Space…”

“Hopefully, we can be lucky enough so that we don’t encounter any void creatures. Otherwise, it’ll be troublesome. The void creatures from the Negative Space are the most annoying ones,” Red Moon said cautiously. “If I am as strong as I used to be, I can easily just eliminate them like bugs. However, it’s different now… This mech can’t even compare to 1% of my previous power. And to make it worse, it’s just a projection… and it has a limited energy. If we were to encounter void creatures, all of you will need to depend on yourself…”

After saying that, Clint and the few of them started being vigilant. They were prepared for any sudden changes.

As time went by, the three of them thought that nothing would happen. Just when the light beam of the mech was about to return to the Positive Universe through the Negative Space.

Pff!

Suddenly, a large pale arm heavily slammed onto the beam of light made by the mech.

The arm stretched out of the void darkness with an infinite force.

“I… smell the odor of flesh and blood…” A loud, seemingly ancient voice was heard.

The beam of light was distorted from the heavy slam. Red Moon was beaten out of his mech, falling onto an asteroid on one side.

The huge pale arm wanted to grab them once again as the three of them were still dizzy and confused.

“Move quickly!” Red Moon shouted. “It’s a four-armed giant!! We’re in trouble! We need to run immediately!”

Clint and the others had just regained their composure. Then, they quickly sat on the seats inside the mech, which were linked together by willpower, and relentlessly flew towards a direction.

Clint controlled the movement of the main mech while Baylon coordinated the flow of energy. Meanwhile, White Winter controlled the mech’s tail and special abilities. They did quite well on their first attempt, despite some flaws in their teamwork.

They carefully avoided the huge, pale arm the size of an asteroid. Compared to the red mech’s arm, there was a clear difference in their sizes. It was the difference between a human and a fly.

Among the dark universe, a pale, giant with four arms slowly climbed out of the black hole. He had the same facial features as that of a human. He was bald and he wore a black, simple leather skirt. His four arms were stretched out in four different directions. He had a muscular body, looking like the Titans from the mythology.

“Flesh and blood…! Fresh meat!!” The four-armed giant roared in the void language, which was similar to the Ancient Endor language. If Garen was here, he would definitely be able to understand what it was saying. The Ancient Endor and the void creatures had intertwined since a long time ago. Both the parties learned and studied from each other for an extended period of time. It had been so long that nobody knew which one of them had greater influences.

“Wow… what a huge head!” Clint turned around and suddenly saw the four-armed giant’s pinky heading straight toward him as he was driving Red Moon’s mech.

Swoosh!

Red Moon’s mech rushed forward with a bursting high speed, heading back into the white beam of light once again. They riskily escaped from the cumbersome four-armed giant.

“That was so close, I’m scared to death,” Red Moon’s voice was heard once again. “This is the silly four-armed giant. If he hadn’t missed, I’m sure that the four of us would have instantly turned into tiny pancakes.”

Chapter 1104: Tide 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Baylon wiped the cold beads of sweat off her forehead. At that moment, she felt as though she might get hit by the four-armed giant.

Meanwhile, White Winter was so scared that he rolled himself into a ball. Never mind controlling the mech, he could barely even open his eyes to look. All he did was sit in the cockpit motionlessly.

“What did the giant say just now?” Clint asked after recovering from the shock.

“I don’t know. No one understood the void creatures’ language,” Red Moon replied helplessly. “As a matter of fact, living things, like void creatures, are considered wild animals in the universe, just like the wild lion and tigers that you see on your planet. There are some which belong in a protected animal category, and some in a fixed resource category. There are many types of void creatures.”

“There are even reserved void creatures?!” Clint was speechless. To think that the monster, which could destroy a Planet with a slap, needed protection.

“There are in danger, and you should know why,” Red Moon answered casually. “It is normal for the four-armed giant to be as huge as a planet. It is also normal that they are protected since they are very scarce in number.”

Suddenly he noticed something wrong.

Huh?

Red Moon realized that the beam of light was starting to vibrate.

Suddenly, a thought flashed through his mind.

“No… I can’t be that unlucky, right…?”

“What happened?” Clint asked worriedly.

“There can’t be another giant, right…?” Baylon’s heart could not take it anymore.

“No… It might be something even worse than that giant…” Red Moon said dryly.

Before he could even finish his sentence, a rainbow-like light ripple suddenly hit them on their side.

Buzz!

The three of them felt extremely dizzy. They could feel the world spin as they sat inside the mech; they fainted almost instantly.

“The tide of energy! Damn it!” Red Moon’s final roar surged a small spark among the rainbow light before he disappeared.

*********************

On a distant star from the Negative Space.

A huge mech with golden armor quietly watched the red mech being swallowed by the rainbow tide.

“How can Red King, who is merely a low-class Regent Level, compare to your Highness? He’s standing on the wheel of fate,” The golden mech’s eyes which resembled emerald gemstones emitted a faint green fluorescent.

“I really don’t know why the King wants to keep him alive. Isn’t it better to just kill him?”

“Kill him?” Countless flaming stars and substances started tumbling behind the mech. A huge woman’s face, which was about a few kilometers wide, was formed by combining magma and high-temperature gas.

“Fate is a tough nut to crack. Do you think that the Lord hasn’t thought about it? Strangely, whenever the Red King appears, the Lord would lose all intentions of killing for no reason at all. No matter what choices you make, destiny will always make some kind of arrangement. Even if you killed the Red King, there might be some other King hidden somewhere else.”

The huge face behind the mech said slowly.

“Instead of killing him and letting the what is known become an unknown, isn’t it better to keep monitoring him?” The golden mech was thinking about something. “As expected of a King. The Lord’s bold vision is not something that we can compare ourselves to. We would definitely just kill all of our enemies.”

“He could even treat his enemy righteously and fairly. The reason why we are willing to follow him is precisely that of his generosity,” The flaming face said straightly.

“That’s right,” The golden mech nodded.

“Fate is fair, some people are destined to not die. Meanwhile, some people are destined to die in some place. It requires a great price to make any changes because that will change the general thread of events…” The flaming face said lightly.

“My Lord is the way,” The golden mech said calmly.

********************

Mother Planet

Bang!

One of the eyeballs of the Seventh Divine Wind General, who was under Garen’s control, suddenly exploded, turning into something gooey on the floor.

“Ah!” The Divine Wind General cried and screamed, “Kill me!”

“Did it fail again?” Garen withdrew his hand reluctantly. “This is the fifth time already. You’re really lucky that your brain hasn’t become an idiotic mess.”

“Just… Kill me… I!” The Seventh Divine Wind General was covered in blood. His body was so swollen that he no longer resembled a human. He was tortured so badly that foul pus was flowing out of some parts of his body.

“This is the last time,” Garen made up a new plan. “This is really the last time.” He felt himself getting impatient with the modifications toward other foreign beings. When he was in the Totem World, was it not very easy to modify himself? Why was it so difficult to retrieve his memory fluctuations this time?

He could easily solve his own fine body structure, but as for other living beings…

At the end of the day, he placed his hands on the Seventh Divine Wind General’s head and transferred an indescribable fluctuation into his head. Ice Dragon got terribly nervous watching them from aside. He had already stood sufficiently far away, yet he could still hear the painful screams of the Seventh Divine Wind General.

In a short while, Garen opened his eyes.

Bang!

The Seventh Divine Wind General’s other eye exploded.

“Master, I caught the people you asked for,” Turing’s voice traveled through Garen’s mind.

“Bring them in,” Garen’s voice transmitted back to Turing.

“Yes.”

Soon, three people walked into the basement. To be exact, a two-headed werewolf strode down the basement as it carried two people in his arms.

Ice Dragon was familiar with the faces of the two of them.

They were Fila and Remington.

Remington was on the verge of dying. When he saw the Seventh Divine Wind General nailed onto the wall of the basement, his eyes widened instantly, as if his socket was about to tear apart.

“Father… no… no!” He struggled to break free from Turing’s arm.

Garen signaled Turing to release him.

Bang.

Remington immediately rushed over and hugged the legs of the Seventh Divine Wind General.

“Father! How is it possible!” His tears fell and his hands trembled. He gently stroked the swelling wounds of the Divine Wind General.

“Is it Remington?” The Seventh Divine Wind General asked weakly.

“Yes! It’s me!” Remington answered loudly.

He suddenly recalled something. He immediately turned around and kneeled at Garen.

Thump! Thump! Thump! Thump!!

He continuously knocked his head on the ground towards Garen.

“Please! I beg you, please spare my father! Please!” He pleaded while he cried. His forehead started bleeding, and the wounds in his flesh could be seen.

“No!” The Seventh Divine Wind General struggled loudly. “Don’t beg him! Stop begging him!” He tried to grab his son by lifting his hands. However, his was too weak and was unable to do it.

“I’ll stand still… even if I have to die!” He shouted with all the strength that was left in him.

Remington did not stop. He continued to knock his head on the ground, facing Garen.

Garen ignored Remington and looked toward Fila, who had a gloomy look on his face.

“Long time no see, Fila,” He greeted him like an old friend.

“Indeed, it has been a long time,” Fila was very calm; it was probably because he realized that he was bound to die. Hence, he accepted everything and overcame his fear.

“Previously, you used to pick on me and wanted me dead. I have always remembered that time at the hospital,” Garen smiled. “Now I’m here to return the favor.”

“I’m willing to accept anything. It’s just death, isn’t it?” Fila smiled faintly.

“If you kneel down and plea like him, I might consider giving you a chance,” Garen laughed while gently stroking his chin.

“Is it possible?” Fila smiled lightly. “I know experts like you have a very big ego. You held grudges from the way I treated you. If you don’t kill me, will you ever be satisfied?”

“You know me so well!” Garen was slightly surprised.

“No matter what I do, I’ll still die in the end. So, why not just die with a free heart?” Fila was oddly calm.

“Unfortunately, you are not that talented. Otherwise, you might be able to develop into a higher level,” Garen shook his head. He reached out his hand slowly and placed his index finger gently between Fila’s eyebrows.

He was unable to read the memory of an Inherited Level expert, but it should not be that difficult for a Resonance Level.

Sss…

Numerous streams of information frantically swarmed into his mind under the arrangement of the Energy Machinist Imprint.

From the time Fila was born all the way until he became an adult, every battle, how he constantly grew stronger… Fila’s whole life flashed through Garen’s eyes like a movie.

Suddenly, he seemed like he saw something strange.

“Uncle, uncle! Did you bring something delicious for us today?”

A group of children was surrounding Fila at the orphanage. Each of their tiny faces was filled with happy smiles.

“There are gem candies and synthetic sausages, everyone has one~ Slow down!” Fila had a gentle smile on his face that Garen had never seen before as he distributed the candies and food to the orphans.

“If you all still want candies next time, you will need to pass the teacher’s exam. Do you understand!” It was as though Fila was a different person as he warned the orphans.

“Yes!” The children answered together loudly.

As the scenes continued to flash through, Garen saw Fila going to one orphanage after the other without anyone noticing. Initially, Fila openly went to fund the establishments of war orphanages. However, later on, he had to wear a face mask before visiting the orphanage for various reasons.

Gradually, the number of people who knew that he funded orphans had gotten lesser and he became more secretive.

In the peoples’ eyes, he was a sinister, domineering and high-ranking genius of the Blackboard Region. However, when no one was watching, he secretly used a large sum of money to fund the orphans who had lost their families during the war.

Garen withdrew his hands and looked at Fila with a complicated look. At that point, he became a little sluggish from having his memory forcibly retrieved; saliva flowed out from the corners of his mouth.

“Humanity is really complicated…” Garen could not help but feel lamented.

“Didn’t master say that there are yin and yang in people? Everyone will naturally seek a balance between their mind and body. It’s inevitable.” Turing answered respectfully.

“Yeah,” Garen tapped on Fila’s head lightly.

Thump!

The bloody arrow went through the back of his head and instantly pierced into his head. It completely ended Fila’s life.

His body fell onto the ground without making any sound.

“Balance is the natural law of the universe. It’s just that each time I encounter such example, I can’t help but to feel emotional,” Garen turned around and looked at Remington who was unconscious from banging his head on the ground.

He was also touched by the genuine emotions of a ruthless young man from a wealthy background.

“How unfortunate…”

Garen reached out his hand, and a huge, ice-blue jagged mouth appeared on his palm. The mouth spewed out a countless amount of blue silk threads, and part of it headed toward another linked secret chamber.

“One last attempt.”

He closed his eyes.

Sss!

The sounds of the silk threads piercing into the head of the Seventh Divine Wind General’s head as well as the sound of the Grand Duke of Destruction’s head exploding in another chamber could be heard. Both of their vital signs quickly disappeared…

At the same time, countless pieces of colorful light began to cover the sky outside. It was as though the entire sky was filled with a large number of rainbows.

The shadows of dozens of mechs could be seen rushing toward the villa where Garen was located.

Diofie, Fiery Fear, and other utterly old mechs controlled by the Non-falling Level experts have gathered here.

“He is trying to start a disaster! We must stop him immediately!” Fiery Fear’s voice transmitted to everyone that was present. “Go!”

Without any hesitation, dozens of top experts activated their engines, and a large number of Non-falling Lights were shot towards the mountain forest villa in all directions.

Chapter 1105: Tide 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Light Beam! Gather!”

Fiery Fear’s Mech spread its four wings, with bright, red beams of light shooting out of every tip of its wings. The light beams were burning bright, bending as they were aimed toward him, forming a beautiful red Light Sphere.

The Light Sphere kept expanding. Soon enough, everything near the red beams of light had been dyed a shade of red that resembled the searing sun.

“Destruction Laser!”

As though it was being pulled by an unknown force, the Light Sphere suddenly jolted downward.

At the same time, the other Non-falling Levels were trying their best, unleashing all their powers. The bright light that exploded from the Mechs were highly concentrated, shooting different forms of colorful streams downward.

“It’s useless.”

A white-robed man looked up at the Mechs in the sky as he walked out slowly from the villa.

As he spoke, a layer of translucent barrier starting forming in the air, surrounding the villa.

All the attacks that were launched disappeared the second they made contact with the invisible barrier, like pebbles sinking into the water.

“Attack!” A furious voice growled.

All the Mechs promptly increased the energy they released, horrifying streams of colorful, electric current-like lights continued to fall from the sky, crashing into the translucent screen before Garen.

However, Garen took no notice of these people and continued staring at the sky which was becoming a concentrated shade of a rainbow.

“It’s coming…”

His stare was intense.

All of a sudden, a white Light Beam shot down from the sky.

Bang!

The light pillar landed not far away. It was at least a thousand meters wide, as though something was hidden inside the Light Beam.

What followed the Light Beam were actual halos the colors of a rainbow.

The air began to stir as a transparent, vortex-like airstream appeared, while an ear-piercing horn sound rang from the sky.

The entire forest was instantly set on fire, and black clouds swarmed above the sky. The black clouds were pushed to two sides by the white light pillar and the rainbow light, yet it did not want to join back together and cover the sky.

White snowflakes danced across the air, spinning around the white column of light just like streams of rivulets.

The ground shook once again.

“It’s really coming this time!”

Garen held his right arm out, his palms curved, as though he was grabbing on to the white light pillar.

“Star Core Resonance…”

As he mumbled in a hushed tone, streaks of red light began appearing on the ground below Garen’s feet; they quickly gathered like streams of water in Garen’s palms.

The streaks of red light were getting more concentrated as the number of streaks increased.

“He’s extracting the Star Core’s powers! Stop him!” Fiery Fear was considered well-experienced and knowledgeable since he knew what was happening and started panicking.

Soon enough, all the Non-falling Levels had a great increase in their powers. However, they noticed that their attacks were harmless to the opponent’s defensive energy field which served as a barrier.

Disappointment crept onto some of the Non-falling Levels’ faces.

Although the Mechs were glamorous and looked magnificent, they were all useless to Garen at this point. Their powers were like absorbed by an endless hole, vanishing instantly as they made contact with the barrier.

The snow was getting heavier and a light fog was cast upon both the sky and the earth. Everything could not be seen anymore, except the white column of light that was standing tall between heaven and earth.

A layer of frost started creeping up Garen’s body, forming a Scarlet Snow Ice Armor while a pair of gigantic, long ice wings slowly condensed to form behind his back.

All of a sudden, Garen took a step forward.

“True form, reveal!”

He suddenly extended both arms like he was embracing the sky.

********************

In space

The whole surface of the Mother Planet was suddenly covered by an abundant of black speckles.

At this very moment, the speckles were moving about swiftly as though they were alive, being pulled toward each other and finally forming a black dot.

In a flash, the black dot formed a huge Peacock’s eyeball. It stuck its skull out from underneath the ground, its entire body was semitransparent just like Mother Planet’s soul. Slowly, the enormous White Peacock emerged from Mother Planet, its massive body almost covering half of Mother Planet already.

Growl!

The White Peacock growled at somewhere deep in space where the rainbow-like lights were shining.

It was as though there was a reaction, the space rainbow lights, which were originally drifting along the white light pillar toward Mother Planet, suddenly accelerated.

Countless streaks of rainbow streams, that were way bigger than Mother Planet, started surging toward the white light pillar.

Boom!

The rainbow tide slammed against the surface of Mother Planet, completely drowning the White Peacock.

********************

Among the White Lights, Clint and the others were staring wide-eyed at Mother Planet, which was getting nearer and nearer, and the massive peacock above.

“There, there… What a huge peacock! Since when did Mother Planet have such a creepy creature?” Clint gulped as he felt his body tingled.

“How bold!” Red Moon was the first one to see right through everything, “Protecting Mother Planet by itself, isn’t it afraid that the energy tide would wipe out its Willpower?” He exclaimed.

It should be noted that the size of an energy tide would vary from small ones to huge ones, and this time around, its scale should exceed hundreds of light years. Merely as big as a small toy ball in a big tide, the Mother Planet was completely unnoticeable. A tide like this had a power that could not be simply defended against by one simple planet.

“Be prepared, we’ll be landing soon!” Little did Red Moon realize that this tide would not actually involve Mother Planet, but he and his men provoked this happening with their Light Beam.

Red Moon’s red Mech was launched toward Mother Planet along with the streak of white light, stumbling among the countless rainbow streams.

*********************

On the Satellite

The lady in a white skirt was staring silently at the rainbow tide that was spreading throughout the entire view of space.

Then, she looked at the White Peacock that was peacefully settling on Mother Planet.

“Level Nine huh?” She mumbled. “No.3.”

A black shadow appeared behind her in the wooden cabin once again and flew out before landed right behind the lady.

“Ready for your commands, ruler.”

“Where’s Carthage? Inform him about what’s happening here, his pawn has been growing a bit too fast.” The ruler spoke calmly.

“Just inform him?” No.3 responded.

“What are you planning to do then?” The ruler asked back again. “I’m not in charge of the region where Chinande is at.”

“Whether he’s Jeros or Nonosiva, wouldn’t it be easier if we just kill whoever gets in the way of our plan?” No.3 asked coldly. “It’s very common for accidents to happen in the Energy Tide…”

The ruler was silent.

Neither one of them spoke for a couple of minutes.

“We’d have a lot of problems once he manages to break the holy bond and becomes a sacred body,” No.3 spoke again.

“We need to consider Carthage’s situation. After all, he’s still one of Chinande’s clones. Nobody would know whether he’s actually speaking for Chinande,” The ruler said.

“Just one of the three hundred and forty-two clones.”

“But this is different.”

No.3 let out a laugh.

“Even if he manages to break the holy bond and become a sacred body, do you think he actually stands a chance to surpass Regent Level? Do you think he can actually rebel against His Majesty?”

“Well, technically, he’d be on the same level already… Regent Level and Perpetual Motion Level, they’re both sacred bodies theoretically, but one has the condensation concept whereas the other one doesn’t. However, in reality, the contrast between these two isn’t as big as we imagine it to be.” The ruler retorted.

“Then why don’t you agree to just kill him now?” No.3 asked curiously.

“Because of me.”

All of a sudden, a figure that resembled fresh blood darted out from a dark corner of space far away, landing beside both the people within seconds, blowing up a mass amount of flowers and plants around the area.

The figure crashed down like a lightning, but soundless.

The newcomer was a fair-skinned lady all dressed in a Blood Robe. Although her gorgeous dress up was elegant and enchanting, she had countless red-black airstreams that had faces encircling her, adding a sense of intimidating power to her presence.

She was the Wraith Royalty’s princess, also Jeros’ sister, Fresh Blood Holy Lord.

A hint of fear flashed on the ruler’s usual cold and heartless expression while her body tensed up, her fingers clenched around the book tightly as though she was ready to move.

“So, it’s Fresh Blood Holy Lord, your Royal Highness. We apologize for not welcoming you, please forgive us.”

Fresh Blood Holy Lord, the number one powerhouse of the Wraith Royalty, was also a highly qualified Holy Lord.

Even though they were the same level as Perpetual Motioners and Regent Level, only a real insider would know that Regent Level was actually the strongest of them all after battling against the Holy Lords after so many years. They represented the ruling over this big piece of land, so they were addressed as the Kings by the Holy Lords.

This was also how Regent Level originated. The concept, in fact, was the common ground that people have discovered from those Regent-Level powerhouses.

There were no longer any specific classifications of combat levels in the Holy Lord Level, only the gap between one’s combat power. Therefore, one would have to kill his own way to gain reputation and status. The so-called Concept Level was just another term for Regent Level.

Fresh Blood Holy Lord, who was standing right across, was one of the few Overlords from Wraith Royalty who would be qualified to enter the elite Regent Level! She challenged the Finite King of the previous generation thrice, and even though she failed, she retreated in good form. Moreover, the Wraith Royalty was able to retain its ruling area mainly because of her support and help.

“Fresh Blood Holy Lord, your Royal Highness, you’ve come here personally, is it because you have decided to deal with your brother?” No.3, on the other hand, was not afraid of her at all. After all, he was just a mere clone over here, and he was hidden well, so the other party would have no clue as to who he really was.

As he finished speaking, Fresh Blood Holy Lord’s appeared before him phantom-like; one arm pierced into his chest.

Bang!

No.3 instantly collapsed into a wisp of smoke and vanished into thin air.

“Suspicious little bastard.”

A malicious look was written on the Fresh Blood Holy Lord’s face. She held out her finger and stared at the droplet of fresh blood on the tip of her finger, before leaning in to lick it.

“Aren’t you going to do something about Jeros’ behavior? He’s already violated the plan. If we don’t do deal with it, the King is definitely not going to ignore the fact that the plan is being ruined…” Bang!

After the blow, the ruler’s body flew backward due to the force of impact, crashing into the wooden cabin, even smashing through the wooden door. She could not be seen after the crash, just a vague view that she was trying hard to get up from the ground.

“Are you trying to pressure me by naming the White King?!” Fresh Blood Holy Lord did not even bother to turn to look at the ruler, instead, she kept her confused gaze on the massive White Peacock resting above Mother Planet.

“Why is Jeros’ qi so weak? He still wants to absorb the energy tide’s energy?” She was getting more confused by the second, but a spiteful crept up her face. “He’s no doubt my idiotic younger brother. Just a short period of time of not seeing him and he’s perished once again! To be so weak until this point, he is a disgrace to the Wraith Royalty!”

She slowly stretched out her jade-like slim fingers.

“Let me teach you what sort of attitude you should possess to exist in this universe as a Wraith Royalty!”

A clump of metallic red blood started burning in her palm.

Boom!

Unexpectedly, she flung her arm at the only huge star in the solar system, Mother Planet.

She then clutched her fist.

Buzz!

The entire star started shaking violently before bursting into red flames suddenly. It was like an ignited solar particle, burning with a bright blood-red shade.

“There you go! Ha ha ha ha!” Fresh Blood Holy Lord enjoyed the immense heat of the star, her body was getting more excited, as though it was being recharged. A vast amount of fresh blood energy started surging into her body and she began laughing wildly.

With a loud boom, a terrifying clump of bloody inflammation burst out from her body and rushed into the sky. At that instant, the entire small planet shook and moved directly out of its original trajectory, flying toward the star.

“My stupid younger brother! Are you trying to take everything? Let me, the Holy Lord, gift you something huge!” Fresh Blood Holy Lord was laughing hysterically, “If you can’t swallow everything, you can die!”

Inside the wooden cabin.

“Crazy! That crazy person! She wants to destroy the entire galaxy!”

The ruler was so overwhelmed by the gigantic amount of energy that she could not even look forward. They were both Holy Lord and Perpetual Motioner Level, yet the difference of powers between them was as different as heaven as hell!

“The King will never forgive you!! You are the one who destroyed the plan…” She yelled, spitting out a mouthful of blood as she spoke.

Chapter 1106: Tide 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The enormous planet was approaching, the scorching heat of the Sun was getting unbearable. As the distance closed up, everyone on the Mother Planet could feel the terrifying heat that was escalating by seconds.

Garen was the first one to sense this alarming change.

As the Hellfrost Peacock, he had already fully converted his Scarlet Snow Ice Armor into its true form by then. Although the Hellfrost Peacock’s true form might only just be a phantom, it was devouring a vast amount of pure energy from the energy tide that moment. The surge of energy would have been considered deadly to an ordinary person. However, for the Hellfrost Peacock’s almost immortal physique, it was nothing.

The gigantic White Peacock phantom continued devouring the crazy amount of rainbow energy.

As for those Non-falling ones surrounding Garen, they could not even survive in the energy tide for ten minutes before all their powers were thoroughly wiped out.

If it was not for Garen’s qi protecting these two regions, absorbing all the energy from the tide that kept rushing in, all the Willpower powerhouses of these two regions would have been completely wiped out by the deadly tide, everyone’s Willpower completely destroyed.

His Scarlet Snow Technique continued surging as it slowly increased.

All the veins on Garen’s body could be seen surfacing his skin and he looked absolutely terrifying.

Black clouds swirled above him, on top of that was the Hellfrost Peacock’s massive body. However, the only thing that could be seen at the moment was the white stream of chill churning in the air, and that was actually one of the Hellfrost Peacock’s blood vessel moving. The peacock’s body could not be seen at all.

The whole rainbow tide was basically blocked out by this white stream of chill.

At that moment, all the Non-falling ones realized that something was wrong – the people they were attacking seemed to be the one actually protecting this region. Each of them stared speechlessly at the other, then fell to the floor in despair. They did not know what to do, other than just observe silently by the side.

The Ice Dragon and the others, who just walked out of the villa, were also shocked at the changes in the sky. It was as if Heaven and Earth were revolving around Garen.

As the white snow melted outside, the ground was once again covered by a new layer of white snow. The forests, which were once luscious, had now wilted, from the original emerald-green to the current shade of burnt black, and they were all covered by the white snow.

This sort of great change in the world, such extraordinary dissipation of the world, definitely marked everyone’s heart deeply, and it would be something unforgettable forever.

Right then, Garen’s qi swiftly broke through the Non-falling Level’s Grade Fifteen Scarlet Snow Technique, and it immediately advanced to Grade Sixteen, and it was still increasing as it continued absorbing energy from the tide. (TL Note: Author wrote ‘Level Sixteen’ but this seems to be a typo, it should be ‘Grade Sixteen’)

In just a few minutes, he managed to break through Grade Sixteen, and a dazzling Frost Seed slowly appeared behind him.

The seed seemed like an ice sculpture, round and delicate, and it was slowly planted into the void. Within seconds, it sprouted and a white, icy vine grew out, weaving something that seemed like a screen.

“Grade Seventeen…” Garen closed his eyes and felt the growth of the Frost Seed. At the same time, a Soul Seed that represented the extreme Hellfrost Peacock started forming in his mind.

This Soul Seed seemed to be different from the ordinary Soul Seeds. It was not just merely illusory, but it had a vague trace of pure Willpower that should only be possessed by Energy Machinists and Pilots.

He should embed a trace of Willpower of Origin into the Soul Seed!

This was the brand new path of improvement that the Scarlet Snow Sect ancestors had opened up in order to bypass the board.

The highest achievements of the Ancient Endors, the Soul Seed and the world’s most powerful power, the Willpower of Origin, this two balanced everything.

“Semi-Soul… Who knew…” Little did Garen suspect that the Scarlet Snow ancestors would actually use such a method to break through the limits, to enter the Level-Nine realm of the same grade as the board.

The tremendous amount of energy from the tide continued gushing into Garen’s peacock. At this point, he was not devouring his own will anymore, but the tide was just pushing into the peacock’s body. He did not have to devour the energy anymore, all he needed was to absorb the consumed energy.

Right at that moment, the most horrifying fact of the Hellfrost Peacock revealed itself.

Garen could sense it himself. As his powers continued to rise, the Hellfrost Peacock’s digestive ability increased just as well.

The energy that was first consumed by his body was still barely able to be digested, however, it was more than adequate now.

It was indeed the Ancient Endors’ rampant creature. That incredible digestive ability was simply the strongest point of the Hellfrost Peacock that was known for its immortality.

Ding!

At this moment, Garen heard a soft sound behind him that sounded like glass clinking against each other.

The vine that grew out from the Frost Seed was slowly weaving into a delicate, huge screen, and it was almost done. Numerous ice crystals growing along the vines shimmered a fluorescent white. Looking from a distance, Garen seemed to have a gigantic piece of vine-made screen that was glinting in white on his back.

The original ice-crystal wings were pushed aside to the back of the vine-made screen.

Crack…

The white, icy crystal vines on Garen’s back continued growing frantically toward all directions. Soon enough, almost the entire sky, which was about thousands of kilometers wide, was fully covered. Both the sky and the ground were filled with mesh vines of ice crystals.

The black clouds were long gone from the sky. At this moment, the Sun was getting nearer and the temperature was rising.

Without even sensing the changes to his own self, Garen raised up his head and looked at the sky.

“This… This is!?” He could actually sense that the Sun was slightly redder and it was diving toward Mother Planet!

“The Sun is getting nearer!”

Fiery Fear and his men also noticed that something was off.

No instruments were able to function right then as the energy particles storm was too big of a disturbance. Only their eyes and senses remained.

“If this continues, the entire Mother Planet will perish!!” Diofie mumbled. All of a sudden, he started panicking and became an utter mess. Under such natural disasters, he had no idea at all what to do despite being the leader of the region.

“What in the world is this!!?” Fiery Fear roared furiously, but his voice was drowned by the endless surge of energy disruption, only to be transmitted within the range of a hundred meters beside him.

This moment, everything came to his mind. His family, children, academy, brothers, best friend, wife… Every familiar face that he knew floated through his mind.

“Oh my goodness! God, why are you punishing me…” Fiery Fear was stunned by the chain of changes that was happening, it was all too overwhelming for him. As the distance between them and the Sun that was closing in, he had zero reaction despite the end of the world being imminent.

Facing such a natural disaster, if the Sun did not return to its own position, the entire Mother Planet would be thoroughly scorched; nobody would stand a chance of surviving through it.

Not just him, every single one of those powerhouses sent to suppress Garen was weak on the ground with their stagnant eyes wide open, not knowing what to do.

No matter how strong they were, they had no chance going against such a powerful force.

Unconsciously, everyone’s eyes paused on Garen.

“It must be him! He must be the one who triggered this doomsday!”

“If we can kill him, everything will return to normal!”

A ferocious grin appeared on each of their faces.

“Let’s not waste any more time! Move, everyone! Let’s get rid of this demon!”

One of them leaped up and dashed toward Garen.

Crack crack…!

A chill started creeping up from beneath the person’s feet before rapidly spreading as it crept upward. He was soon frozen, his eyes wide opened with disbelief. As he stood in the block of ice, his body started corroding swiftly just like a candle.

Everyone was shocked at this sight.

Right then, Garen simply ignored those people.

He was engrossed in devouring the heat from the approaching star.

The terrifying thermal tide was mixed among the energy tide, but the Solar Seeds, which were tougher to be digested compared to the energy tide, was still pouring into his body.

Most of the energy that was emitted by the Sun itself was not just pure energy. They mostly required a longer period of time for one to absorb and convert them into Cold Energy. This was why Garen did not choose to absorb the star.

All of a sudden, a bright white light burst out of his body and he entered the Eighteenth Grade of Scarlet Snow Technique completely.

Cough!

However, at the same time, Garen suddenly coughed out a mouthful of fresh blood.

That was the sign of his body was damaged by all sorts of gas substances that were mixed along the star.

Cold Energy and Thermal Energy were battling against each other. These two entirely different energy were high up in the sky, constantly colliding with each other between Mother Planet and the Star.

The massive gravitational force gradually diffused around. Garen could no longer hold against the control of the gravitational force. Besides the protected villa region, everything around him collapsed instantly, turning into a black abyss.

The villa basically became an island.

“Who is it!” Garen remembered clearly that he did not see anything about the star back then. “Who is it!?”

He felt an excruciating pain all over his body, waves of pain were transmitted from his Hellfrost Peacock’s body.

His Willpower was slightly blurred… But the star was still getting nearer.

The Hellfrost Peacock’s digestive system finally collapsed. After all, it was not the actual Hellfrost Peacock Queen but a mere phantom. A result like this was already way beyond Garen’s imagination.

“It’s Sister!! It’s Gersa!! Hahahaha!!!” A sudden laughter rang through Garen’s head. To his surprise, it was Jeros, the one who was once devoured by the Nine-headed Dragon’s Soul.

Turns out he had yet to perish, the remnants of his Will just regained consciousness, fully taking advantage of Garen’s currently-weak state.

“You’re doomed! Doomed!” Jeros continued to laugh hysterically.

Although his last piece of soul would soon be devoured by the Nine-headed Dragon once again, he did not seem to mind.

Garen’s will was still blurred.

The star was not just destroying Mother Planet at this moment, its primary target was actually him.

The immense gravitational pull of the star had completely locked on to him. He had no way to escape or dodge, he could only keep resisting!

Cracks could be seen on the Semi-Soul that was just condensed as it was being placed under extreme force right now.

“I… How can I die here…” Garen’s deepest conscious was growling relentlessly. He wanted to break through this monstrous force so badly.

“How is this possible! How can I fall here!!” He bellowed, but still, he was unable to resist the terrifying force pushed upon him.

“You are Scarlet Snow Sect’s last hope! It’s been a couple of thousand years already! How can you fall here!” An angry rumble thundered from the Armor of Ice that Garen was wearing.

The human souls of the early ancestors started flowing out from the armor, spinning around Garen.

“You are destined to be the strongest of Scarlet Snow in the past thousands of years!”

“No! You can’t let Scarlet Snow’s hope die in a place like this!”

“Those in our path shall die!”

All the ancestors were beyond furious, their souls burnt with raging fire. As the souls burn within the Scarlet Snow Ice Armor, an incomparable burst of energy surged within him.

Boom!

The enormous gush of cold air rushed toward the sky, heading straight toward the nearing Sun.

With a hard knock at the side, bursts of fiery lava and rocks flew out. However, it did nothing to stop the steadily-moving Sun that was still heading straight for Mother Planet.

Boom!

Another gush of cold air flew toward the sky, crashing into the star.

Each and every Level Nine Elders’ strengths were showcased, all of them burnt madly as their souls started melting. Their power, combined with Garen’s, shot into the sky.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

Against the continuous ferocious hits, the Sun finally seemed to slow down.

After all, the Level Nine powers had already reached a terrifying state. Plus, Garen was still continuously devouring energy from the tide to convert into Cold Energy to be used as the source of his powers. As long as his body could withstand it, he would have an endless supply of Cold Energy.

The Mother Star, once again, started moving along with each hit.

Finally, the Sun began to move away.

“No… The Mother Planet was the one that moved…” Garen’s Energy Machinist Imprint formed such a conclusion under his current blur state.

Thump.

He fell to the ground.

Everywhere around him was chaos. Other than him, the villa was shattered, the others were frozen icicles, some melted, yet some remained as blocks of ice. Although this attack was not directed towards them, only some were able to survive.

Now, Garen knelt alone at the stone pillar of what was originally the villa. There was nothing around him.

The distance between Mother Planet and the Sun had finally returned to normal, and the Sun was back to its original shade, not the horrifying, bloody-red hue anymore.

Right at that moment, Garen cracked. His blood was frozen by the chill within him as lines of scars started forming all over his body.

The land was yellow, both heat and cold sizzled together, making the entire surface around the pillar and everywhere else akin to a desert.

Chapter 1107: Breakthrough 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On the planet.

Fresh Blood Holy Lord spat quietly.

“So he survived? Damn, that’s too bad for Jeros. You were lucky this time.”

Instead of taking action, she simply tugged off her red blouse and turned into a stream of blood, entering the Void.

It was only after a moment did the ruler start crawling out slowly from the wooden cabin. She exhaled heavily, her entire body covered with injuries.

She lied on her back and stared at the enormous, blue Mother Planet in the sky. There was a huge, black splotch on its surface that seemed like a burn mark caused by a star that got too close to it.

“Mother Planet actually exceeded the energy tide’s range, that’s really terrifying…”

A wisp of black smoke appeared beside the ruler.

“Fresh Blood Holy Lord has already transcended the ordinary Regent Level, hasn’t she? She’s long become her own concept, Fresh Blood.”

The ruler nodded.

“That’s right, Master said it once too. To be able to manipulate the concept of all things, that’s the true Regent Level. Gersa is already capable of controlling the stars. After all, concept-wise, stars have their own blood too.”

“Such powers are beyond the controlling category,” Black Smoke mumbled.

“Don’t worry,” The ruler replied calmly. “She’s going to challenge the King soon, and nobody has ever beaten His Majesty… Herself included. After the battle, if she’s not injured badly, she’s probably going to die. His Majesty has already decided to unify everything.”

“Really?” Black Smoke responded.

*******************

Garen kneeled on the scorching sand; his body no longer felt chilly. The Hellfrost Peacock was thoroughly charred by the star’s alarmingly high temperature, it was incapable of emitting and trace of chill at the moment.

Hu…

He let out a deep breath.

The Scarlet Snow armor had disappeared already, all the ancestors’ souls completely thawed. In order to fight against the star, they focused the powers of all their souls and converted them into pure strength. They charged forward with no hesitation.

This also became the key that gave Garen the strength to push through everything. Garen felt dejected, the Scarlet Snow Sect ancestors did entrust all their hopes on him after all. This was a heavy obligation that he must perform.

Crack…

The ice crystal vines on Garen’s back began to crack, shattering onto the ground.

Crack!

One of the shards fell before him.

He reached out and grabbed the shard of glass fuzzily.

Chi!

All of a sudden, a massive, sturdy blue pillar of light burst out from the debris, piercing right through Garen’s chest.

The light pillar penetrated into the sky as the sky rumbled non-stop, stirring up the clouds once again in the clear peaceful sky.

Chi, chi, chi!

At the same time, sharp rays of blue light burst out from almost all the shards, forming light pillars that all pierced into Garen’s chest from all directions.

From afar, it looked like ten or more blue spears were securing Garen on the sand so that he could not move at all.

Whoosh…

Garen reacted surprisingly quick, immediately activating his potential points and swiftly piling them on his body so he could recover instantly.

However, those blue lights were not doing actual damage to his energy.

Stunned, Garen extended his arm and touched his chest. He felt no pain where the blue light just pierced through, but an indescribable comfort instead.

“This is…?”

He stared at his Attribute Pane, confused.

To his surprise, what was supposed to be his original Attribute Pane was currently going through some earth-shattering changes.

What was initially a dark mist of mystical genes were now completely crystal clear.

The dark mist dissipated, revealing from within was a mysterious white-gold symbol.

The symbol was extremely complex and it seemed like a merge of multiple symbols laying on top of each other.

“What is this?”

The instant the symbol formed completely, all the blue threads from the Hellfrost Peacock within him started swarming toward the symbol, immediately cocooning and devouring it by gulps.

Boom…

Just that moment, a ball of blue flames exploded from his body.

A steady flow of energy that seemed to appear out of nowhere started flowing into Garen’s mind where the Soul Seed was at.

A brand new Soul Seed was then slowly condensed deep in Garen’s mind, side by side with the other Soul Seed.

His Attribute Pane then slowly updated a new display.

‘Soul Seed — Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, Holy Phoenix Demon Book. Hellfrost Peacock Soul Seed .’

The three Soul Seeds interweaved and formed a trace of translucent current that seemed to be interchained, but nevertheless suspended on air itself.

Blue, black-gold, and white. The three Soul Seed s formed a triangular chain altogether and started spinning slowly.

The seemingly never-ending energy seemed to be emitting from those three Soul Seeds. It was as if the three Soul Seeds were deriving a completely new strength out of themselves.

Within seconds, that power filled Garen’s body to the brim, and yet it was still eagerly surging into his body.

The immense force washed upon Garen’s body wave by wave.

The tremendous force was incomparable, far from what he felt from the oppression of the star earlier on. Garen felt as if he was back to how he was as an ordinary person, with a balloon that was expanding non-stop within him, as if he was going to explode.

The change this time around seemed to have connected the powers of all three of the Soul Seeds’ powers, erupting a new unusual derivative energy at the same time. This derivative energy was so pure, and it was able to draw an endless supply of external energy.

The immense force caused Garen’s entire body to crack, as fresh, scarlet-red blood started trickling down.

A spaceship far away that was on the way to observe was slowly approaching, rays of light beams shining in his direction.

“There seem to be people there, let’s go over and check if they’re survivors.”

“Spaceship No.2 ruling out all danger.”

“No.3 alert.”

Signals started interchanging in the air.

“Hank, pass me the focus stick.”

“Alright, no problem. Hmm… What is happening, why is it shining all of a sudden?”

“Oh… Oh, no! Oh, my goodness!! Run!”

Without a sound, a ray of pure white light suddenly flared up, covering a radius of approximately a thousand meters. The Mechs that just exited the spaceship to check out the surroundings were not spared as well, vanishing instantly within the white light.

Garen could not hold it in anymore and completely exploded.

His body detonated and became pieces of white-blue flesh, bursting into all directions in the white light.

In just mere seconds, they all spread to a couple of thousand kilometers of space.

Instantly, numerous white light mixed with flesh quickly solidified, forming the actual White Hellfrost Peacock.

The peacock’s form lasted for only a mere second before vanishing straight away, once again covered up by the bright white light.

**********************

Garen had another dream, a very long dream.

In the dream, he was a gigantic peacock from the depths of space. The moment he was born, he swallowed a nearby star. Countless chill flowed in the air, freezing every star that it met.

The ice-cold space was the perfect place for it to grow.

Its natural ability to devour Celestial Bodies one by one was to replenish the energy consumption consumed by its body that was constantly expanding.

It would meet the occasional Celestial Bodies that would explode in resistance, but that was nothing different from drinking a soda, they were just bubbles bursting in its mouth, bringing about little to no threat.

Time was meaningless, its colossal gravitational force had distorted time already.

Multiple years passed, even it did not know how many years.

Strange creatures started appearing one by one. They each had a head and four legs. They looked hideous, but they did have strong powers Every one of them was comparable to a star.

These creatures gradually increased. At first, all they did was observe quietly, and after it ate a few of them, the others soon left.

But it was not long before they returned, and this time around they were stronger.

They could let it fall asleep. Those kinds of sleep that were comfortable and relaxing.

Gradually, it realized that it enjoyed sleeping.

Soon enough, its brain slowly started to get foggy, as if it spent too much time sleeping. Too long… It’s too long…

Hu!

All of sudden, Garen woke up from the dream.

He opened his eyes to a lush, green forest before him.

Turing was not far away roasting a huge, wild boar. Noticing that Garen has awakened, this loyal Two-Headed Big Wolf immediately rushed toward him.

“Master, you’ve finally woken up!” Turing’s face was haggard and full of scars, some even slightly rotten, revealing his white bones. It was evident that the war was over for a long period of time already.

He carefully helped Garen up.

“Here, drink some water.”

Feeling thirsty, Garen gulped down a few mouthfuls of water from a metal bottle. It tasted sweet.

“Alright, I can help myself,” Slowly, Garen sat up.

He swiftly activated his potential points. However, he noticed that his points were completely consumed.

On the other hand, numerous conspicuous state symbols appeared on his Status Pane. With just a glance, he could sense a trace of information.

‘Hellfrost Peacock growth: Three Army-Level Soul Seeds’ Dimensional Dream ability triggered the extreme Hellfrost Peacock ultimate body — Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s evolution, but the evolution requires an unimaginable energy growth… Progress is now 5%.’

Garen suddenly remembered something Black Sethe mentioned once.

‘As long as three Soul Seeds are used as fuel backup, it’s possible to push the limit of one’s secret technique to the next level.’

“As expected, the three Soul Seeds really did cause a big change. Perhaps the mysterious gene symbol did some work as well. My Hellfrost Peacock has reached its peak already, though now it’s having a brand new breakthrough. It’s really changing into Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s form…”

Garen was amazed as he glanced toward his other states, sweeping through most of the useless skills and immediately pausing his gaze when he found the key pane of his Cold Scarlet Snow Technique.

‘Eighteenth Grade Cold Scarlet Snow complete: gestures endow the ninth level peak power of frost aura. (Frost strengthened by three levels, sharpness strengthened by three levels, purity strengthened by three levels,)’

There was another symbol at the back that was white. Garen moved his sight and immediately sensed the message.

‘Cold Chaos strengthened increment. Full attribute enhanced by 1’

Chapter 1108: Breakthrough 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The instant Garen sensed this symbol, it had already melted abruptly, rapidly merging into the Scarlet Snow Technique’s pane.

And the Scarlet Snow Technique also changed once more.

‘Eighteen Grade Cold Scarlet Snow: every move contains cold energy equivalent to the peak of Level Nine.

(Coldness Strengthening Level Four, Sharpness Strengthening Level Four. Purity Strengthening Level Four.)’

“So all the Strengthening abilities increased by one level? Not bad. After devouring so much energy, not only did it condense the Soul Seed of the Living Secret Technique, it even influenced the Scarlet Snow Technique to increase as well.”

Garen had inherited many of his forefathers’ memories, so he knew how strong the chill would be once he reached Grade Eighteen of the Scarlet Snow Technique.

Out of all the forefathers, the strongest was the First Generation Forefather, his Eighteen Grade Scarlet Snow Technique had increased the Coldness Strengthening to Level Three. His Purity Strengthening had also reached Level Three. He did not have Sharpness Strengthening, but even so, he had already reached an extremely terrifying level.

No one would protest if you were to call him one of the top ten users of frost among the Energy Machinists. He would certainly have a spot among the top ten strongest frost users.

Unfortunately, although he was extremely powerful in his time, and brought an era of glory to the Scarlet Snow Sect, none of his successors ever reached his level. Some of the forefathers had reached the eighteenth grade, and condensed their Soul Seed, but no one could reach Level Three in their Strengthening levels anymore. This was especially true of the Coldness Strengthening, they found countless materials, used all sorts of techniques and technology, but could only ever strengthen themselves up to Level Two. As for Purity Strengthening, they could also only reach Level Three.

As such, the Scarlet Snow Sect’s position started to drop from its initial status as a middle-grade sect.

Now, Garen had once more raised his Scarlet Snow Technique to Level Three in terms of Strengthening, and had even achieved Level Four.

This power was already unprecedented in the history of the Scarlet Snow Technique.

The last thing was the most crucial, the Attribute Pane.

‘Nonosiva Lin – Strength 50, Agility 50, Vitality 50 (+8), Intelligence 42, potential power 0%. Soul Limit 50.’

Other than his Intelligence, everything else had reached fifty. His Soul Limit had also reached fifty. Garen was not surprised at that, he had always planned to condense the Scarlet Snow Technique’s Soul Seed, but he had not expected that he would gather the Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s one instead. Evidently, out of the two frost-type techniques, the Scarlet Snow Technique could not be placed on the same pedestal as the Living Secret Technique. Therefore, his understanding of the frost-type ended up benefiting his Hellfrost Peacock Technique.

Sitting up straight, Garen pulled back his attention, and only then did he realize how much he had benefited from this. It was way beyond his expectations.

“Where is this?” Garen pulled back his gaze, and began to consider his surroundings.

“Master, this is still the Mother Planet, I carried you out of the middle of the Battlefield. We did not go far, because I was worried we would be found by the search parties,” replied Turing respectfully. “You have been unconscious for three days. All our equipment and tools have been rendered ineffective by the battle’s energy field, so we could not simply leap away, and had to temporarily wait here for you to awaken.”

“Is that so?” Garen nodded, and put down the canteen.

He glanced at the torn-up rags on his body, and saw that his Space Equipment had also been utterly destroyed, rendered completely useless. He knew immediately that the things inside had all floated into the torrents of Space.

“This is still the Blackboard Region, right?” he asked.

“That’s right, we did not go too far,” replied Turing honestly.

“How would we go about returning to Planet Scarlet Snow from here?” Garen was not familiar with this aspect.

“I’m afraid we would need to borrow a jump portal, and go to the Central Academy first, then find a decent Galactic Battleship before we can leave,” Turing replied according to the usual conventions.

“No, we don’t need to do that. The Energy Machinists still have a base in the radiation area, we can go straight to the base and use the portal there to jump to the City of Nagadako. That was how I did it last time.” Garen shook his head, and reestablished another route.

“But before we go, we should go see the situation on the Mother Planet first.”

Finally, he exhaled deeply.

“I wonder how many of these people survived.”

The two of them ate some barbequed meat, and then rapidly flew out from the forest, enveloping themselves in Non-Falling Light. In an instant, they had become a flash of white light, disappearing into the sky.

Fifty points of speed had already long surpassed what the average person could detect. Even some equipment would be hard-pressed to detect them.

After they flew through the air for some time, Garen quickly caught sight of a black battleship in the distance.

The battleship was shaped like a Torpedo Ship, and had the words ‘Maria Region’ printed on it.

He flew straight for it, approaching the battleship as fast as lightning, and reached his hand out to grab it.

Scree!

He basically tore a hole through the outer layer of the battleship.

Garen and Turing walked straight inside. They stood in the white corridors of the spaceship, the red alarms above their heads blinking brightly and wailing sharply.

“Control this ship, but don’t kill all who resist, leave some alive so they can steer the ship,” Garen instructed carelessly.

“Understood.”

Turing nodded, and immediately wrapped himself up in Non-Falling Light, crashing hard into the walls of the corridor.

Boom.

The alloy wall caved in, twisting and bending toward the sides, revealing their sharp metallic sides.

Turing walked in quickly, and dashed toward the front of the ship.

Garen strolled through the spaceship slowly, feeling the tremors coming from it.

Soon, there were quick footsteps coming from up ahead.

“Over here! The intruders are here.”

A woman’s voice kept saying.

All of a sudden, Garen sensed that Turing’s presence seemed to have been suppressed.

“Hm?” He was instantly interested. No matter what, Turing was still a Non-Falling-Level fighter, even though he was weaker than regular Non-Falling Levels, and had fewer skills or abilities, he was still not an opponent an Inherited Level could take. And now, he was actually being suppressed.

“But we can’t afford any delays now, we need to determine where we are, and we can borrow this spaceship’s data storage and topographic map for that.” Once he thought of that, he stopped his leisurely stroll, and strode instead toward the footsteps coming at him.

He walked down the silver-white metallic corridor and turned the corner. At the crossroads, Garen saw a group of young women dressed in golden clothing, jogging toward him while holding High-Energy Destruction Guns.

And the person at the very front, leading the pack, was actually a familiar face – Zero-Gun Sue-Anna.

Her signature crepe-like long golden hair was extremely eye-catching, add that to her gentle but strong-willed aura, and Garen instantly recognized her with just a glance.

Of course, Garen recognized her, but she did not know Garen at all.

Ka-chak!

They all raised their guns in unison. Before the team members who were about to shoot managed to pull the trigger, Sue-Anna held her arms open and stood in front of the nozzle.

“Nobody shoot!” she yelled loudly and abruptly. Her expression was abnormally nervous, her large and pretty eyes staring at Garen intently, unblinking.

Garen also lowered his battle-ready right palm.

“I want to borrow your topographic map, and head for the Blackboard Region’s Blackboard City. That’s okay, right?”

“S-sure.” Sue-Anna had broken out into a slight cold sweat, and replied hurriedly. “Wherever you want to go, sir, we’ll happily escort you there.”

She could now sense the terror of Garen’s power. After all, Garen was emitting a wisp of his aura, without any attempt to hide it.

“That’s best.”

Garen nodded in satisfaction.

Seeing that Garen was not very violent, Sue-Anna also heaved a sigh of relief. She signaled for the members behind her to retreat quickly, and ignoring her subordinates’ worried gazes, she slowly approached Garen.

“May I invite you to move to the reception room, sir? Are you heading to Blackboard City? We happen to have some people from Blackboard City on board, and we just happen to be heading there now.”

Seeing that Sue-Anna was being considerate, Garen decided not to press her any longer, and called Turing to pull back.

Anyone who could suppress Turing on this ship had to be a Non-Falling-Level powerhouse, and it was impossible for Maria to have that many Non-Falling Levels, so it was very likely that this ship was their main force, holding all of their elites. He just happened to bump into it.

“Oh, yeah, how did you recognize me?” Garen knew the look in her eyes, she was clearly not unfamiliar with him.

Sue-Anna laughed awkwardly.

“When you were at the Polar Region… we all saw your image, sir.”

“Oh.” Only then did Garen completely understand.

Nothing much happened on the airship, and soon they had reached the Blackboard Region. Along the way, other than Sue-Anna, nobody else came to disturb Garen, she was the only one who accompanied Garen with tea and idle chatter.

Clearly, she was worried that if Garen was surrounded by too many people and angered as a result of it, things might end up badly for her. It looked like Sue-Anna harbored no ill intent toward Garen, so he just let her approach him.

When they reached Blackboard City, Garen found a set of casual clothing on the ship, and put them on. Then he led Turing out, again quick as lightning, and instantly vanished down the vast and empty streets of Blackboard City.

On the spaceship, Sue-Anna finally heaved a long sigh of relief.

“At first I had thought that once that Non-Falling Level, Diofie, died, the Blackboard Region would not be able to hang in there. It never occurred to me that… this person was related to Blackboard City…”

“Looks like our original takeover plan needs to change, inform the Royal Region immediately. The Polar Region is over, and if we anger that esteemed man, the next one might very well be us.”

A white-haired old crone appeared from behind Sue-Anna, speaking solemnly with her hands behind her back.

“Try to be as friendly with Blackboard as you can,” sighed the old crone, before turning around and walking into the depths of the spaceship.

****************

Garen first visited Blackboard Academy, and saw that his teacher Van Doe did not seem to be around. However, it looked like he had just left, the coffee on the table was still hot.

After he blocked that terrifying tide that covered the entire Blackboard Region, the Blackboard Region, as well as the neighboring Maria and Polar Regions, all escaped safely. However, the other academies that were further away, such as the Central Academy, all incurred heavy losses. The energy tide could be considered a short one, and had not lasted as long as stated in the original history, but even so, it had severely injured the Willpower powerhouses from the many great academies.

The practitioners of Willpower at different stages had each sustained injuries of varying degrees.

Garen left a letter on the table. After he discovered the truth, he knew that after he and Baylon left, his teacher had been caring for Nono’s relatives. Although he had given up on Garen in the end, he had still fulfilled his basic duties as a teacher.

This energy tide this time was Garen’s repayment to the Blackboard Region.

There was no longer any reason for him to stay here in the Blackboard Region.

Garen led Turing back to the inner parts of the Academy Battleship, and as expected, Diofie had died. Many people were mourning him, gathering together and remembering him in silence, so Garen joined the crowd and watched a while. He soon realized that it was not just Diofie, on the list of the dead persons, it stated that all the Non-Falling-Level powerhouses who had attacked him, including the principal of Central Academy, had perished, without a single survivor.

“True, even I got seriously injured back there, what’s more the rest of them.” As for the grievously-injured Grand Duke of Destruction, Ice Dragon, and the rest, they must surely have all died.

It was a shame, since he had implanted so many Distorted Seeds, but in the face of that catastrophic power, all resistance was futile.

Originally, Garen was confident that he could safely withstand this tide, but he had not taken the star that suddenly appeared at the very end into account.

Judging from what Jeros said, it was highly likely that the previously-unseen star was the doing of Jeros’ older sister, a woman called Gersa.

The members of the Wraith Royalty were selfish, and used whatever means to achieve their ends. Their bonds to each other were extremely shallow, so it was not surprising that Jeros’ sister would do something like that.

But what bothered Garen was that the name Gersa seemed to have shown up before in the original history.

She seemed to have been a main force in the last resistance within Finite borders against the conquer of the White King, and had finally died after she failed in her challenge against the White King.

Chapter 1109: Dark Prologue 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Emerging from the funeral, Garen was still lost in his shock over the tremendous power controlling the star.

He believed that his Scarlet Snow Technique had already reached the very peak, and was now even stronger than that of the First Generation Forefather. And even if he put all his power into it, if he tried to influence a star, unfortunately…

He could influence the Mother Planet, but that did not mean he could move a star.

The Sun’s mass was 290,000 times that of the Mother Planet, can you imagine the difference? It was the difference between a basketball and a grain of rice!

Garen had thought that he was strong enough already, but once he compared it like that…

But in this world, he could no longer grow any stronger. The only hope he had left was on the Hellfrost Peacock Queen, he could sense that he had already reached Army Level, and with this breakthrough, he had completely attained the peak of Army Level. In terms of fighting power, perhaps he was no longer at Level Nine, perhaps he had reached Level Ten, but even he could not be sure.

Back then, the First Generation Forefather had been at the peak of Level Nine. And now, Garen had surpassed him.

Maybe he was even Level Ten now.

Even in this whole universe, Level Ten fighters were a domineering force, many Perpetual Motioners were called saints, but you could not tell who was stronger because they never really fought each other.

As with the Secret Technique World back then, their reputations allowed them to each take hold of a piece of territory. None of them dared to haphazardly attack, or to provoke other Perpetual Motioners.

It would be fine if they could win, but it would also be troublesome if they could not. Since they were all at the same level, the loser would instantly be considered inferior to the winner.

Plus, Perpetual Motioners were extremely hard to kill. The words Perpetual Motion represented a limit, their Timeless Boards could perpetually invoke the power of antimatter, and they could directly absorb the power of antispace. Since time flowed backward in antispace, the Perpetual Motioners basically no longer cared about time. They were immortal, and could influence time, forever maintaining their power at their peak conditions.

When everyone had infinite power like this, the difference came from the disparities in their understanding and abilities.

“I’m now also one of Planet Naga’s Perpetual Motioners, I just don’t know whether the Energy Machinists have a plan to deal with this threat…”

Garen left Blackboard Academy, and finally flew toward the direction of the Seventh Ruins as he remembered it.

That should be the place where Clint and the rest will arrive on the Mother Planet. Nono’s relatives were all dead, and only Baylon was left, so no matter what, he could not allow himself to break this promise as well.

As for as the disciple he had meant to accept, Tesna, she seemed to have passed out from exhaustion, but fortunately Turing managed to carry her away and protect her in time, so she did not die. Just like that, she had also passed Garen’s last test – luck.

Looks like she was pretty lucky, to have survived that apocalyptic disaster despite being a normal human, that was nothing short of a miracle.

“Once I go back this time, I’ll really have to consider how to deal with this incident. And Carthage…” A hint of coldness flashed through Garen’s eyes.

**********************************

Mother Planet, Seventh Ruins

It was a complete wasteland here, and a thick pillar of white light descended onto it from the sky, turning this place into an isolated island.

The ruins in the middle were somehow still there, but everything around it had been completely turned to desert, so from afar, it looked like an island floating in the ocean of sand.

After so many years, Garen had finally returned to this place. Looking at it from a distance, the ruins looked just like they did back then, blurry and foggy, so that he could not quite see what was inside.

The last time he came in here, he was nearly threatened by the terrifying time-space distortion.

“Let’s go. Let’s see that beloved little brother of mine, how long has it been…?”

Garen wore white robes, while Turing and Tesna followed behind him, also dressed in white robes.

“Little brother? Tutor, you have a little brother?” asked Tesna in confusion, she knew next to nothing about Garen.

“Just do whatever Master tells you to do, why are you asking so much?” Turing had also hidden himself in the enormous white robes, and looked almost like a mutated radiation person.

“Okay…” Tesna was the classic airhead-type, and nodded rather embarrassedly when she heard that.

The three of them headed toward the ruins quickly, leaving the scooter they had arrived in not far behind them. The vehicle had been rented from the Blackboard Region.

“Are we just going to leave the scooter there!?” Tesna turned around and looked at it.

“It will go back on its own,” explained Turing exasperatedly.

“It’s automatic? This big thing? Not bad.” Tesna was instantly somewhat surprised. Ever since she woke up, she seemed to have recovered some of her girlhood innocence, and was no longer as cold or distant. Now, she was interested in everything, and curious about everything.

“You’ve always lived in the Regions, and never ventured out into the radiation area, so naturally you would be curious about everything here,” explained Garen with a smile. “Now come with me and don’t delay anymore. My brother is still waiting for us, y’know.”

“Oh…” Tesna instantly fell quiet, and obeyed obediently. This teacher looked all mysterious, and rather than a martial artist, he felt more like a traveller.

She could no longer stay in that family any longer anyway, so she may as well leave the Blackboard Region with this newly-recognized master of hers. That might bring her a new life.

It was just that she would sometimes think of her older brother, and find him hard to forget. Once she left this time, who knew how long it would be until they meet again.

The three of them slowly walked through the desert, toward the ruins.

Inside the ruins, it seemed as though everything unusual has vanished.

There were only bits and pieces of the circus equipment and stage left, whereas the strange factory parts and machines had all vanished.

The Seventh Ruins, once the most mysterious location, had now become just another set of old, regular ruins.

They did not walk for long before catching sight of what looked like a newly-built metallic cottage. It was made of the metal structures readily found here, and looked very simple, but also seemed extremely sturdy.

A red-haired young man was saying something loudly to a young girl with short white hair. The girl had her head lowered shyly, but the young man seemed open and brash.

At the same time, another pretty girl in skin-tight clothes happened to walk out of the house. She wore white jeans, a figure-hugging black top, and had a wide black metallic belt tied around her waist. There were many strange tools sticking out of the belt.

The girl who had come out had her long black hair tied into a ponytail, and her fair skin was covered in oil stains, but her unnaturally perky figure was enough to attract and keep the gaze of any male. It was a completely style from the white-haired girl’s innocent purity, she was full of vigor and strangely sexy.

If anyone looked closer, they might notice that this handsome girl’s aura was rather similar to Garen’s.

As though hearing the footsteps from afar, the trio in front of the metallic house glanced over, their gazes following the source of the sound.

At first glance, all three gazes focused on Turing, who had the strongest sense of presence. Even when shrunken down, he was still two meters tall, and anyone’s gaze would find him first.

Next was Garen.

The instant she saw Garen, the girl with the ponytail dropped the tweezers in her hand with a loud clang.

“Brother!!”

Her face was instantly covered with joy, and she forgot all about the oil stains on her body, rushing toward Garen like a madwoman.

“Big Bro Nono?!” The young man, Clint, was also instantly overjoyed. After all, he had wanted to thank Big Brother Nonosiva in person for a long time now, if it were not for Nonosiva’s interference back then, Clint would not even have been able to escape the Blackboard Region.

Only the white-haired girl looked completely confused.

Garen’s smile was full of relief, thank goodness Baylon was fine.

She really was the last of Nono’s family, if something had happened to her too, then he would have nothing left but feelings of guilt toward the owner of this body that he had possessed.

Seeing that Baylon was overcome with sincere emotions, Garen held his arms slightly open, allowing her to pounce at him.

“Brother!! I heard that you’d gone missing, I looked for so long but I could never find you!! Where did you go!?” Baylon cried tears of happiness, the tears splashing down her face as she pounced straight into Garen’s embrace.

“You really surprised me.” Garen shook his head slightly, feeling Baylon’s soft body that had lost all traces of masculinity.

Instantly, Baylon stiffened up somewhat.

“Big Bro! You can’t blame her for that! There’s a reason Baylon’s like this!” said Clint loudly, hurriedly rushing up to him.

“Of course I know that, otherwise the first thing I would do is give this punk a good beating!” Garen put on a fierce tone. Then he started to carefully observe this future Red King赤之王.

This was the Red King who would eventually be able to go toe to toe against the White King, his power would be stronger than half of the galaxy, but now he just looked like a regular wimp.

“Also, since when have I allowed you to call me Big Bro?” retorted Garen somewhat unhappily. He used Nono’s signature haughtiness and arrogant tone to look down at Clint from above.

“Urk!…” Clint held his forehead and smiled blankly, at a loss on how to reply.

“Oh, yeah, Brother, this is our new friend, White Winter.” Baylon immediately changed the subject, left Garen and ran across to drag White Winter over.

White Winter lowered his head shyly, and was dragged over by Baylon, looking bashful and intimidated.

“C’mon, call him Big Bro!” Baylon pressed his head down, saying loudly.

“B-B-Big Bro…”

He felt a bit like a mob boss…

Garen’s expression was exasperated, and he waved his hand.

“Stop fooling around. How have you guys been recently? After I left the Blackboard Region, how did you guys end up in a place like this? I heard that these ruins are extremely dangerous inside.”

“Uh… about that.” Baylon glanced at Turing and Tesna, “It’s a long story.”

Since Red Moon had some contact with Garen, Clint and the others did not plan to hide it from him, but they were still wary of the two behind him. After all, these matters and incidents were extremely important, and the results could be disastrous if the information was leaked out.

Garen understood that as well, and waved his hand, a signal telling Turing to take Tesna out for a walk.

The two of them left accordingly, and the remaining few could speak more easily.

Baylon immediately chattered about all their adventures and traumatic experiences, spilling it all out for Garen.

The Four-Star Alliance? Planet Gideon?

As soon as he heard it, Garen knew that this was the family planet that White Night had been on, that was once White Night’s Gideon family planet, but now it was being inhabited by some guy called the Spirit King.

“So you’re saying that Red Moon has gotten part of his Mech back?” Garen was thoughtful.

Seeing the trio’s strange expressions, Garen finally asked about Red Moon’s condition.

“In order to protect us, the Lord… was hit by the energy tide, and is now seriously injured. He’s still recuperating…” Clint said helplessly, his expression desolate.

“Then what do you plan to do? Wait here until he wakes up?” Garen asked.

Clint instantly scratched his head, and did not reply.

Baylon’s gaze wandered as well, Garen had evidently hit the jackpot.

Looking at the two of them, Garen was instantly at a loss. Look at the White King, he had been planning things for decades. On the other hand, Clint right now was just an immature child, the difference between them was like heaven and hell. Garen had no idea how he ended up becoming the Red King.

Chapter 1110: Dark Prologue 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Since you’re here, Big Bro, why don’t you help us think of something!” Baylon said with a flattering smile. Compared to that shy, introverted Baylon from before, she seemed to be a lot more cheerful and extroverted now.

“Yeah yeah yeah, if it’s Big Bro Nono, I’m sure you’ll have an idea!” Clint hurriedly nodded in agreement.

Only White Winter was unconvinced. He had heard Baylon bring up her brother before, but no matter how he looked it, Nonosiva was just a regular prodigy from the Blackboard Region, with limited talent. He had seen plenty people just like that in the Gideon family. There was nothing special about him, so he had no idea why Clint and Baylon respected him so much.

“If you guys really have nowhere else to go, I guess you could come with me.” But Garen was already planning something. Right now, Clint had one of Red Moon’s mech parts, that was a Regent-Level part. If he could just examine it closely, he should be able to gain a great deal from it.

“With Big Bro?” said Clint, confused.

“That’s right, I was just on my way to do something, join a competition,” said Garen calmly, with a smile. “There’s been a dramatic shift here, so I bet this place has become a focus point amongst all the factions. It’d be very troublesome for you to continue staying here, it’s best if you could temporarily leave the Mother Planet.”

He was absolutely right, and the three of them also nodded in agreement.

“We do want to leave the Mother Planet, but we can’t find any other way…” said Clint helplessly. “The only way is to buy a spaceship and then fly out, but that sort of thing isn’t for sale…”

Garen instantly laughed.

“No, other than the regular route, there is another way. Don’t forget, I’m also an Energy Machinist…”

“Huh? Energy Machinist!!??” Clint and Baylon instantly widened their eyes, turning around immediately to look at White Winter.

“What are you looking at him for?” Garen was also slightly mystified now.

White Winter, however, lowered his head awkwardly.

“I-I’m also… an Energy Machinist…”

“You too?”

Garen had not noticed it, but once it was mentioned, he realized that White Winter really was an Energy Machinist, albeit a weakest Level-One Energy Machinist. His Willpower was weak enough to be negligible, and that was why Garen had overlooked it.

At Garen’s current realm, he could basically just ignore anyone lower than Inherited Level, because anyone weaker than that was not even worth his gaze. It was impossible for them to pose a threat.

But he knew the general way things would go, so he knew that White Winter would also become one of the Star Generals in the future. The Red King had four Star Generals in total, and the same went for the White King. That was the tally during the final battle, and the Red King’s Star Generals changed a few times along the way, but White Winter was always consistently there. He and Baylon would keep improving up until the final battle.

The other two, including the original Nonosiva, both changed twice. After Nono died in battle, there were two more replacements until it finally settled down.

“Alright, I’ll admit that I might have overlooked you.” Garen nodded at White Winter. “The Energy Machinists have a Teleportation Point here, we can reach one of the Energy Machinists’ three main cities, the City of Nagadako, directly from here.”

“We can do that too!?” Clint was instantly overjoyed.

*****************

Radiation Zone, an Energy Machinist base

On the scarlet-golden sands, there was a floating, giant city that moved along slowly, projecting an enormous black shadow onto the ground.

By the time Garen and company reached here, it was already three days later.

Garen did not immediately tell them what level he was at now, in case Clint and Baylon began to rely on him. They still needed to grow, or else they would never be able to fight against the White King.

And the way things were going, they would still accidentally stumble across this base at one point. They were supposed to have made a contact on the inside, eventually disguising themselves as Energy Machinists, and getting teleported to the City of Nagadako.

Garen merely simplified the process.

“This is the place…” Garen looked up at the floating city in the sky, and felt the emotions surging in his heart. Back then, he had left the Sixth Divine Wind General and Sinno here, but he did not know how they were getting along now.

“Let’s go.”

He strode towards the base.

Behind him, the other three were like sun-dried brinjals, completely weak and exhausted. Without their mechs, they were just slightly better than normal people, and so they had no resistance at all toward the intense scorching heat of the sun.

Garen would not block the sun and rain for them, and he proceeded on ahead by himself. The only good thing is that they knew that the temperature would drop slightly if they were closer to him.

That was the only thing they had to comfort themselves over the three days of walking.

Tesna, on the other hand, bit her lip and followed wordlessly. She had the worst physical fitness, after all, she was a true-blue regular person. If it were not for Turing’s occasional support, she would have crashed out a long time ago, collapsing onto the ground, unable to get back up.

Just as before, there was a line of people queuing up in front of a tall, large, black stone pillar.

The people in the line took turns entering a small house, and they never came back, so they had clearly been teleported into the base somehow.

There were many people in Garen’s group, so they were very eye-catching as they walked, but when many people saw that Tesna, Clint, and the rest were just regular people, they instantly pulled back their gazes and lost all interest.

Garen led the team to the back of the line, and queued up.

He came to the City of Nagadako, not only to visit his few long-time friends, but also to join the Major Sect Battle, and… to meet Celine!

Celine was also an Energy Machinist, and she had always been living in the Three Major Cities, so she would surely appear during this competition as well.

Thinking of Celine, ripples rose in Garen’s heart. All these years, she had lied to him for all these years, but this was the first time his feelings toward her were so complicated.

The team slowly moved ahead, and some more Energy Machinists joined the line behind them. Some of them frowned when they saw the normal people beside Garen.

“Doesn’t he know that normal people can’t enter the base? Does he not know the rules?”

Someone said softly.

Garen turned around, but saw that the Energy Machinists were all acting as though it has nothing to do with them, as though it was not any of them who said it.

“Hahaha! Brother, I can’t believe it’s you!!” Suddenly, a familiar face appeared in front of Garen abruptly.

It was actually the little fatty that had lent Garen a hand last time, and that pretty girl with the bright eyes and white teeth was still with him,wearing a white face veil and a cold expression.

The fatty approached Garen, pushing his way forward, until he actually reached Garen’s side.

“He’s a friend, a friend, we’re here together,” he said smilingly as he squeezed past the dissatisfied Energy Machinists.

“It’s you? Little Fatty?” Garen also recognized him from before.

“The prodigy from back then! Haha!!” the little fatty laughed, scratching his head.

Garen also was very fond of this guy, if it weren’t for his help back then, he and the Sixth Divine Wind General may not have been able to deal with the Seventh Divine Wind General, who was chasing after them.

“Why are you still here?”

“Cuz I’m bored!” said the fatty, pouting helplessly. He came closer to Garen and mysteriously transmitted his voice.

“Since we seem fated to meet, let me tell you a secret. Have you heard of the Prodigy Alliance?”

Garen blinked. It was a signal to Turing, who was growing wary, telling him to calm down.

“Prodigy Alliance?”

“That’s right, it’s powerful alliance where all sorts of prodigies gather together!” praised the little fatty, sticking up his thumb. “Take this lovely lady beside me for example, she has irrepressible talent! She’s the professional liaison for the Prodigy Alliance!”

“So?” Garen really had never heard of any Prodigy Alliance.

“Seeing as you’re a prodigy as well, you have the right to join us. Whataya think? Do you wanna join our Prodigy Alliance? I can give you a discounted recommendation fee!” The fatty chuckled, rubbing his fingers together.

Garen broke out laughing, the Energy Machinists were about to face the biggest crisis they had ever seen, so what good would this Prodigy Alliance be?

“That depends on whether or not your Whatever Alliance has the right to have me join it.”

“Hmph! What are you being so arrogant for, you should be honored that we invited you to join.”

His words instantly caused the pretty girl beside him to bristle, and she snorted coldly.

“What do you mean by snorting like that! Don’t you have any manners?” Baylon instantly lost her usual composure, and immediately said unhappily. Big Brother Nono had always been her idol, and she could not allow others to be disrespectful to him.

“It’s my matter whether I snort or not, what’s it have to do with you?” The girl was getting riled up too.

“You snorted at my brother, so that just shows you don’t have manners. You’re young and you look decent, but why don’t you have any sense of common courtesy at all?”

“You’re the one without manners! Do you know who I am? Back then, I was…”

The two of them actually started arguing as though there was no one else around. Clint smiled helplessly at the side, and could not get a word in edgewise.

Garen and the fatty just ignored the two of them.

“Let’s talk about this after we get in, it’s almost our turn now.” Garen indicated for the fatty to stop mentioning it now, while he motioned for the person behind back him to stay back for now, so he could proceed into the small house alone.

It was the same process, where he pressed his hand against the huge metallic ball.

“An Energy Machinist can only bring two followers. Your identity card has been filled up,” said the old Energy Machinist who was in charge of the two-way traffic after checking Garen’s Energy Machine Imprint.

“Filled up? Can you check it again?” Garen took out a scarlet badge, and tossed it at the old man.

When he saw this Imprint, the atmosphere in the room instantly changed, becoming almost bone-piercingly cold.

“This is… a Sect Imprint? And a high-level one at that!?” The old man immediately got to his feet in shock, and hurriedly lowered his head in a bow.

“So you’re from a sect, sir, no problem, Inherited-Level Energy Machinists from sects have a twenty-person quota, please, do as you like!!”

He added hurriedly.

“That’s good to hear.”

Garen nodded, satisfied.

The group entered the base under such strange circumstances, surprising all the other Energy Machinists. They were low-level members, so they did not know about Garen’s true identity, or about that special rule.

The little fatty also followed Garen into the base.

At the first possible moment, Garen looked for Sinno, but unfortunately, the room inside the base was somehow empty. He has no idea where Sinno and the Sixth Divine Wind General went, the house was empty, and covered with a thick layer of dust. It was clear that nobody had been in here for a while.

Garen was slightly disappointed that he could not find Sinno and the Sixth Divine Wind General. But the most crucial thing right now was still the crisis that would befall the Energy Machinists.

The Major Battle was back, and it would be happening very soon. Toward the end of the competition, there would be more and more unsavory participants, and they would slowly reveal what was hidden before. There would be chaos, until the entire Battle fell apart at the seams, with betrayals and casualties galore. It would be the darkest day in the history of the Energy Machinist.

What Garen needed to do was to protect himself and the Scarlet Snow Sect, making sure that they survived the crisis.

Before things started to get chaotic, he must never reveal his true powers, or else he would incur even stronger rivals. This was a destined catastrophe, but it would also be his first chance to test Chinande.

Chapter 1111: Gathering 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

City of Nagadako

Planet Naga

In the middle of the white light shooting up from the volcano into the sky, Garen and company walked out slowly, still recovering from the long-distance teleportation.

They could vaguely hear the soft melody of a violin coming from a distance.

The pure music was accompanied by a heavy and majestic chorus of countless voices, ringing out through the distant sky and swirling in the air above the entire city.

Garen raised his gaze to look into the sky above the capital, and he saw an enormous, spinning round blue stage there. There were countless audience stands suspended around the stage, and as several thousand or even ten thousand audiences watched, the gentle melody of the violin kept coming from the center of the stage.

“May the arriving passengers please leave the teleportation point as soon as possible,” said an electric voice around them.

Garen and his friends followed the crowd out of the volcano, and just like them, the few visitors sparsely scattered around them were mostly looking up at the round board in the sky. That shining blue round stage had attracted these visitors to the City of Nagadako at the first possible moment.

At the exiting elevator, there was a screen displaying some advertised information.

‘The renowned Queen of Violin, Lady Annie Victoria, performs in celebration of the Energy Machinist Ranking Competition.’

“This place is so developed.”

It was Tesna’s first time leaving the planet, so she found everything new and fascinating, looking at the restroom teleportation point beside her with an awestruck expression. “They’re using teleportation even for the restroom, how extravagant!”

In the Blackboard Region, only the higher-ups could enjoy teleportation facilities, but here, even the toilet involved teleportation…

It was Clint and the others’ first time coming here, so they were villagers who had come to the city for the first time. They understood nothing, but they wanted to get a closer look at everything, to better understand what all these things were actually meant to do.

The people around them moved like the tide, making it rather crowded and noisy.

Suddenly, a group of people walked out from another teleportation elevator. They were all dressed in green uniforms, the men well-built, the women devilishly attractive, and they all wore a green shield badge.

“It’s the people from Two-Headed Snake.”

Someone mumbled softly around him.

Garen heard it, and did not stop Clint, Baylon and White Winter, since he knew that Turing would naturally greet the newcomers for him.

But his gaze moved toward the team of Energy Machinists dressed in green, these people had workers whose only job was to open a path for them, preventing others from bumping into them and causing conflict. They were just like celebrities, and it was not long before many young people ran out from goodness knows where, rushing up and clamoring to take a picture with them, or to get their autographs.

Garen and crew were pushed out of the crowd by the security, just to make space for this group to walk.

Separated from the crowd and the security, Garen quickly looked for the relevant information in his Imprint.

Two-Headed Snake—a mid-range Energy Machinist Sect, they definitely had a Level-Eight Guardian, and at least five Non-Falling-Level Elders.

There was already a Non-Falling-Level team coach hidden among the people here, and all the disciples who were here to compete were Inherited Level, be it the men or the women.

“As expected of a mid-range sect.” Garen was silently appreciative.

He compared this group with his own. There was nothing to be said about Clint and Baylon, they were no different from ordinary people without their Mechs, and White Winter was a novice, there was nothing a Level-One Energy Machinist could do. Garen himself and Turing were hiding their auras and energy waves, so they seemed like normal people as well.

Suddenly Garen’s gaze sharpened, he had actually sensed a familiar presence among the group from Two-Headed Snake.

“Hm? This presence?” He frowned abruptly.

“What is it, Brother?” Baylon was constantly observing Garen, so when she saw that he was frowning, she hurriedly asked.

“It’s nothing, let’s go. Do you want to go back to my place first, and settle down a bit before you consider your options?” Garen asked back. They were here now, but Garen knew that Clint and the others could very well have orders from Red Moon, and so it was highly likely that they would operate freely. Although Red Moon was seriously injured right now, he could still wake up occasionally and send them some messages. After all, he had been supplemented with one of his component parts now, and was no longer just a core like before.

It was just as he expected. Clint scratched his head awkwardly.

“Sorry, Bro, we still have some private matters to settle, so we’ll still need to stay here for a bit.”

“What about Lonnie?” Garen looked at Baylon.

“Sorry… Brother, this is for you!” Baylon lowered her head, her expression tortured. Suddenly, she stuffed a small item into Garen’s hands.

“Alright, then,” Garen smiled. However, his face was always on the fiercer side, and smiling made him look scarier than if he had cried. He looked at the small black ring in his hand, it was evidently a Space Ring.

“I’ll leave Turing here to help you guys out, how does that sound?”

“Hehe, thanks a lot, Big Bro!” Clint hurriedly smiled, his expression eager to please.

Suddenly, they heard Red Moon’s voice.

“Get him to help, go to the Great Bronze Hall!” The voice softened and vanished almost as soon as it rang out. Evidently, Red Moon was still incapable of maintaining long-term communication.

“Great Bronze Hall?” Clint and Baylon were both taken aback, and they exchanged a glance. Since Garen had set aside the training method Red Moon gave him without ever practicing it, he could not hear the voice, and only the other three could.

They hurriedly told him the place.

When he heard it, however, Garen frowned.

“Great Bronze Hall?” He knew the place, it was one of the Planet Naga Holy Lord’s old hideouts, an important place for storing bronze crystals. These were delicate times, and he could not show his true powers, so it would be very hard for him to accomplish that.

“I can’t get you in directly, but I can help you guys to apply for a tourist pass.” He knew that Clint and the rest would soon encounter their first greatest enemy, the Non-Falling Demon Lord, Shaunt.

In the process of their bold attempt to retrieve one of Red Moon’s parts from the Great Bronze Hall, they might encounter many challenges and dangers, but this was a path they had to take.

“That’d be more than enough! Thanks, Big Bro!” said Baylon immediately, full of gratitude.

“No problem.” Garen summoned Turing, and told him to pass a message to the Sect. It was still possible for him to use his connections to arrange for a pass, this was a matter he could settle with money.

Once everything was arranged, and the contact methods sorted out, Garen finally split up with Clint and the others.

Only his disciple Tesna was with him now. Both of them took another cab that was teleporting towards the Scarlet Snow Sect.

“Master, where are we going?” asked Tesna in a small voice.

“To meet two friends.”

Garen replied softly.

“Friends?” Tesna felt as though this whole trip was a dream. She really did not understand the world of Energy Machinists and pilots, but she had something of a one-track mind. Her principle was that once she believed in someone, she would believe everything about them. Now, for example, she had absolute faith in Garen, and believed that he would not hurt her.

The cabbie kept chatting with Garen throughout the journey, he was clearly a very talkative guy, but that was also to be expected. When there was an innocent-looking young girl like Tesna sitting in the car, most men would act talkative.

“I heard that the competition will be held on Planet Naga this year?” Garen suddenly changed the topic, raising this important matter.

“That’s right, there would be a Major Battle held every so often, to distribute the resources among the sects. This is the highest-level competition among Energy Machinists, just look at how many more people there are now compared to usual. Our business gets a lot better as well, tourists and Energy Machinists from all over are here to watch the action. Almost all of the elite Energy Machinists wool be here, after all, it’ll help widen their horizons if they can which the way others fight. Naturally, there won’t be much of an effect on us normal people,” chuckled the cabbie.

“Is that so?”

“I hear that the Old Mayor will also show up and speak for the competition this year, wonder if that’s true.”

Garen nodded, and said nothing else. He knew who the Old Mayor the cabbie mentioned was, in the eyes of normal civilians, this Old Mayor was just a leader, the highest-ranking one. But as an Energy Machinist, he was the Holy Lord that maintained discipline throughout the entire Planet Naga, the man known as the Backlight Holy Lord. He was one of the three strongest Energy Machinists.

Soon, the car stopped in front of a bar.

Two people with slightly cold expressions were waiting outside, and they nodded slightly at Garen.

Winding down the car window, Garen motioned for Tesna to get out of the car.

“Follow them, they’ll send you to a place where you can settle down, and I’ll be there in a bit.”

“Okay.” Tesna nodded hurriedly. She got off the car, and after those two said a few words to her in private, she followed them away.

Garen watched as the people from Scarlet Snow led Tesna away, and got the cabbie to continue driving, telling him a location softly.

“Before the prologue begins, I had better get all the trivial matters properly sorted out.” He remembered those two friends from way back then who he had not seen for a long time, and his mood lightened slightly.

****************

In another grey-brown coffee shop

Accord leaned in front of the private room’s ceiling-to-floor window, looking out at the crowd of passersby, slightly dazed.

Everything inside the private room was brown in color, the sofa, the table and chairs, the wallpaper, and even the projector sphere suspended above his head, spinning slowly.

Accord was dressed just like any other relatively wealthy man, his appearance completely inconspicuous. To him, when he was meeting friends, it was best to set aside status or positions. If he still had to consider these things when meeting his true friends, then how would it be different from his regular social gatherings? Those were all about making connections for mutual benefit and social capital, but with his current status and position, he was surely not lacking in those aspects. He had attended such gatherings far, far too many times, so many times that they frustrated him.

Beep-beep, beep-beep.

The Energy Machine Imprint rang again.

Accord glanced at it, it was a call from the sect, they were probably trying to ask him about annoying trivial matters again. So he just muted the sound, letting it flash and blink on its own.

He opened the Friends tab in his Contacts, and chose Garen’s name.

“Hey, where are you now?”

“Outside the door.”

Ka-chak.

The door opened.

Garen walked in, dressed in white robes. The clothes looked a little unique, as though he was a member of the cleric.

The two of them exchanged glances, and each could instantly tell that the other had changed tremendously.

Garen looked even colder, and also stronger.

And Accord no longer looked as unassuming as before, although he was not handsome by any means, he still had a mysterious aura of sharpness and confidence that made his originally messy hair and slightly dark skin all look naturally glossier.

His glasses had also changed to a nicer model, and his overall impression was that of a gentle, scholarly man.

“You’re as skinny as ever!” Garen smiled, and patted Accord’s shoulder forcefully.

“You’re even buffer than before…” Accord was exasperated.

Chapter 1112: Gathering 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Where’s Liz?”

“She’ll be here soon.”

As soon as he said that, there was the tapping of footsteps from the door.

A pretty little face peeked in through the door crack. She wore some light make-up, replacing some of her past innocence with an extra dose of allure.

“I’m not late, am I?” She blinked, looking at Garen and Accord, but her gaze was more heavily focused on Accord.

“You’re just in time,” replied Accord nonchalantly, smiling.

The door opened, and Liz evidently had not come alone. There were three others behind her, two men and a woman, and they all wore the Dragon Light Sect’s pale silver costumes. There was the logo of a flying dragon embroidered onto their sleeves. The men were handsome and the woman beautiful, but they all had traces of cosmetic surgery.

“It just so happens that my few Senior Brothers and my Senior Sister is here with me. When they heard that we were meeting up, they wanted to join the fun. You two don’t mind, do you?” Liz said with a giggle.

A hint of discomfort flashed past Accord’s eyes, but he did not say anything.

“It’s fine, it’s fine,” Garen interrupted hurriedly. He knew Accord’s temper well, the man was unbelievably arrogant, and he was not afraid to show it on his face at the slightest disagreement.

But they had initially agreed on a three-person gathering, and Liz actually brought others in here, so Garen could understand where Accord was coming from.

“”Let’s get to know each other, I’m Liz’s Senior Brother, Dios, shall we be friends?” The young man in charge held out his hand to shake Garen’s.

“Garen. Scarlet Snow Sect.”

“Scarlet Snow Sect?” Dios seemed to be rather unfamiliar with it, but he quickly searched up the relevant information, and found out that it was just a small sect. He just smiled politely. Looking at Garen, it seemed as though there was nothing at all unusual about him, he only had regular Level Four forces. He seemed even weaker than Liz, so Dios stopped paying attention to him and turned his gaze onto Accord instead.

“Accord from Star Cloud?” He raised an eyebrow, and held out his hand. “My older brother is very close to Senior Brother Eco from your sect, I hear that you have a powerhouse called Dark Light who’s really something.”

“You’re not from Dragon Light? Dios, I never heard of such a person in Dragon Light.” Accord frowned, ignoring both his outstretched hand and his question. This blatant display of rudeness instantly caused some dissatisfaction among the other two.

“I’m just temporarily staying in Dragon Light, I’m from Black Blade.” The young man smiled slightly, but there was a hint of contempt in his gentleness.

“Senior Brother Dios is a Three-Blades-Level Black Blade powerhouse!” the one girl could not help but introduce rather haughtily as well. “It’s equal to what you guys call the peak of Inherited Level, y’know!”

“Is that so?” Accord was exasperated, and wanted to ignore these outsiders completely, but the other party was acting perfectly politely, so he could not find a reason to pick a fight. If he continued like this, it just showed that he lacked moral upbringing, because he could not be bothered to deal with them.

The other two were also Liz’s Senior Brothers from Dragon Light, but they were all over Dios from Black Blade, and Dios was a proud one as well. When he saw that Accord did not respond to his kind offer, he stopped trying to press the matter.

At first, he had only come here because he heard that Accord was an elite from Star Cloud. That was the only reason he actually bothered to come here for a look, and he had nothing better to do anywhere.

As for what Liz was thinking, he knew it very well too. This Junior Sister of him, who he was quite fond of, was trying to give her friends more connections. Unfortunately, the other two did not seem to be trying to help themselves.

Putting aside that Accord, even that Garen from the Scarlet Snow Sect did not seem particularly pleased.

Garen and Accord gathered together, quietly drinking their wine in a corner of the room. The others stayed together, laughing and chatting about something. Dios’ arrival seemed to have attracted other disciples from the Dragon Light Sect to join in one after the other, and some members of other mid-range sects also approached them to socialize. There were even two Magnetic Region powerhouses, they seemed to be Dios’ friends as well, and all of them were at the same level. Instantly, the room grew crowded. Soon, they received news from outside that the whole coffee shop had been booked.

Thank goodness the room Accord booked was big enough, or else it would really be crowded in here.

“Won’t you go and get to know them? These are all powerhouses from the major mid-range sects,” said Accord via voice transmission, his expression sarcastic.

Garen raised his wine glass, and took a small sip.

“What about you? Why aren’t you going? There’s a powerhouse at the same level as your Senior Brother there now.”

“Forget it, I hate this type of socializing the most.” A hint of impatience flashed through Accord’s eyes. “Wanna go out for a walk?”

“Sure.”

Garen nodded.

The two of them seemed completely inconspicuous among the crowd, and they left the private room soundlessly. Only Liz, who had been constantly paying attention to them, noticed them through the crowd, and melancholy flashed through her heart.

For some reason, she always felt as though there was a chasm between her and the other two.

But this thought was soon washed away by the conversations and questions she had with the people around her. The powerhouses around her were a crucial key that she could not afford to ignore. Dios and one of the powerhouses, someone called Herring, were also talking about training tips, and she benefited a lot from that conversation.

Maybe this was the price to pay for getting stronger…

That was what she thought.

She went through a lot before she could convince Senior Brother Dios to come here, if they could build a connection with Dios, it would be very useful for Accord and Garen. But she did not expect them to not appreciate it at all.

Thinking back to how Accord and Garen looked, and comparing that to Senior Brother Dios’ gentle, warm, and unassuming smile, she vaguely felt her impression of her two friends deteriorating.

“You were the ones who didn’t want to improve, if you’re weak and still don’t know how to build connections, I won’t be able to help you either.”

*************

Outside the coffee shop, there were many lines of parked luxury cars. The crowd was slightly sparser, it was already evening.

Garen and Accord stood beside the door, and talked about some recent developments in low voices.

“What do you plan to do in the future? Will you continue mucking it out with Scarlet Snow?” Accord asked.

“Maybe.” Garen laughed. “Something big might happen soon, you must have noticed that many sects were annihilated, right?” No matter what, Accord was one of his few friends, and he had helped Garen out a lot back then. Garen had a duty to warn him.

“What’s that? Do you have some insider news?” Accord seemed to be done with drinking, and he just poured the rest of the wine onto the ground, tossing the cup into a cleaning robot nearby.

“If you sense anything wrong, just get out of there ASAP. Remember, don’t use any Teleportation Points,” Garen advised him, with a hint of severity.

Accord saw that Garen was extremely serious about this, and his expression turned solemn as well.

“Sure, I’ll remember that.”

Putting aside that topic, the two of them started talking about some matters from the past, but neither could understand how Liz turned out this way.

She was leeching off a powerful senior brother, but the two of them treated such an attitude with the utmost contempt.

“Everyone makes different choices. We choose our own paths,” said Garen calmly. “We can’t force a lot of things to stay unchanged. Don’t you agree?”

Accord released a long breath.

“True. Who knew that I wouldn’t take it as well as you could.”

Both of them hid their true powers to prevent creating a rift between them and their friends, but Liz had interpreted that to mean that they were weaklings who still refused to improve… Both of them were not particularly happy with that.

Now, chatting in the clean night breeze, they managed to force away some of that frustration.

But neither of them bothered to explain, so what if they explained? Some people were just naturally like that. So although they knew that Liz meant well, both of them were not as fond of her as they used to be.

“For the Major Battle this time, I’ve done all my preparations, and I’m ready to take the next step any time. What do you have planned?” Accord asked about the Major Sect Battle.

“Same here,” Garen smiled. “The Scarlet Snow Sect is a small sect, so it’s fine as long as perform well, and try to break past our limits. I think we should be able to get some good results this time.”

“Hehe, you’re that confident? You have a Herculean task in front of you, then let’s try our best together.”

“Of course.” Garen reached out his hand and got a high-five.

“When the Major Battle starts, I’ll introduce you to a hot girl. Didn’t I say so last time?” Accord smiled craftily. “You shouldn’t be single at this age.”

Garen was exasperated. “You sure progress quickly, but we’ll see how it goes. We’ll see.”

“There are three days left, I gotta make a trip back first.” He glanced at the time. “Okay, I gotta go back, you tell Liz for me, I won’t go in again.”

“No, I don’t wanna go in either. Just seeing the way those arrogant bastards look down on us just pisses me off.” Accord waved him off. “We’ll just tell her through our Imprints, we’re just small-fry anyway, it doesn’t matter if we leave or not.”

He laughed self-deprecatingly.

“True.”

The two of them exchanged glances, and both found it rather funny.

“See ya around.”

“Yeah, see ya.”

*******************

Without a moment’s delay.

Garen went to the hotel Tesna was resting at, got her out, and hired a car to send them straight to the Scarlet Snow Teleportation Point.

Not long later, a pillar of white light shot into the air, heading towards another planet in the distance.

Accord was walking on the streets, and just happened to be standing in some shade at that moment, so he raised his head and looked at the volcanic white light headed in the direction of Scarlet Snow.

Suddenly, a black shadow appeared behind him.

“Yo, isn’t that our Senior Brother Eco?” said Accord sarcastically as he turned around and looked at the shadow. “Are you looking for me, your junior brother, for something?”

“Black Light, this time Red Skeleton is here too.”

“So what?” Accord laughed cynically. “You’re in charge, I’m just the vice-captain.”

“The Elder wants you to eliminate the others from the contest first. Focus on Red Skeleton and Black Jade Dragon.

“Sabotage them secretly?” Accord frowned.

“Up to you. But remember, you must do it cleanly,” said the black shadow darkly.

“Are you ordering me around?” Accord stood up angrily, a hint of violence emanating from his body.

Psst!

A black shadow shot out from beneath him, and hit the black shadow hard. Clang!

The black shadow took two steps back, his hand quickly darting out to grab the poisonous black snake that had soundlessly appeared on his face. The snake’s blood-red tongue had nearly touched his face.

Hiss…

The hand that he used to grab the snake was actually starting to rot away.

“I’m warning you, if you dare to try and order me around again, I’ll kill you!” Accord laughed coldly, turned around, and left. “Also, tell the Elders that I’m aiming for a rank in the main headquarters, and not just in one of the eighty-one Planet Naga main divisions.”

The black shadow trembled slightly, and walked into the light. He turned out to be a dark-skinned man, and there was already a slight sheen of sweat over his head. He stared at the direction Accord left in, but no one knew what he was thinking.

Chapter 1113: Consolidate 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Planet Scarlet Snow

Garen brought Tesna along, and they suddenly arrived in a boundless forest. The surrounding was deserted, as the slanting golden sunlight shone down from among the trees, giving off a pure and fresh feeling.

An array of horns sounded from afar. Fermium Cloud Tower was clearly visible in the distance with layers of clouds moving around the tower. It was spectacular.

“Teacher, where is this place?” Tesna asked with a look of discomfort on her face. Her body constitution was that of an ordinary person. Even though she had been protected by Garen, teleporting such a long distance still made her feel uncomfortable.

“This is my place,” Garen answered lightly.

After he had left Scarlet Snow Sect, with Osho Ice-Ocean and Second Elder around, as well as the newly-appointed Three Hearted Royalties and the group of allied powerhouses, securing the entire sect was not a problem.

The resources reserved were also sufficient for a long period of time. There was no need to worry about any shortages in this catastrophe.

Nonetheless, just because one did not take the initiative to attack did not mean that he would not be targetted by others.

“Let’s go.”

Garen walked in the direction of Fermium Cloud Tower. Tesna, on the other hand, was shocked when she saw the enormous tower. From the gap between the trees, she could clearly see the entire tower.

It was only after Garen had walked out a few steps did she respond and follow.

The two seemed to be walking aimlessly, but Garen knew that there were people of Scarlet Snow Sect approaching here speedily.

The strongest force in Scarlet Snow Sect right now was not the Three Hearted, but the eleven Ice Demon Generals newly set up by Garen. All of them were raised to Non-falling Level through the Distorted Seed; they were extremely powerful.

Among them, Osho Ice-Ocean was the acting Sect Master after Garen’s departure, which was equivalent to a deputy Sect Master. His strength originally was at Non-falling Level. After obtaining the Distorted Seed, even Garen did not know what level he had advanced to. The only thing he knew was that he was definitely not merely at Non-Falling Level, the seventh level.

The current Scarlet Snow Sect, even with Garen’s temporary departure, was not inferior to the average medium-sized sect.

It was full of talented people, and it had terrific strength.

The two walked some distance. Soon, some figures appeared in front of them. A few Scarlet Snow white-shirt disciples came and respectfully bowed to Garen.

“Take her to the Beginner-Level disciple area to start learning the fundamental basics.”

Garen motioned for the two to take Tesna away.

“Alright.”

“Teacher,” Tesna was somewhat dazed as she looked at Garen. She did not know what to do.

“Go on. Learn the basic things first. I will arrange everything,” Garen gently smiled at her.

The purpose of him accepting Tesna was to test the extent his level of modifying human body was on. Using the Biochemical Pool to modify the body to form a biochemical army, this was also a kind of development direction for Energy Machinists. It belonged to the direction of modulating Demon Lord.

Tesna saw Garen’s incontestable eyes and realized that she could not avoid this matter. She could only leave quickly with the two people.

Only Garen was left standing alone.

Whish, whish, whish!

In an instance, several white lights fell around Garen. They formed a circle before transforming into four people.

“Sect Master,” One of them was notably Osho Ice-Ocean. This old gentleman with a cane in his hand was showing full of respect at the moment.

The others were the newly-promoted Ice Demon Generals. They were looking at Garen with exceptional enthusiastic eyes. This was because if it were not for Garen, they would never be able to break through Non-falling Level.

“Is everything ready?” Garen spoke solemnly.

“It’s all done,” Osho Ice-Ocean bowed down to respond.

“Let’s begin then,” Garen looked at Fermium Cloud Tower from afar. “This will be the time when I truly show my strength to the world.”

“Understood!”

The four people answered simultaneously, reflecting how well-trained they were.

“The first target, the Dual-Key Sect,” Garen’s voice was deep. Before the Major Battle, it was the time for his plan to rejuvenate the entire Scarlet Snow Sect to be in full swing.

*****************

Dual-Key Sect

It was a medium-sized sect in the star region nearby Planet Scarlet Snow. Their main training exercise involved wind. In other words, they primarily controlled the air flow. From the highest level to the lowest level in the sect, there were a total of one hundred and thirty thousand people. The strongest was the Guardian, a biochemical huge beast, whose strength was unknown. It was said that it was at a strength of Level Eight a thousand years ago, but no one knew how it was now.

Planet Dual-Key was yellowish, and it looked almost like an ordinary, unmanned planet. However, the pale yellow atmosphere on the surface was its protective camouflaged color. In reality, the atmosphere inside was another component.

Planet Dual-Key ruled this solar system, which was called the Dual-Key Galaxy. With it as its core, it was surrounded by two planets which were transformed into resources and tourist planet.

In the dark outer space at this moment, a group of white, densely-packed spaceships slowly flew out from a nearby galaxy in the distance. Their entire body was shining with a thin silver membrane, which was the space energy left from jumping back through the inverse space.

The tens of thousands of white spaceships were all marked with a logo – the distorted text logo of Scarlet Snow.

The spaceships darted toward Dual-Key Galaxy without any disguise. The dense blue flames emitted from the ends of the ships were spectacular. They looked like blue fireworks sparkling over the entire sky.

“This is Dual-Key Galaxy. This is Dual-Key Galaxy. Friends of Planet Scarlet Snow, please tell us about your intention of coming here. Otherwise, it will be regarded as an intrusion and we will counterattack.”

A clear, broadcasting female voice spread out loudly, it was directed to all the Planet Scarlet Snow’s battleships.

Garen was in a battle fortress, which was at the core, and was looking at this beautiful yellow galaxy from far.

The battle fortress was like a hedgehog. It was filled with tens of thousands of barrels. This was a veritable battle machine, a weapon of mass destruction built with the terrific wealth of Energy Machinists.

There were more than twenty people standing beside him, and they were divided into two groups. One of the groups were the Ice Demon Generals while the other was a group of emperors or queens from the empires and kingdoms under him.

In this intrusive war, Garen directly issued an order to launch all the imperialist forces under him, which had an expeditionary jumping ability. He commissioned the battleships to form an army. Apart from leaving a little of manpower at the base, most of them moved out and directly charged at Planet Dual-Key, starting a war.

Because they were hurriedly assembled, the battleships had already jumped away before the spies from other sects had the time to transmit the message.

The stars were shining in the outer space overhead. Underneath it was an enormous fortress made of white metal alloys. There was no protection facility around it, giving people a feeling of easy access whereby one could enter the outer space with just a jump.

The surrounding was all densely-packed with white battleships of various kinds. Some of them were not even white but were quickly painted white. The paint at some spots had not even dried up yet.

Garen was in a white robe. Other than his head, the other parts of him were shrouded in the large white robe.

“The Dual-Key Sect of the Dual-Key Galaxy is the main exporter of the technology used in the manufacturing of large-scale Stargates. Our operations later will be much easier if we took over here. The battle against the few small fries will have to depend on all of you.”

Garen smiled and spoke in a deep voice.

“Rest assured, Sect Master. We, the Ice Demon Generals, will live up to your expectations. Those who dare to rebel against us, we will tear them apart!” A newly-promoted Ice Demon General wore the Ice Demonic Armor on his entire body. This was an enhanced external armor which was naturally formed by the Distorted Seed in order to break through the limits of the human beings here. Only by relying on the Ice Demonic Armor could they be promoted to Non-falling Level Ice Demon Generals.

Some of the newly promoted Ice Demon Generals were emitting an aura of eagerness to go. Obviously, they could not help but wish to exhibit their best qualities. The older generation of Ice Demon Generals such as Osho Ice-Ocean, and Ice-Crack and Ice-Grand the two brothers, however, were all extremely calm. They knew that it was not only command and strategy that determined the outcome of a war, but also the confrontation of high-end forces.

“We are here with a sincerity to unite, not to cause destruction. Take note to not involve too many innocent people. People are the foundation of everything,” Garen reminded.

“Understood!” The group of people responded.

The emperors, queens and other national leaders on the other side were somewhat unsettled. In the face of using the power of the sect to start a war, the majority of them disapproved. However, due to the deterrence of Scarlet Snow Sect, they did not dare to oppose, and they could only obey. Most of them did not have strong Willpower and only cultivated the ordinary Willpower, which was mainly used for refreshing oneself and keeping fit.

They were now gathered here to centralize the controlling of the fleet.

In their view, this kind of seemingly insurrectional move, once unsuccessful, was equivalent to having put all the eggs in one basket. It would place the entire sect in a defeated situation. After all, they were on the offensive while the other party was the defensive side. Their headquarters would absolutely be solidly secured. So, it was extremely difficult to want to completely defeat them.

To them, Garen’s move seemed to be more of being young and ignorant. He probably did not understand war, but he only thought that he could suppress everything with individual force.

“Rest assured. Maybe we don’t really have to move in this time,” The underling behind Garen specifically helped him put on a ferocious, golden-helmet that was patterned on the Scarlet Snow Ice Armor. His entire face was immediately covered. Only the part of the eyes was exposed, but it was still total darkness.

Of course, he had not come to start a war. The original strength of the Energy Machinists was insufficient, and internal conflicts would make it worse. Garen’s purpose was to integrate the forces.

After wearing the helmet, the pointed helmet extended golden horns toward the front from both sides of the neck, looking unusually majestic and mysterious. Adding on Garen’s body being shrouded in the white robe, he instantly gave off an unfathomable aura.

Outside of the battle fortress on a battleship, Alice and Aloran had now been marginalized. Although Alice was also one of the Ice Demon Generals, she was still enlisted on the fleet.

In the intrusive war launched through the power of a sect by the Scarlet Snow Sect, although there were only tens of thousands of battleships, they were a high-grade fleet, several times more expensive than the typical battleships. Naturally, their combat strength was much stronger.

In addition to the hired pilots and the various types of Energy Machineries in the sect, the torrent of the army formed was much stronger than before.

“Sure enough… Garen’s superiority brings disaster and destruction,” Alice frowned, looking at the beautiful Planet Dual-Key from far.

Beside her, Aloran was also not looking good.

“Garen’s ambitions are too great. Was it not enough for him to destroy Frost Hell…? What exactly does he want to do? Does he want to ruin the entire Scarlet Snow Sect before giving up? Why is it that, with such an obvious and unreasonable plan, no one would actually unite to oppose him?!”

“They’re here!” Alice looked into the distance in the direction of Dual-Key Galaxy. A large armada of pale yellow battleships soared into the air. They jumped momentarily, flashing a few times toward this side before gradually appearing right in front of Scarlet Snow Sect’s fleet.

Chapter 1114: Consolidate 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Last warning! Scarlet Snow Sect, do you intend on starting a war?!” The female voice sounded again.

There was faint, metallic luster on the few planets around. Clearly, the defense system on those planets had been fully initiated.

It could be said that the entire Scarlet Snow’s fleet was completely within the firepower net several times that of its own. The situation was extremely critical. This was the consequence of rashly invading the headquarters of another sect. Energy Machinists had no shortage of money. Completely transforming a planet into a combative one was also a simple matter. If necessary, they would even detonate the entire planet as a countermeasure against the enemy.

At this moment, all the battleships in the Scarlet Snow’s fleet were all tensed up. After all, most of the soldiers were unwilling to fight. It was only the higher-ups who were controlled by Garen. Although they had to obey because of their higher-ups’ orders, facing such a disparity in the battles, nothing much could be said against them, even if they were quickly defeated and had to retreat.

On the battle fortress which resembled a vertical water droplet.

“Sect Master, let us, your subordinates, go and wipe out the other party’s higher-ups!” An Ice Demon General named Besset loudly requested for a fight. Having become a Non-falling Level, the Ice Demonic Armor on him gave him an endless energy and confidence, which blinded him a little.

The rest were still waiting for Garen’s decision. At the moment, once the war was started, Scarlet Snow’s fleet would definitely suffer an unimaginable net of firepower attack. They could hold out for ten minutes at most, though they would still be heavily injured and defeated.

Only Osho, as well as the Ice-Crack and Ice-Grand brothers had absolute confidence in Garen. They did not make any move at all and remained calm.

“I think we should focus on Sect Master’s plan. We are here not for war. The fleet is only used for deterrence,” Osho Ice-Ocean said plainly.

“Sect Master, for those who dare to aim their muzzle at us, if we do not counterattack severely, it may affect the perception of the outside world toward our Scarlet Snow Sect,” Besset still advocated a war.

“Sect Master has his own way of doing things. Does he need you to remind him?” Ice-Crack responded irritatingly. As a few of the most powerful Ice Demon General, he had his prestige. These Ice Demon Generals had also compared moves with one another privately and naturally, there was a conclusion of superiority. The brothers and Ice-Ocean Osho together formed the strongest trio. And so, the rest of the people were naturally convinced by the trio. However, although Besset’s voice had stopped, he clearly showed an impatient face.

Garen put up his hand. His face was hidden in the golden metal helmet, so his expression could not be seen clearly.

“We are here to spread peace and sincerity. We do not fire against our compatriots in a war. They are also Energy Machinists and one of us,” After Garen’s voice passed through the gold helmet, it became deep and slow and there was a sense of echo.

“Sect Master is so brilliant!” The monarchs and queens by the side quickly chimed in; tumultuous voices rose and faltered. They were the ones who did not want to initiate a war. Once a war was started, no matter which side won, it would cause losses to their battleships. This was not what they wanted to see.

“I will personally go and negotiate. All of you just wait here,” Garen’s voice came out from under the helmet.

Regarding his decision, before the people reacted, Garen had darted into the sky and flickered in the outer space, disappearing immediately in the air nearby.

The people beneath were suddenly startled.

“What is this nonsense!?” A monarch finally could not help but shout loudly. “How can we let the Sect Master enter into danger alone!”

“This is Sect Master’s decision. You only need to obey unconditionally!” An Ice Demon General spoke coldly. They, who were modified by the Distorted Seed, trusted Garen deeply. Each of his words had an absolute effect.

Like him, all the Ice Demon Generals were motionless. Because of the Distorted Seed, they could already sense the mystery and power of Garen. Among them, there were also some who had sinister motives. The Distorted Seed could only keep others from harming Garen, it that did not mean that those who were parasitized would absolutely protect him. They would also not necessarily obey his orders.

Each of them was having their own kind of thoughts while they quietly waited for Garen’s return.

********************

After jumping a few times in the outer space, Garen quickly passed through the large area of firepower protection net. No one intercepted him. Perhaps, they thought that even if he had come in alone with any malicious intent, it would just be like walking into the lion’s den. There was no need to be bothered at all, so they allowed his entry regardless.

Garen jumped a few times and put away the jump ball. He hovered in front of Planet Dual-Key, looking at the entire pale yellow planet.

“Planet Dual-Key Guardian, could you come out and meet with me?”

His voice was low and distant. It seemed to have countless echoes.

His voice faltered. After waiting for a minute or so, a giant, pitch-black python gradually appeared not far away in front of Garen.

The body of the python was a few thousand meters long, and it spiraled into a serpentine array. On top of the giant snake’s head were two huge eyes like red lanterns. They were scanning and staring at Garen.

The size of a human differed vastly than that of a snake. Garen quietly hovered in front the python, like an adult and an ant, which could easily be crushed. But, there was no panic in him at all.

“My name is Andes, the snake of Black Waters, Guardian of Dual-Key. The mighty one of the Scarlet Snow Sect, speak out your intention,” The giant python produced a sharp, female-like voice. The sound wave itself was almost equivalent to a kind of sound wave attack. If it were the general Inherited Levels, it was estimated that their eardrums would be directly punctured and bled.

Garen looked carefully at this giant snake. He did not answer immediately, and the helmet covered his facial expression at the moment.

After a few minutes, when the giant snake was a little impatient, Garen spoke up.

“I don’t know if Andes has felt that something is amiss, with all that has happened recently?”

The giant snake was silent for a while and its huge eyes blinked.

“Amiss?”

Garen’s deep laughter came from under the helmet.

“Do you know the Fear-Night Sect? The Life-Leaf Sect, The Nairar Sect, The Golden Light…” He kept mentioning the names of various sects one after another. These were the medium and small-sized sects that had recently been destroyed.

The look of the giant snake gradually darkened.

“What do you mean by this?”

Garen reached out his hand and made a grabbing motion. Suddenly, numerous white chills in the universe were released from the dark space around, quickly converging into the palm of his right hand.

“This is the destruction caused of us, the Energy Machinists. It is also our chance for a new life. Nirvana and rebirth!”

The infinite chill instantly condensed into a terrific Level-Eight force field. However, the force field was still growing, quickly reaching the peak of Level Eight and actually entering into Level Nine.

Whoosh!

A vine-ice-crystal screen appeared behind Garen. The immense number of white vines grew wildly like roots, spreading around the surrounding space in the universe as though they were climbing on panels of transparent glass.

In the blink of an eye, it surpassed the shape of the giant snake’s body and reached a length of tens of thousands of meters!

Whew…

The horrific cold wind rolled up a huge amount of chill. He spread them out in all directions, blowing on the giant snake and covering its body surface with a faint white frost.

Hiss…

It hurriedly drew back a few hundred meters before managing to drive away the hoarfrost on it.

Looking at Garen from afar, whose whole body extended out white ice-crystal roots, its lantern-like large eyes clearly revealed shock and disbelief.

“Come on,” Garen reached out his hands to the giant snake. “Join me. By uniting, our strength will become stronger!”

“Join you? I think my Dual-Key Sect should be stronger than your Scarlet Snow. Why won’t you join me?” The giant snake was immediately exasperated. “Bringing your army here and asking me to join you, I don’t think it’s a cooperation, but to have us submit to you!”

“If you want to understand it this way, you can,” Garen was equivocal. “Those who comply with me will prosper, while those who resist me will perish. All the things in the world are attributed to this principle.”

Countless ice-crystal vines swayed behind him like numerous white light tentacles. They were unusually dazzling and gorgeous.

“If you want me to submit, even if you are Level Nine, that can only happen after a fight!” Once the voice had just sounded, the giant snake abruptly hit out.

Endless winds gathered together. Contained within them was a vast amount of black sewage. No one knew from where the giant snake summoned it from. Human screams were faintly coming out from the wind continuously.

“Ah!”

The giant snake opened its huge mouth and issued a hoarse cry like that of a man.

Countless black water and airstreams converged at its mouth, quickly fusing into a badge. The extremely sophisticated and delicate small black badge looked like a blurry shield.

“Let me see if you are qualified to have me submit to you!”

The serpent spewed out the airstream.

The turbulent airstream along with the black water and badge was shot at Garen. A feeling of time and space were frozen rose in the hearts of every spectator.

“Star Core Resonance! Explode!” The giant snake thundered.

The badge flew to the front of Garen in the blink of an eye, exploding at the roar of the giant snake.

Countless bright yellow, transparent energy tentacles spread out from the yellowish planet behind the giant snake, flowing into the giant snake’s body.

Boom!

The huge wreath of black clouds exploded, quickly covered Garen’s enormous white ice-crystal vines.

Boom! Boom! Boom! Boom!

It was not just once, but the explosion actually continued non-nonstop for four times in a row!

“Level Nine?” Garen’s voice came out of the dark cloud and remained calm as it was.

The giant snake’s pupil constricted. This was the strongest hidden power it could produce at the moment. To be able to produce a Level Nine power was extremely difficult. It was not Level Nine at all, and it could only temporarily activate such a power. If it were not for the other party being so arrogant, it would not have used this kind of strength to attack right away.

“Again!” Its gigantically long tail brought along a black light and a Level Eight Thousand Gravitational Force, lashing toward Garen’s small body. The huge tail and the tiny human was like a stick and dust. However, it was the giant snake which was the nervous party instead.

“Attack!” At this moment, another woman’s voice sounded.

Boom!

In a flash, the universe brightened up!

Innumerable giant beams of high-energetic particles crossed the outer space from all directions, gathering on Garen with a dazzling array of red lights.

Huge particle beams with humming sounds and terrific disturbance, coupled with the giant snake’s lash and gravitational force, instantaneously condensed most of the particle beams and converged them at the small space where Garen’s body was located.

In a flash, the whole universe became bright.

The surrounding planets released terrifying red beams of light, most of which were from Planet Dual-Key. Hundreds of horrific particle beams shot out from the surface of the planets. They were straight and swift, converging at one point and striking the space Garen was at.

Chapter 1115: Alliance 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It was as though the intertwined beams of red light were weaving a giant cage. They filled up the small space less than a meter without leaving any gap.

Roar!

Suddenly, there was a painful cry coming from the giant snake within the beam.

“It’s no use.”

The red light dissipated, and large, bright spots remained on everyone’s retina. The black cloud had been completely dispersed by the particle beams.

Garen was still hovering in the air without any injuries. His whole body seemed to have an invisible barrier blocking all the attacks from the outside.

Including the gigantic tail of the giant snake.

“The barrier of my Faded Creation can shield against and absorb any attacks that are harmful to me,” Garen calmly explained. It was indeed a little boring to bully a pathetic Level Eight snake with his Level-Ten skills. “At your level, even if the attack is twice as strong, there’s still no use.”

“Alright, the drama is over. For the sake of my future, just obediently offer me your strength…” Garen stretched out his hands. The extremely horrific Ten Thousand Gravitational Force in his palms ferociously slammed toward the giant snake, which had turned around to escape in fear.

Hiss!

The giant snake gave out an awful scream and was caught by an invisible gravitational energy field.

Whish, whish, whish!

Beams of red particles shot out again, trying to stop Garen from catching the giant snake. The people of the Dual-Key Sect were clearly on the edge.

Very soon, there was some vague, Non-Falling-Level aura rising into the air; some of it was flowing from the spaceships which were headed this way from a distance.

The red lights which were shot out vanished completely when they reached less than one meter in front of Garen. The Non-falling-Level powerhouses were all hindered by the Scarlet Snow Sect’s Non-falling-Level Ice Demon Generals who were unable to contain themselves any longer. The Scarlet Snow Sect did not mobilize everyone. Only seven Ice Demon Generals were dispatched, and with that, all the powerhouses of the Dual-Key Sect were stopped. The current Scarlet Snow Sect way different from the weak sect it used to be.

“Obediently submit to our Scarlet Snow! Hahahaha!” Besset chortled and engaged a black-armored man. A huge amount of energy dissipated with white and red explosions in the outer space from time to time, much like a display of fireworks.

“Support Lord Andes!” Someone desperately rushed toward Garen without caring about the pain and the attacks. However, before he could even get close, he was blocked on the outside by a huge energy field.

“It’s over,” Garen reached out and held the snake’s neck, lifting up its entire body.

Whoosh!

Numerous white vines extended wildly toward the giant snake and wrapped around it. A Distorted Seed silently shot out at the snake following the vines.

On the battle fortress, the originally flurried monarchs and others were all taken aback by what they had seen. They had no idea how to react, but very soon, their faces became more and more ecstatic. No one had imagined that Garen would actually be this strong.

“But… There must be a trial for rashly breaching the Alliance Treaty!” Very quickly, the monarchs and others began to worry again.

The fact that the Sect Alliance did not allow mutual attacks was also the biggest rule. Otherwise, if it was a dog-eat-dog state, would the entire Sect Alliance not be left only with the Holy-Lord forces? Where would there be the opportunity for the Scarlet Snow to attack the Dual-Key Sect?

However, at this moment, everyone was stunned by Garen’s sudden outburst.

Even the trio of Osho Ice-Ocean, Ice-crack, and Ice-Grand was completely suppressed by the terrific force field just now.

“Indeed, it is the Lord whom we pursue! I… I…” Osho was a little excited. The supporting order earlier on was given out by him. In the absence of Garen, he was the temporary Sect Master.

“It seems that even if there is no Guardian, Scarlet Snow will also usher in a new era of glory!” Ice-Grand slowly spoke. There was also a hint of excitement which could hardly be concealed in his tone. With strength comes wealth, power, and everything!

No one would not be unmoved by these things. There might be such noble people, but they were definitely not here.

The Dual-Key Sect’s powerhouses were quickly subdued. However, they were all rebellious; they clearly thought that the people of Scarlet Snow did not dare to kill them. The Alliance’s pact was not to be trifled with. Once it was contravened, it would bring about an absolute destruction. There was such a precedent. A powerful sect ignored the treaty and went to attack and invade another small sect. That sect was immediately razed by the Alliance’s powerhouses. All the elite disciples were killed, and the ordinary disciples disbanded. The heritage of the entire sect was wiped out.

Under the brilliant radiance of a star, surrounded by various other stars in the universe, the entire battlefield was enveloped by countless ice-crystal vines. It was impossible to see what was happening on the inside.

Inside the white space, only Garen and the giant snake, which was also the Guardian, were there.

“I have told you everything. You can decide for yourself what you want to choose,” Garen looked calmly at the giant snake before him. He directly told the other party about the catastrophe of Energy Machinists and placed the Distorted Seed in front of it.

He believed that this level of powerhouse absolutely had their own means of judging whether the Distorted Seed was useful to it.

Hence, all he had to do was to calmly show the pros and cons. After all, if these powerhouses of such a level were not willing to be controlled by him, even if they were successfully parasitized, they would not harm him. At most, they would not obey his commands.

After all, the Hellfrost Peacock Queen itself did not have the ability to control the contaminated bodies. If they could be controlled, the Distorted Seed would not have such a powerful enhancing effect. There were advantages and disadvantages to everything.

Especially now that Garen had entered Level Ten, the Peacock Technique had also been boosted and enhanced, entering the peak of a successful completion and beginning to evolve toward Hellfrost Peacock Queen. The Distorted Seed seemed to have boosted to an extreme and horrific level with the further advancement of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique – twelve times.

The horrific property of being able to enhance the powers of the average person by twelve times was the real power of the Distorted Seed.

It could pull all the chaotic emotions in him together, turn them into a substantial energy to boost and strengthen himself, and ultimately control everything with a cold heart. This was the process of controlling the Chaotic Power using the Heart of Ice. It was also the manifestation of the true meaning of Cold Chaos.

Therefore, all who were parasitized could release a natural Cold Chaos and further expand the scope of Hellfrost Peacock’s contamination.

The Black Water giant snake’s pupils kept flashing and changing. At this point, it knew that even if it did not want to, it still had to eat the seed regardless. Moreover, after examining this thing several times, there was no harm in it. Instead, the giant snake felt like it would benefit itself.

“This is the general trend. If we don’t cling together, we will all die!” Garen added one last sentence.

“Regardless of what you say is true or false, at this point, do I have the choice to not eat it?” The giant snake mocked. Although it could destroy the Distorted Seed easily, it was just as it said, it had no choice.

The giant snake opened its mouth and swallowed the Distorted Seed suspended in the air.

The second its gigantic body swallowed the seed, it immediately began to emanate a glowing white light. A kind of white silky network-like light path emerged from its body and appeared on its entire scales and skin.

Hiss…

The surrounding vines quickly recoiled.

Exposing the outer space on the outside world, the people of the Dual-Key Sect had all been subdued. Seeing that the giant snake was safe and unharmed at this moment, both sides appeared to be unusually at peace. With that, the pace of battle gradually slowed down.

“Stop,” Garen’s deep voice came from the helmet.

The people of the Scarlet Snow Sect quickly withdrew and left the battling group. Without the entanglement and obstruction, the powerhouses of the Dual-Key Sect also gradually came to a halt. They were initially almost at the same levels as the Scarlet Snow’s Non-falling Levels. However, among the powerhouses in Scarlet Snow, a few of them, who were initially already at Non-falling Level, gained a great increase of power after consuming the Distorted Seed, thus suppressing them totally. Without Garen’s prior arrangements, they would have been immediately wiped out. It was necessary to know that there was still a difference between the Non-falling Levels.

Garen looked at the giant snake.

At this moment, the entire aura of the giant snake was swelling up more and more, becoming increasingly powerful. There seemed to be some signs of losing control. Twelve times of physical strengthening was simply a big killer move for this kind of horrific presence which utilized the advantage of its body size as a means for livelihood.

“This… This kind of power…?!” He murmured unbelievably.

Whoosh!

A black gas spewed out from the mouth of the giant snake and diffused into the surroundings. The black gas warped into human figures which were holding hands and dancing, resembling the most primitive dance during offerings.

Boom!

Suddenly, the black gas around the giant snake exploded and dissipated, exposing its current body. From the previous gigantic snake body, it had swelled up to twice the original. It then quickly scaled down to a snake-headed person roughly similar to Garen. It had a white robe on and a golden headdress on its head.

A moment later, the fluctuation of its aura had entered Level Nine, reaching the middle stage of Level Nine before stabilizing.

“Thank you for making it happen!” The snake-man opened his eyes and revealed a sincere appreciation and respect. He now really believed Garen’s words. If things were not at stake, how could the other party be as generous as to hand out this kind of treasure, the Distorted Seed, for the outsiders to use?

“We are all Energy Machinists. If we do not unite in the face of such a disaster, we will not have a way out,” Garen shook his head. “So, it’s not that I intend to do this, but the situation compelled me into so doing.”

“If what you say is true, I am willing to form an alliance with the Scarlet Snow on behalf of the Dual-Key Sect. If even a powerhouse such as yourself dread it, I can’t imagine how terrible the upcoming disaster will be,” The giant snake transmitted its voice. That was what it truly thought.

Garen was not anxious. The effect of the Distorted Seed on the nature of mind was not immediate. It would take some time, and there was no need to worry. When the parasitized bodies really wanted to harm him, they would naturally eliminate this idea. The influence of the Distorted Seed would only appear during these times.

Plus, if Garen was at risk and his life was in danger, all the Distorted Seeds would feel it and take the initiative to protect him. This was because Garen, as the initiator of the Distorted Seed, was the source of the powers required to strengthen all the Distorted Seeds.

Once he died, all the Distorted Seeds would lose their effects, thus restoring the fortified parasitized bodies back to their original state, losing the enhanced power. This was often the most unbearable matter to any of the strengthened, parasitized bodies.

“Alright. The Scarlet Snow’s army needs some maintenance. It all depends on you now,” Garen said plainly. The reason he brought the army here to create a big parade so that the people of the Dual-Key Sect would not view them lightly and only send out some small fries.

“If it is maintenance, there is no problem with that,” The giant snake had already believed in Garen at this moment. Its own strength had entered Level Nine for real, and this made it overjoyed. It initially thought that this would be a disaster, but it did not expect it to be a blessing in disguise.

After contemplating for a while, it finally decided.

“My Dual-Key Sect formally joins His Highness the Sect Master of the Scarlet Snow Sect’s alliance, and we will go through thick and thin together,” Its voice suddenly traveled to every Dual-Key Sect’s powerhouse.

As the Guardian, who was the strongest in the sect, it had the supreme authority to decide on the sect affairs in Dual-Key Sect.

As this directive spread out, all the Non-falling Levels of the Dual-Key Sect were at a loss.

Chapter 1116: Alliance 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“It was all a misunderstanding. Our friends from Scarlet Snow did not come to start a war but for other purposes,” no one believed in the giant snake’s words. Just then, one of Scarlet Snow’s Non-Falling Levels shouted for them to come under subjection.

However, the aura and strength of their own Guardian had greatly increased and it did not look fake.

Could it be that it had really submitted to the other party?!

“Return to hold an internal sect meeting!” The giant snake issued the notice straight away. It then looked at Garen. “I have to explain to the top officials first, so I will take leave now.”

“Alright, go ahead,” Garen nodded.

The snake-man turned around and made a hissing sound, saying something. The people of Dual-Key Sect then quickly gathered together and flew toward Planet Dual-Key with him, leaving only a small number of people monitoring Scarlet Snow’s army.

Garen glanced at Osho. “Deputy Sect Master, stay here to coordinate the situation here. If Andes has any doubts, he can go to the Major Battle Arena on Planet Naga to look for me.”

“Yes, Sect Master,” Osho immediately nodded respectfully. “Rest assured that the Guardian of Dual-Key Sect has been dealt with, so there will not be any problems with the others. The key to this sect is that giant snake, unlike the other sects.”

“Of course. The rest of you, follow me,” Garen exclaimed loudly, “Prepare for the jump to the next destination!”

No activity could be seen from outside of the army battleships. However, on the inside, it was already a sea of celebration and excitement. From the initial uneasiness, threats and danger, the situation had swiftly turned around. The opponent had suddenly become one of their own!

This bizarre change made every soldier on the fleet overjoyed. At the same time, they had also begun to develop a kind of dependence and trust in Garen.

The previous doomsday-like horrific war was visible to everyone.

At this moment, all the monarchs’ fleet had a clear sense of belonging to this new Sect Master Garen. Everyone was vaguely entwined and gathered together.

With Garen’s order, there was no need for the Chief of Army’s command. All the battleships of the primary force immediately opened the Jump Energy Furnace and blasted open a pitch-black temporary jump-wormhole in the universe.

Only a few of the secondary battleships were to be left behind so that they could be serviced and modified by the people of the Dual-Key Sect.

About half of the tens of thousands of battleships were gone in an instant, leaving only six thousands of them.

Garen flew back to the battle fortress and was greeted by all the monarchs and Ice Demon Generals with respect and admiration.

*******************

Medium-sized Sect – Silver Bell Stream.

Silver Bell Stream was rather special. They did not recruit disciples on a large scale and did not have a high demand for resources. Therefore, their site was not vast and their key lied in the cultivating of the heart.

However, in recent decades, the new Sect Master of Silver Bell Stream had become very ambitious and had gradually begun to discreetly swallow up and control the surrounding small sects.

Silver Bell Galaxy –

There was a sudden distortion in the dark spatial universe. A huge black round hole emerged from the darkness and groups of densely packed white battleships suddenly shot out from the inside of it. These battleships were long and shuttle-shaped. Each one was the most expensive battleship of the primary force and was encircling a mightier battle fortress in the center.

Garen stood on the fortress and looked at the second target.

“This second target is more difficult. Bring into subjection the two of the strongest sects in the vicinity first. It will be easier to resolve the rest then,” he said slowly.

“Sect Master is brilliant. This time, however, the Sect Master of Silver Bell Stream is not someone who will easily come under the subjugation of others. We will probably have to fight a tough war?” Besset still wanted a real battle to prove himself, so he hurriedly asked for a fight.

“How about letting me be the vanguard to go and check it out?”

Garen looked at him. He was clear about the intention of these newly promoted Non-Falling Levels.

“No need. I’ve heard of this person, Silver Bell Light, before. Entered resonance stage at twenty-two, Inherited Level at fifty and broke through Non-Falling at one hundred and sixty. A genius among the geniuses. If there’s no conflict, we will try not to engage.”

“Unfortunately, even though we don’t engage, they are going to…”

Ice-Grand snorted from the side.

Sure enough, in the distant outer space, a dark cloud shot into the sky from Planet Silver Bell and turned into a huge, fuzzy face. Its mouth spewed out large, invisible airstreams toward Scarlet Snow’s fleet.

The ferocious airstreams rushed toward Scarlet Snow’s fleet and the target they were concentrated on was the battle fortress Garen was at.

“Do not be dismayed as this is not an attack,” Garen raised his hand and motioned for everyone to keep calm and be quiet.

Only then did the fleet quickly calm down and the muzzles of the offensive cannons that were lighting up extinguish. The Ice Demon Generals and others also eased up and were not as nervous as before.

At this moment, an inexplicable voice amid the invisible airstream was transmitted into Garen’s mind.

“Jeros, why are you here at my place and not staying put at Lord Carthage’s territory? Don’t think that your sister can protect you all the time!” The old woman’s voice was clear and chilly.

Garen was startled. This was another insider, but he did not know whether this Silver Bell Light was being controlled or was a spy all along.

“Who are you? How do you know that I am Jeros?” He transmitted in response.

“That’s not right! It’s impossible for Jeros to not know my identity!” That voice suddenly changed slightly.

Garen called out ‘Not good!’ in his heart, and his eyes flashed a fierce light.

“Attack!” He bellowed.

His entire person charged into the sky and darted toward Planet Silver Bell in a few flashes right away.

“Stupid!” Silver Bell Light sneered. The black gaseous face gaped open her mouth to devour Garen.

The massive inhalation sound of the terrifying human face swept in all directions, drawing large amounts of cosmic rays and particle dust to form an enormous whirlpool.

Srraakk!

With a loud sound, the back of Garen suddenly opened up an immense white ice-crystal vine.

Numerous layers of ice crystals stacked to form pairs of white wings, slowly fanning and assembling behind him.

Looking from afar, Garen was like a mythical angel who had descended to the earth. The numerous ice-crystal vines which were glimmering with white light were rapidly deriving like a silk screen and tentacles.

Numerous ice-crystal white wings were flapped backward forcefully, creating an extremely horrifying massive thrust and blasting off toward the black gaseous human face on the surface of Planet Silver Bell.

Boom bang!!

Garen and the human face collided with each other. A clear wave of light exploded and turned into a disk-like halo, spreading across the surface of the planet. The pale blue atmosphere was blown open and a large hole appeared.

Owh!!

The black gaseous face let out a howl. More than half of the face was torn up. Only now did everyone see clearly that in the center of the human face was a robust figure, hovering in a black robe. A large amount of root-shaped black gas was naturally discharged underneath and behind the figure as the supply for the maintenance of the human face.

Garen’s impact hit the figure on the spot. It was apparent that this person was no match for Garen at all.

“Who the hell are you?” The figure yelled.

“Submit to me. Otherwise, die!!” Garen did not waste any words. He flapped his numerous wings right away and dived down. There was no need for any moves. With his current state, he naturally emitted a Level Nine Ten Thousand Gravitational Force. A direct collision would cause great damage to the body of this Silver Bell Light who had not reached the peak of Level Nine.

“Who do you think you are!!?”

Silver Bell Light bellowed wildly.

Roar!!

Her entire body exploded instantaneously, turning into countless black gas. The black gas condensed to form a horrifying gigantic beast, which was like a colossal dragon. It was the size of half a planet.

Roar!!! The dark colossal dragon raised its head and bawled. The weird thing was that unlike the traditional mythical colossal dragon, this gigantic dragon had only one eye on its face, which was a single white eye.

“Dragon gene?” Garen snickered. He was most unafraid of a dragon!

Nine-Headed Dragon’s Soul Will instantly emitted a pale psychedelic fluorescence from the Soul Seed Ring.

At the same time, the single-eye of the black one-eyed dragon silently ejected a thick black light toward Garen.

There was a feeling of absolute destruction in the black light and no one knew what the energy attribute was.

When the black light reached Garen, it suddenly divided into two halves and burst out in high-speed toward both sides.

Garen withdrew his knife-hand. He had only lifted his palm straight up and the destructive black light was directly cut into two. He was not hurt at all.

“Im…impossible!!!” The black one-eyed dragon could not believe that its Destructive Light was handled by the other party without any avoidance and injuries.

It was necessary to know that its Destructive Light was a terrific killer move which could pose a great threat to a top Level Nine. The general Level-Ten ranking Holy Lords would not dare to take the hit upfront. This skill was its greatest dependence as one with the dark colossal dragon’s gene.

The dark colossal dragon’s gene, combined with its own Mech fused within its body, formed a horrific force which had once destroyed an entire planet.

Although it had now transmigrated, its power had weakened a lot and it did not erupt all of its strength, the move was still not something that the general Level Nine could take on!

“Could it be that…you’re not Level Nine?!!”

The dark colossal dragon was anxious and doubtful as it transmitted its voice.

“Submit to me and I will grant you more powerful strength,” Garen was standing high up and overlooking the dark colossal dragon, which was half the size of a giant planet. This kind of giant creature was already an unusual and terrific kind in the dragon species. Unfortunately, Garen’s Nine-Headed Dragon’s Will had been refined and sublimated in the battle against the ancient Nine-Headed Dragon Queen.

Even if it was simply a pure dragon gene, the ancient Nine-Headed Dragon also seemed to be stronger than the other party. This dark colossal dragon did not appear to be this powerful due to gene alone, but it because the inside of its body had absorbed lots of metal-like components. Clearly, it had fused the Mech it absorbed into its body and then utilized the superposition of the Mech and dragon gene to increase its strength.

And so, the result was apparent and the dark colossal dragon was suppressed; easily suppressed by the ancient Nine-Headed Dragon’s Will.

Garen did not even use the true form of his Hellfrost Peacock. Hellfrost Peacock was a giant universal creature ranked even higher than Nine-Headed Dragon. It was also rather well-known in the Endor civilization. Ranking thirty-two, it had long been extinct.

“Submit to you? Who do you think you are?!! Even White King couldn’t make me submit to him!!” Silver Bell Light went berserk. Deep darkness appeared in the single-eye, instantly filling the white single-eye with pitch-black darkness.

“Dark Era!!”

He obviously went all out.

A violent ink-like black airstream suddenly exploded and instantly crossed the distance of light-years apart, tainting the vast space around into darkness.

A small number of Scarlet Snow’s fleet were also affected and quickly swallowed up by the darkness. They were completely submerged without any sound. The entire fleet was not able to respond in time and quickly withdrew chaotically.

All the places that were covered by the darkness became pitch-black, almost like another space.

An abundance of darkness surrounded Garen, wrapping many layers around his entire body and wings.

“This is…”

Garen reached out and touched the darkness, but found that it was only pitch-black and void, without any substance.

In the darkness, waves of invisible and dangerous breaths slowly emerged.

“These are actually…??!” When Garen felt these dangerous breaths, his expression suddenly froze for a moment. He did not expect this kind of thing to be hidden in this darkness! It was something that could make his Hellfrost Peacock shudder…

Chapter 1117: Unite 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Void Creatures!

Those gradually approaching in the dark were all Void Creatures!

In all of Garen’s senses, only the sense of touch was functioning. The rest of his sensory organs were directly obscured by the darkness. Each of the Void Creatures’ breath fluctuation were like ripples on the surface of water. They were spread out from a distance and came into contact with Garen’s skin.

“Void Creatures? I didn’t expect…” Garen’s expression was a little bizarre. Others did not know but the thing which his Living Secret Technique did not fear the most was Void Creatures. This was because Secret Technique was created for the purpose of fighting against Void Creatures.

In the darkness far away, a creature with the upper body of a human and the lower body made up of black fog was closing in. However, just as it got nearer, an extremely powerful and horrific force was emitted out of Garen.

Hiss…

It made a terrified cry and quickly retreated.

These lowly Void Creatures naturally felt oppressed when they were close-by, not to mention to besiege. Initially, there should have been a surge of endless Void Creatures, but they had all disappeared suddenly without a trace.

“Interesting,” Garen tried to look around with his tactile sense, but he found that this kind of darkness had completely cut off his other senses, leaving only the sense of touch. No matter how he tried, there was no way to relieve this kind of state even when he used a greater force.

Boom!!

Garen suddenly released a massive violent airstream and the force field which had barely reached Level Ten and immediately shattered all the Void Creatures which did not manage to run away in time into debris.

However, the entire dark space seemed to remain unmoved and was not affected by this Level Ten force field at all.

“This should be a dimensional technique which has temporarily transferred me to another space and that this space is not something it can control by itself,” Garen vaguely guessed the truth.

“If that is the case…”

He stretched out his right palm and aimed flatly in front of him.

“One Time Fist Pressure.”

Hum!

Several hundred meters of space around suddenly became a glue-like horrific liquid state.

“Two Times Fist Pressure!!”

A more violent energy field broke out from Garen. The Level-Ten force field of Two Times Fist Pressure rocked the surrounding space. It had reached the full force of outbreak from the general Level-Ten Perpetual Motioners, but it still was not enough. The space only shook, but there were no cracks at all.

“Three times!”

Garen increased again. Of the Eighty-eight Times Destructive Impact Fist, he was now able to reach Fifteen Times. After thoroughly passing through the Level-Ten threshold, he himself seemed to have a huge leap in every aspect. It seemed that this was the rule of this universe in that by entering Level Ten, he would naturally receive more endowments. In this way, a boundary to separate the lower grades was drawn. This was a qualitative difference.

The space began to tremble and quavered violently. A strange roaring sound was faintly heard in the distant, as if there was a Void Creature that was simply screaming out of fear.

“I’d like to see how much of my energy field this space can support. Four times!!” A transparent ball of light was already condensed on Garen’s right palm. No light was supposed be seen in the dark space, but at this moment, a ball of transparent stuff was actually emitting an astonishing light on his right palm. It was not a white light, but it also looked like a white light. The light seemed to be able to penetrate all objects including Garen’s body, turning everything into a translucent-like existence.

“Five times!!” Garen spat, initiating the strengthening of the Destructive Impact Fist for the fifth time.

Pooh!!!

The dark colossal dragon on the outside world spurted a mouthful of black blood, which instantaneously evaporated into black gas and fused into the fog around it.

There was a trace of fear in its eyes.

“This fellow… To what extent can he increase his strength?!!” From the general strength at the beginning to the current energy field which could actually affect itself through space, this kind of strength…this kind of pure strength was powerful enough to make people shudder.

“What a delusion to think of confining Sect Master!” On the battle fortress, Ice-Crack and Ice-Grand had seen Garen’s power before and were not worried at all. Their arms were crossed at their chest as they smirked.

“But this kind of extent should have exceeded Level Eight. This indeed is our Sect Master! The strongest person in the whole of our Scarlet Snow in thousands of years,” Besset remarked with a little fanaticism.

“Sect Master will be victorious!”

“My Lord is invincible,” the Two-Headed Werewolves under Garen had a new fortification. After the Hellfrost Peacock Technique entered the peak of success, the Distorted Seed had a twelve-fold enhancement. At the same time, it also caused those who were parasitized to begin a new round of advancement. This kind of advancement were simultaneous. All those who had been parasitized would simultaneously increase in strength through the advancement of the Distorted Seed, regardless of distance.

The Two-Headed Werewolves also felt an increase of horrific strength. One by one, from the general Non-Falling Level, they had advanced to the peak of it.

Meanwhile, as Ice-Crack and others were already at this level to begin with, they had entered into Level Eight directly without any indication. This kind of improvement, which was almost like cheating, all stemmed from the advancement of Garen’s strength. This was the horrific part of Hellfrost Peacock Queen. One person could set off a turmoil and sow the Distorted Seeds continually like a plague, which would be enough to contaminate the whole earth and transform it into a chaotic cold region. This was the dangerous presence which could be ranked thirty-two among the Endor historical creatures!

This number thirty-two placing was no ordinary feat.

Just like the various kind of creatures on Planet Earth. From the ancient times to the present and from the time of the dinosaurs to the present, when all the creatures were put together, what would the concept of placing thirty-two be? At worst, it would also be a tyrannical dinosaur-level, not to mention that the ancient Endor Civilization belonged to a great civilization which spanned across dimensions and time and it had countless horrifying monsters. The strongest among the Void Creatures such as the ancient Nine-Headed Dragon could not even be compared to Hellfrost Peacock Queen.

In the whole of Silver Bell Galaxy at this moment, with Planet Silver Bell as the core, numerous black cracks were gradually appearing in the surrounding space. Like large swaths of spider webs, they spread in all directions.

“Six times!” A great voice traveled out of the void.

Numerous cracks shattered, and the dark colossal dragon uttered a yelp. Various degrees of explosions burst out from all over its body. Each explosion would cause a blood hole of different sizes to appear on its body.

Garen’s enormous white ice-crystal wings re-appeared before all eyes.

He stepped directly out of the crack, and the dark space behind him crashed. Everything returned to the cosmic state where there was no black fog before.

As the dark space was shredded, strands of various rainbow-like substances automatically emerged in the outer space.

“This is?” Garen reached out to grab a strand, attempting to analyze its properties. However, he did not expect these strands to dissipate. They turned into countless rainbow spots and frittered away.

“Looks like they can’t get hold of it,” only then did he turn his gaze on the dark colossal dragon that was still struggling and screaming. The powerhouses of Silver Bell Stream had already rushed out of the planet’s atmosphere and charged at Garen. But then again, they were all immediately stopped by Scarlet Snow’s powerhouses. The current Scarlet Snow was already stronger than the average medium-sized sect. More than a dozen Ice Demon Generals, who were Non-Falling-Level powerhouses, moved in and completely suppressed the entire Silver Bell Stream.

With Garen and the dark colossal dragon as the center, wave after wave of rainbow-like combat force field and ripples were constantly blooming and being destroyed.

Garen finally stretched out his hand toward the dark colossal dragon that was at the gate of death due to the impact from just now.

“Devour!”

He launched his Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s Devourer Ability, which had not been used for some time.

Numerous blue silk threads rushed out of his hand and quickly wrapped the dark colossal dragon in it.

“No!!” The dark colossal dragon was extremely weak and unable to resist. In any case, its Dark Era move had a terribly horrific power. It could confine the general Level Ten Perpetual Motioners with its Level Nine degree so that they could not get out. If it was not for the Six Times Destructive Impact Fist Garen erupted at the end, which had exceeded the general Level-Ten force, he probably could only quietly wait inside that space for the follow-up changes in this move.

A widespread of numerous blue silk threads sputtered from the large mouth on Garen’s palm, covering more than half of the planet instantaneously. The dark colossal dragon that was crouching on it was also completely wrapped in them.

The numerous blue silk threads soon formed a huge white cocoon. The dark colossal dragon struggled slowly and painfully in it, but its action were getting slower and slower…

“There was still unexpected incidents in the end…” Garen’s expression was calm. This was something he had expected way earlier. There was no way of knowing how many pilots were lurking as spies among the Energy Machinists. It was normal to encounter this kind of situation, so he had decided in the beginning that once he encountered such undercover agents, he would quickly suppress and kill the other party with the greatest speed and strength. There was no room for hesitation.

“Kill them all,” Garen ordered calmly while glancing at the rest of the people of Silver Bell Stream. The sound from the golden helmet was instantly conveyed to all Scarlet Snow’s powerhouse. He did not use voice transmission, but through the vibrating resonance of the Distorted Seed, the information was easily passed across space.

Once the order was given, whiffs of aura belonging to Non-Falling Levels suddenly rose again from the battle fortress not far away.

Before this, the people of Scarlet Snow were actually playing tricks with the Silver Bell Stream’s Non-Falling Levels by fighting one against two. Only now did they really get serious.

Soon, silver-white fireworks exploded in the universe. That was Silver Bell Streams’ powerhouses blowing up themselves, wanting to perish together with Secret Snow’s powerhouses. Unfortunately, it was useless as the gap between the two parties was too great.

Scarlet Snow’s Non-Falling Levels had now reached the peak level. Moreover, there was also Ice-Crack and Ice-Grand, who had entered Level Eight silently.

“I have actually entered Level Eight!! Hahahaha!!” Immediately, Ice-Grand’s frantic laughter was heard. Clearly, only when he battled did he realize that he had once again advanced. The source of this advancement clearly came from Garen.

“Thanks to Sect Master! Who knew that I, Ice-Grand, will actually have this day! Hahaha!!” He had already grasped Garen’s level at this moment. It was definitely at Level Ten Holy Lord Level!! Scarlet Snow Sect had produced a Perpetual Motioner!

Due to Garen’s command in advance, he did not spread the word.

“Everyone, speed up.”

Garen slowly watched the ever-shrinking dark colossal dragon-cocoon. Endless streams of pure cold energy surged into his body.

“Who’s there?!” He suddenly flicked his finger and shot out a cool light at the dark void to the right of Planet Silver Bell.

Chapter 1118: Unite 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Hum!

A dazzling white light burst forth and made a whooshing noise before a dark silhouette appeared.

When he realized that something was amiss, a jumping wormhole opened behind the black figure instantly. He retreated swiftly while attempting to escape.

“Roar!!!”

Suddenly, a transparent and shapeless sound wave leaped across the distance in the middle. It sputtered out of Garen’s mouth and struck the wormhole.

A puffing noise could be heard as the wormhole turned into fragile soap bubbles that evaporated quickly. The black figure who had just entered it screamed painfully. His body was instantly cut into two halves by the empty space before it self-detonated.

“There are more here!”

Ice-Crack snorted coldly and extended his hand simultaneously. He grabbed another black figure from a different area and pressed down against his head directly. He was getting ready to subdue his opponent but did not expect this person to detonate himself abruptly. He was able to quickly move backward in time but his clothes were now slightly messy. Ice-Crack’s expression remained somewhat indifferent.

Within a few short moments, the dark colossal dragon was almost digested completely. Garen saw that the evolution and rate of progress of the Hellfrost Peacock Queen inside his body had gradually increased by one point and had reached six percent.

The surrounding powerhouses of Silver Bell Stream were either dead or captured.

“Ice-Crack, stay back and kill all the high-grade Silver Bell members on this planet. The others will continue to set out. We’ll converge on Planet Naga,” Garen released an order before countless strands flew back into his palm cleanly and quickly. Only then did he turn around to leave.

“Yes!” Ice-Crack’s entire body was brimming with tremendous and uncontrollable energy and gravitational forces. These were the symptoms of someone who had recently entered Level Eight but could not perfectly restrain themselves yet.

Garen and Ice-Grand returned to the battle fortress. After a period of jumps, they disappeared in outer space quickly.

******************

“Has Jeros gone mad?!”

A voice sounded within a certain completely dark space in the universe suddenly. It was unclear whether the voice belonged to a man or a woman.

“He actually led Scarlet Snow Sect to invade the other sects everywhere. How bold… He destroyed thirteen individual sects within two days while forming coalition agreements with eight other sects. What is he trying to do?” The sound of another woman’s voice could be heard.

“If his older sister wasn’t here… Hmph!”

“The title of Wraith Monarch has already been conferred upon his older sister. She’s currently vying with her father, the previous Wraith Monarch, for supremacy. After that, she will probably challenge His Majesty. After all, the Wraith Royalty is a declining aristocracy. They were indeed glorious previously but have already become out-of-date now.”

“The times are advancing. Therefore, those who don’t follow the changes will be eliminated.”

Numerous clamorous voices echoed continuously as if many people were trying to speak simultaneously.

Boom!!!

In the faraway starry sky, a star exploded suddenly and burst into dazzling and bewitching halos that illuminated the entire space.

Everything here was instantly illuminated and completely exposed down to the smallest detail.

There was only a single gigantic human figure here. Its upper body was human while its lower body had taken root within an enormous monster on the pitch-black planet.

The strangest part was that it did not only have one head. Instead, it had more than ten human heads that were all attached to one body.

There were both male and female heads that were densely packed together. All of them had long snake-like necks that were connected to the torso. These human heads were debating, discussing and speaking to each other as if they were not a single person but a large group of individuals instead.

The monster looked like a large black tree. The tree roots were indistinct root hairs while the tree trunk was the monster’s torso and body. Meanwhile, the crown of the tree was its countless human heads.

“Do you want to get rid of Jeros?” Within the large crowd, the head of an old man opened his mouth slowly. The surrounding human heads became silent instantly when he opened his mouth.

“What about Nila? Let him decide.”

“I’m afraid that he won’t agree. Despite who he is, he probably isn’t the opponent of the new Wraith Monarch. Other than His Majesty and the Black King, the two major nebulae of our human race and the Finites can only depend on the Golden Thread Flower King who is the only one who can suppress the Wraith Monarch. The others are not her opponents.”

Another head of an old woman opened its mouth as well.

“Within the twenty-five Regent Levels, unless we can find three of them who are closely ranked to the first few Regent Levels and ally ourselves with them simultaneously, we won’t be able to touch Jeros temporarily,” nodded the old man.

“But if we just look on while he plunders recklessly, what’s going to happen in the event that the plan is sabotaged?”

“Isn’t the plan already considered as an overt plot?” said the old man indifferently. “Inform the other nine planets that they should get to work now.”

********************

Boom!!!

There was an intense vibration before a dazzling yet terrifying golden light exploded in front of Garen in outer space.

In the space between Garen and the planet on the opposite side of him, both Ice-Crack and Ice-Grand were currently working together to besiege a mummy-like Guardian whose entire body was ragged.

It was already the third day of their expedition. They had jumped across numerous medium-sized sects. Garen had overlooked the small-sized sects directly because they were not major threats. He had leeched on to more than ten Level Eight Guardians and the one that he was currently suppressing was the nineteenth one.

The golden light dimmed quickly. The white bandages that covered the mummified Guardian’s body completely were gradually frozen solid by the hard ice before most of them broke and cracked. He continued supporting himself while the remaining powerhouses of this sect were already completely seized by the powerhouses of Scarlet Snow and the remaining powerhouses of other sects that were being subdued midway. The slightest chance for resistance was non-existent.

Garen did not even have to undertake the task personally. He merely stood in outer space and looked on quietly while his subordinates besieged his opponents without a trace of foul temperament.

Shh!

He jerked his hand before a sliver of a hidden Distorted Seed poked out. When one of its opponent’s flaws was exposed in the crossfire, the seed immediately took the opportunity to penetrate the body of the dark mummified Guardian.

The entire mummy halted firmly before its body stiffened at once.

Ice-Crack and Ice-Grand who were in the surroundings stopped moving simultaneously as if they had a mutual agreement with each other as well. They watched the following changes that occurred within the mummy with ease. They knew that a powerful new member was about to join them.

This was another frightening aspect of the Hellfrost Peacock. Its powers would increase like a rolling snowball and become stronger. Even in Ancient Endor, no one dared to allow the Hellfrost Peacock to unleash its developed strength.

Although this creature’s own powers were not the strongest, they were able to amplify the strength of others creatures who initially possessed tyrannical powers already. Moreover, they were able to make these creatures surpass themselves!

Golden light that was even more dazzling than before burst forth from the body of the mummy instantly. Numerous golden characters formed ribbon-like things that appeared beside his body and revolved around there. They turned slowly in an extraordinary mysterious manner.

The mummy raised its head before terrifying its Level Nine aura burst forth.

From the lowest stage of Level Nine, the aura expanded to the middle stage of Level Nine quickly before entering Level Nine Peak immediately.

“Oh? Another Guardian that uses his own qualities as his foundation?” Garen was somewhat surprised because the average Guardian’s increment would stop at the lower stages of Level Nine. However, this fellow was apparently different because he was able to rush to the peak of the highest stage directly.

“Strength… What powerful strength!!!” The mummy howled impatiently as if he was being absorbed into a realm that upgraded him unceasingly.

Shh!!!

Another ray of golden light exploded inside his body suddenly.

Even Garen was faintly stunned this time.

“This is…”

Ice-Grand and Ice-Crack were struck by the golden light directly. Large patches of bloody blisters that resembled burn wounds formed throughout their entire bodies before they fled frantically while screaming wildly.

The golden light condensed rapidly and synthesized into a thick golden whip that twisted and swept through outer space violently before moving towards Garen.

“Die!! Hahahaha!!”

The mummy laughed madly while controlling the golden whip and cracking it at Garen.

Garen remained completely still and allowed the golden whip to move closer.

Strangely enough, when the golden whip was about to approach Garen, it shrunk and narrowed itself quickly. From its initial thickness of a few thousand meters, it immediately shrunk to a few hundred meters before merely becoming more than ten meters and finally, only a few meters.

When it finally reached the front of Garen’s face, a sliver that was only as thick as a strand of hair remained.

Poof.

Garen exhaled and blew the strand of golden hair before separating it.

“How could you use the strength that I had bestowed upon you against me instead?” He looked at the other party calmly.

The mummy held its own head suddenly. It seemed as though an enormous switch that was hidden inside his body to control his strength was instantly activated and exploded by Garen’s Distorted Seed. Palpitations that were usually used to pulsate human hearts suddenly spread throughout his body again.

The Distorted Seed was affecting his consciousness. It made him clearly aware that the Distorted Seed was the source of everything. Moreover, the source of the Distorted Seed was Garen.

He only gradually calmed down after a long time before the strength throughout his entire body weakened.

The golden light in outer space slowly disappeared and weakened as well before everything returned to tranquility.

The mummy finally calmed down completely. He raised his head and looked at Garen silently.

“I had initially assumed that old age was right around the corner. I never expected that…” There was an indefinite expression on his face when he looked at the skin and muscles beneath his bandages that had already regained their youthfulness. His gaze was complicated.

“I’m willing to return as your subordinate,” the madly brutal nature throughout his entire body was now subjugated. He finally understood that the source of his own strength and life came from the man in front of him. Hence, he chose to submit himself to him for the sake of his life and this intoxicating strength instead.

“Then, the next one.”

Garen turned around and flew towards the battle fortress.

“You should come with me.”

An ominous glint glimmered in the depths of the mummy’s eyes. However, it was finally suppressed by the Distorted Seed. Once the connection to the source was made clear, he could no longer attempt to attack Garen in the end. Instead, he hurried behind him frantically.

As for the sect behind him, he was never concerned about that thing. He had only chosen to train there secretly to quietly improve his own powers and benefit himself. Thus, he became the founder of a sect there. However, now that he had another path, there were naturally no more reasons for him to remain here anymore.

While flying towards the battle fortress and following Garen, shock stirred in the mind of the mummy suddenly.

Other than a few normal people on the battle fortress, the rest were Non-falling Levels and the two Level Eight powerhouses that besieged him recently.

However, the thing that truly shocked him the most was another group of people who were the only ones standing on another side.

There were four terrifying human figures who were completely clad in white robes that were emitting faint chills. Each one of their bodies were enveloped in distortions, making it completely impossible for people to see their bodies and appearances clearly.

However, the similarity that all of them shared was their great power!!

Level Nine! All of them were on Level Nine!!

Apparently, none of these four people were lower than this grade. The two strongest ones were even Level Nine Peaks like himself. Perpetual Motioners required Ultimate Boards but this was not something that could be simply achieved by strength upgrades. Therefore, Level Nine Peak was the pinnacle of the Ultimate Board.

“There will be five people including you,” said Garen indifferently. “Be mindful of hiding yourself and don’t expose your identity. All of you must stay here and cannot leave. After a short while, a time will come when I will need you all to strike with all of your strength.”

The mummy nodded and walked beside the four people. It used its entire body to distort space in a similar manner to cover the gazes and fields of vision of the others.

Garen nodded his head in a satisfied manner.

Most of the Star Regions near Scarlet Snow Sect were cleared away while the many of the sect domains that were slightly further away were gotten rid of as well. The strongest Guardians of at least half of the thirty-six medium-sized sects were either openly or secretly leeched on by him. After that, the Alliance would have definitely dispatched their powerhouses to obstruct him already. However, even if the Alliance had sent people, what grades would they be? Would they be Level Nine or Level Ten?

Although Level Ten was the pinnacle of the Energy Machinists, there were only three Level Tens among them. This meant that the Alliance could not engage them easily. Therefore, they could only dispatch Level Nines. However, they would have to be the most powerful ones in Level Nine.

Chapter 1119: Parasitism 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Meanwhile, within the Federation of Energy Machinists, these few people were the strongest in Level Nine. They each represented the fifteen strongest large-sized sects within the Big Three Sects. There would generally be more than a few strong individuals in the Big Three Sects who were Level Nine. Moreover, they were generally found in states of semi-seclusion and would never act rashly. All the famous powerhouses were Level Nine Peaks. Every one of them was an experienced veteran who had fought in numerous battles. Hence, they were not opponents that others would want to go up against.

“There will probably be a tough battle after that,” Garen said softly while exhaling slowly. Within a few short days, he had reached the limit of his abilities to control such a huge amount of strength. There were five Level Nine powerhouses, two of whom were Level Nine Peaks. There were eighteen of them including the Level Eight Peak Guardian who had undergone parasitism.

During these few days, the Distorted Seed unleashed unimaginably terrifying effects. It resembled a rolling snowball that kept getting bigger.

However, the Energy Machinists were not idiots. Instead, they were merely caught unprepared during the attack. Moreover, those at the top were already aware of the Mech Pilots’ plot. Hence, their energy was mainly focused in that area now. They had temporarily no time to attend to Garen and this allowed him to develop himself steadily for three days.

After all, neither the lower medium-sized sects nor the small-sized sects were threats in the eyes of the higher grades. Meanwhile, when the total number of medium-sized sects were added up, how many Level Nines were there? Even if all of them joined together, they would not necessarily be able to defeat a large-sized sect, much less giants like the Big Three Sects that stood at the very top.

However, no one could imagine that Garen could actually increase the strength of the powerhouses tremendously. He upgraded numerous Level Eight powerhouses to either Level Eight Peaks or Level Nines while upgrading the Level Nines to Level Nine Peaks. Terrifying increment like this allowed Garen to form an enormous organization of power quickly. His current power was already almost on par with most large-sized Level Nine sects.

With Scarlet Snow as the center, he had occupied large stretches of Star Regions in his surroundings to form the Scarlet Snow Alliance.

“Everyone, return to the base,” Garen commanded briefly. Scarlet Snow’s ship convoys opened the jumping wormhole immediately and flew towards their own planet.

The next task that he needed to undertake was to wait for the response of the Federation of Energy Machinists. However, Garen could predict that he already possessed sufficient power in the circumstance where he did not stir the interests of the large-sized sects. Thus, there was a high likelihood that the conclusion would be as he had expected…

*********************

In the cold dark universe.

A small shroud of white gas enlarged and quickly expanded into the size of a human. A tall man who wore white earrings walked out slowly. There was a straightforward and sincere smile on his face. One of his eyes was red while the other was as blue as a crystal of the most superior purity.

“You actually took the opportunity to annex my territories while I was facing trouble. How interesting…”

He glanced in the direction of Planet Scarlet Snow from afar and licked his lips.

Suddenly, a red meteor shot directly in his direction from afar. It brought along a gigantic mass that was generally associated with planets and pulled the gravitational force towards the man firmly when it charged at him.

“Still not giving up?!” The white-haired man’s expression changed slightly and he cursed the other person in a furious but quiet tone. He turned around and left before turning into a shroud of white gas and disappearing from his original location.

The red meteor did not display any signs of stopping. Instead, it rushed towards the Star Region on another side directly.

Not long after, a burst of bewitching red light suddenly exploded in the faraway Star Region. The redness diffused throughout all four corners and dyed the numerous planets in bright scarlet shades.

“Carthage, save me quickly!!” yelled a voice in the middle of the red light explosion.

“No one can save you now!” said a different voice of a young girl loudly in a pleased tone. “Hehehe, you can keep screaming! No one will save you even if you scream until your throat is damaged!”

The red light became more blinding.

“Holy Lord Phoenix, don’t bully others!! Don’t assume that I’m afraid of you!! Ahh!!” A painful scream could be heard before the sentence trailed off.

On the other side, a white silhouette floated in outer space quietly while glancing at the center of the glittering red light without moving at all. A long white sword hung at his waist. The plain-looking white robe that covered his entire body and the apathetic expression on his face gave off a strange cold disposition.

While glancing at the glimmering red light, Carthage did not display the slightest intention of making a move.

“Scarlet Snow Sect… Looks like it’s time for me to return…”

Whoosh!

A white meteor shot over suddenly from afar and struck his body violently before disappearing completely in the blink of an eye.

Another whooshing noise was heard soon after as a white meteor flew over again and crashed into his body before vanishing instantly. If someone could see the white meteor clearly, they would realize that there was actually a blurry human figure inside it.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh…

Numerous white meteors flew over from all four directions quickly and flowed into Carthage’s body. He could see these white meteors clearly and easily now.

Shockingly, they were actually several human figures that were exactly like him. Regardless of their dressing or appearances, their icy dispositions were almost the same.

These white meteors increased slowly and became even more densely packed. This extraordinary sight remained for a few good minutes.

Finally, Carthage exhaled slowly when the last meteor flowed into his body. The gravitational forces around his body suddenly rose from one thousand times to ten thousand times within Level Nine before it shrunk back down again from ten thousand times instantly. In the blink of an eye, it diminished itself completely into a blurry black hole that could fit in the center of his body.

Black holes– they were the symbols of true Level Ten Perpetual Motioners. All Perpetual Motioners possessed a great weapon of destruction that caused them to suffer a common downfall. It was their Bodily Black Holes.

This was not a normal little black hole. Instead, it was a gigantic inverse space hole that could swallow everything endlessly. It could instantly connect actual and inverse space fully while its tremendous gravitational distortions could tear time and space into shreds. Hence, all creation would be ripped apart by its terrifying gravitational forces instantaneously.

The planets were not excluded.

Therefore, this was the key reason why it was difficult to counter Perpetual Motioners. When they were offended, they would simply take everything down with them and cause everyone to perish together. The Bodily Black Holes were the greatest symbols of Level Ten Perpetual Motioners. However, their limitless energy was merely sourced from their endless absorption of inverse space’s energy that they used in actual space. That was all.

In reality, the black holes in the universe were divided into two types. The first type was a matter black hole that was naturally formed. Once the density of its own mass reached a terrifying stage, it would form even greater traction. The traction was so strong that it was impossible for even light to escape from being absorbed into a part of its body. Therefore, humans called them black holes because they could not see these things. In reality, these matter black holes were actually high-density objects that were similar to planets that died from exhaustion. Since light could not escape due to the overly intense gravitational forces, these things appeared black and were then known as black holes.

However, the second type of black hole was different because it was an antimatter black hole. This was the scariest thing.

These were physically formed in the bodies of Perpetual Motioners. Since the antimatter black holes could capture light similarly, they would also appear black. They were also known as black holes because of this reason but had different matters from the first type.

This type of black hole followed the principles of the antimatter universe. They were the boundaries between time and space of the universe. Therefore, the living matter that was sucked inside them would decompose from actual matter to antimatter. They would shrink into an unimaginable stage before turning into the most basic energy particles that would enter the inverse spatial universe. As such, their souls would also be ground up into the most basic energy particles.

This resembled a grinder that would stir constantly and swallow everything unceasingly.

This type of black hole would not grow bigger but could never be filled completely. Moreover, its powers were much stronger than the first type.

The Perpetual Motioners themselves were feeble forces of balance. They walked and lived between two spatial universes and transcended time and space. They were constantly situated within unimaginably enormous gravitational forces.

When the final white meteor surged through his body, Carthage’s entire being seemed to become even more perfect. His qualities were purely icy cold in the beginning but now felt as if they were faintly brimming with hints of strength that were so powerful that they were dissipating.

“Chinande, it seems like something unexpected has occurred within your plans.”

Red light flashed before a young girl whose red hair was tied in two separate ponytails appeared above Carthage. She wore a pink dress and did not look older than five or six years old. She looked like an elementary schooler who had recently started schooling. Nothing was amiss but strangely enough, the little girl’s mouth was opened and a red colored little person who was the size of a fingernail was sitting on her fair and tender tongue. That was actually another little red-haired girl who was a few times smaller than her. Her appearance was exactly the same as the girl on the outside, down to the backpack that they carried, except that she was completely naked.

The voice came from her body.

Chinande’s gaze fell on the little girl on the tongue. His pupils dilated slightly as if they were lacking moisture while his machinery turned a few times.

“What do you think?”

“I would never dare have any opinions towards you, Captain. I’m merely somewhat curious that someone was actually able to escape from your plan. This is a rare occurrence,” the little girl on the tongue smiled charmingly. She gave off a tempting sort of seduction.

“You want to come along?”

The pupils of Carthage, who should perhaps be called Chinande instead, did not move at all. He resembled a zombie who was glaring at the other person somewhat scarily.

After retrieving all of his parts, it seemed as though he had become less natural instead. He appeared stiffer and more mechanical now.

“Can I?”

“It’s up to you.”

Chinande turned around simply grabbed something before a black crevice split open in the space in front of him suddenly. He flew into the crevice gently straight away while the little girl in the red dress followed behind him frantically.

“Wait for me!!”

The white-haired man from earlier appeared again. A straightforward and sincere smile was still hung across the corner of his mouth. However, his clean and pure body from earlier was now covered in cuts and bruises. Smoke was coming out of his hair while his face was covered in jet-black smog.

The man followed the two others from behind closely before instantly turning into a shroud of white gas that shot into the crevice and fully disappeared cleanly.

******************************

Planet Scarlet Snow

Garen returned to the headquarters with everyone again. The surroundings of the entire Planet Scarlet Snow were densely packed with various suspended defensive cannons. Numerous defensive space station satellites guarded the entire planet like a fierce pitch-black beast that was powerful and terrifying.

Scarlet Snow Sect had already launched surprise lightning attacks during the past few days. The military exploits of these attacks were unimaginable. Twenty sects were either destroyed or subjugated by Scarlet Snow while more than ten others had joined their alliance.

The Scarlet Snow Alliance had finally formed a brand new structure now. It inclined the center of the entire nebula of the human race towards the north while forcibly occupying a small area of its star atlas to form a colossus that greatly surpassed the previous Scarlet Snow Sect.

Within an extremely short period of time, Garen’s reputation had spread widely throughout various large-sized sects through instantaneous communication, allowing him to enter their field of vision.

Chapter 1120: Parasitism 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Scarlet Snow Headquarters, in the courtroom.

A golden pillar of light that reached the sky and touched the earth had shot down directly from the outer space, descending upright onto the basilica right in front of the courtroom.

Garen led all of the Scarlet Snow Sect powerhouses to stand in front of the golden light. There was a modest smile on his face when he gazed upon the light pillar.

Shh…

The light pillar scattered, revealing a group of nine people inside.

These nine people wore peculiar golden clothes. Eight of them looked considerably normal, but the leader looked exceptionally strange.

He was a Two-faced Person!

He had a man’s face in front and a woman’s face on the back of his head. It seemed like these male and female faces were sliced into two halves and glued together from the back. It was extremely peculiar.

The leader wore a golden skirt-like outfit. He had no hair, and his shiny bald head reflected some faint, silver shades. He had obviously absorbed some specialized substances into his body.

“Scarlet Snow Sect! How daring!” The moment he descended, the leading Two-faced Person spoke in a shrill yet bewitching voice. He used a universal language to chide Garen loudly, but he spoke very strangely.

“I’m here to pay a formal visit to the great Lord Emissary,” Garen was still dressed in a white robe and golden helmet. The helmet made it impossible to see his face underneath clearly, as everything was merely pitch-black.

He led his group of Non-falling Level powerhouses to face the Two-faced Person and the others before bowing slightly.

“Pay a formal visit? Do you still think that it’s necessary for you to pay a formal visit after you openly and brazenly broke the rules of the Alliance?!” The Two-faced Person’s entire body was brimming with extremely terrifying distorted forces when he exposed his Level Nine Peak powers completely without bothering to conceal them at all.

Aside from him, there were two Level Nines among the eight other people behind him, while the remainders of them were Level Eights. It was clear that only large-sized sects could receive insider information like this.

“Despite the Major Battle being in sight, you actually dared take advantage of the void and enter before assaulting the headquarters of the other sects. According to the rules of the Alliance, a severe capital punishment in accordance with the laws may be inflicted upon those who break the rules!” said the Two-faced Person sternly in a shrill voice.

The atmosphere became tense suddenly. The powerhouses of the Scarlet Snow became anxious instantly, as auras of mutual hostility filled the air around as if they could strike at any time.

However, Garen raised his hand and signaled everyone to remain calm. He faced the other party head-on and opened his mouth.

“Allow me to inform you, Lord Emissary. The small-sized sects received support from the other sects that were their close friends. The great concern regarding this matter made it impossible for us not to dispatch our troops immediately to help the other sects eliminate any future troubles…” Garen explained in a respectful tone. “A shocking secret was concealed within it as well. All of the powerhouses who were there can attest to this.”

Garen lowered his head immediately after that and transmitted a few voice messages.

Although the Two-faced Person and the others were initially harboring traces of an unconcerned attitude, their gazes became more serious after this voice transmission instead.

The voice transmission ended quickly. Garen had even transferred a series of images that were actually his memories of the battle between him and the dark colossal dragon.

After they had finished looking at the images.

“Everything that you mentioned was real?!” The Two-faced Person’s tone relaxed. The spies among the Energy Machinists had apparently infiltrated them to this extent. This was simply unimaginable! Since they were a large-sized sect, they were unfortunately unconcerned about the small and medium-sized sects. He recalled this now and thought about the consequences that would occur in the event that these sects suddenly revolted during the Major Battle…

The aftermath would be unimaginably severe!

The Two-faced Person himself was of a high ranking, he also knew that some Mech Pilots were against the overall arrangement of Energy Machinists. However, he had not expected that the situation had reached this stage. Moreover, he had never anticipated that his heart would suddenly suffer a great shock the moment he heard Garen mention these things.

“I can assure you that everything I said was true!” Garen answered in a strangely confident manner. “If you don’t believe me, you can look for the other Guardians of the sects that I’ve visited and ask them yourself. It’s impossible that this matter is a lie. I do not have the powers great enough to lie about this.”

“The Major Battle will officially begin in a few days! If what you said is true, we will have to deploy even stronger forces here as well. However, we’re afraid that it’ll be very difficult to transfer forces to attend to this area!” The Two-faced Person’s tone had calmed down. “If what you said is true, you deserve great credit in this matter! I will relay your merits to the three Holy Lords properly!”

When he saw that Garen’s powers were clearly at Level Nine Peak through the images, the Two-faced Person looked squarely at him now. Moreover, he started to humble himself when facing Garen after receiving such major news.

“Thank you very much, Lord Emissary.”

“The pleasure is mine, Sect Master Garen,” The Two-faced Person was more polite now. “I was wondering if the Guardians of any other sects in the Scarlet Snow Alliance were here. I was hoping to meet them personally and ask them briefly about the entire situation.”

“This isn’t a problem,” nodded Garen. “My own sect accidentally received a mysterious and specialized treasure that can strengthen one’s own powers recently. Since we sensed that the Energy Machinists would probably encounter great difficulties, I resolved to invite a few Sect Masters with whom I have good relations to come forward and share this with me. Right now, they’re coincidentally here as well and have not left yet. Lord Emissary, you can question them freely at any time.”

He purposely emphasized the treasure and its strengthening capabilities clearly when he mentioned both of them. His intentions to bribe the other party could not be any clearer.

The Two-faced Person’s gaze faintly stirred suddenly when he heard this. A treasure that could upgrade their powers at this grade was simply something extremely precious. These abilities were not something that could be achieved by just using anything.

“Lord Emissary, this way please,” Garen extended his hand and led the group of nine people toward a stone staircase on another side that led to a banquet hall.

The remaining Ice Demon Generals exchanged glances secretly and dispersed naturally after taking the hint. Only the Level Eight Osho Ice-Ocean remained like an old housekeeper who began acting in a friendly manner towards the few Emissaries.

Along the way, Garen used the Imprint to openly inform the few Guardians to come forward and pay their respects to the Lord Emissary formally.

The few Guardians over there who had undergone his parasitic controls displayed certain vigilant responses respectively. They clearly exhibited attitudes of not wanting to share the treasure that they had received with even more outsiders.

This made the heart of the Two-faced Person, who had assumed he was eavesdropping on the voice transmissions, even more determined.

“Didn’t you say that we were only sharing it among these few people? Why is there another additional Emissary now?” said the mummy through the voice transmission unhappily. “Should I be worried that he won’t even be able to reach Level Nine Peak?”

“The Lord Emissary is different. He’s unlike the previous Emissaries…” Garen persuaded him with kind words before the mummy reluctantly agreed and cut off the connection while huffing.

“Was that the golden mummy? I’ve heard of this person. Wasn’t he just on Level Eight? How did he get to Level Nine suddenly?”

Within the group of Emissaries, a blue-haired girl behind the Two-faced Person opened her mouth and asked suddenly.

“This…” Garen made a face which hinted that it was difficult to explain.

“It’s a scam!” The woman stopped asking disdainfully.

They were all Two-faced People, but some of them were unsatisfied with the blue-haired woman. This allowed Garen and the others to see that this group was not completely united.

The Level Nine Peaks of the large-sized sects were unlike the average Level Nines. Their trump cards could be similar to the dark colossal dragon or perhaps even stronger. Moreover, they could also use other means of resolving their issues. Naturally, Garen would not choose to use violence.

The group was led into the banquet hall quickly.

A few Guardians were already waiting there. Although their behaviors were secretly disdainful, they were still forced to put in sufficient effort into their appearances. After all, these Emissaries represented the entire Federation of Energy Machinists.

When they entered the banquet hall, the group of Emissaries paid no attention to the handsome men and beautiful women who were currently serving the food while fluttering about like gorgeous butterflies. Instead, the gazes of these Emissaries were focused on the few Guardians who had stood up from their seats.

The Energy Machine Imprints of the Energy Machinists in this grade could be used as extensive databanks. The information of these Guardians would naturally be included inside as well. Within a short span of time, the group was clearly aware of the exact details regarding the three Guardians here. They even uncovered the strength of their sects and some other detailed information.

However, the thing that truly shocked them was that these few people’s strength and the information that was listed were severely mismatched. On average, their strength was critically underestimated by at least a full level!

Even so, how significant would the difference of one level be if they had already reached Level Eight?

One would only need to compare the quantities of those of Level Eight and those of Level Nine to discover the magnitude of the obstacles between those two levels.

According to the official statistics, there were more than sixty thousand Level Eight powerhouses in the entire human race.

On the other hand, there were only more than five thousand that reached Level Nine. This included the number of internal Mech Pilots in the entire human race. However, since it was impossible to estimate the current total human population, these were merely rough calculations from earlier.

The human race and the Finite people ruled more than ten thousand habitable planets and over a hundred thousand inhabitable ones. There were at least seven to eight billion people on each of these planets.

These enormous populations were spread across two gigantic nebulae.

There were only over five thousand Level Nine powerhouses throughout these populations. The difference between them was extremely terrifying.

After all, not every planet occupied Guardians that were Level Eight or above. Only the important planets would have Level Eight, Level Nine, or even Level Ten Perpetual Motioners defending them. Most of the remaining planets would naturally not be allocated with such an important military strength.

Moreover, these statistics were basically stagnant for more than a thousand years without any changes. Throughout a period of over a thousand years in the other worlds, there were seemingly no groups of Level Eights that could break through to Level Nine, or at least there were not enough to affect the numbers and cause changes. The difficulty could be seen through this.

In order for a Level Eight to enter Level Nine, other than experiencing at least a thousand years of hardships, they would also need to grasp the realm of the Sublime Board. They would experience soaring improvements if they were able to grasp these realm-like things. However, it would be a complete waste if they were unable to comprehend it throughout their entire lives no matter how much of it they accumulated.

The Emissaries were shocked now because these three people who were only listed as Level Eights in the information a thousand years ago had apparently entered Level Nine instantly. It would not be a big deal if they had merely entered Level Nine, but now they were apparently at the Level Nine Peaks as well!

“This…” The Two-faced Person suppressed the shock in his mind forcibly. He instantly understood that this was definitely the effect of the treasure that Garen had mentioned earlier.

“Lord Emissary, you guessed it correctly,” Garen transmitted his voice to him secretly. “This treasure is the reason why I went on an expedition to form an alliance. I knew that my own sect could not support first-rate resources like this at all. This is the primary reason that the Scarlet Snow Alliance was truly established. If you are willing to join us, I will naturally give you a part of this treasure, Lord Emissary. This treasure can only be used once on each person but it can increase and strengthen various aspects of one’s physical qualities by over tenfold. It’s extremely terrifying!”

The Two-faced Person was already abnormally greedy from the start. A tinge of expectation flashed in the depths of his eyes immediately after he heard the things that were said.

“Let me see this treasure first.”

The remaining Emissaries could not suppress their curiosity and expectations either. They were all looking at Garen.

Garen invited everyone to sit down first.

“Lord Emissary, you arrived at such a good time. If you, Lord Emissary, became a member of our alliance, our forces would definitely increase greatly,” When he noticed that the gazes of the crowd were hopeful but somewhat impatient as well, Garen did not say too much.

He turned his hand and faced his palm upwards. A spherical flesh ball covered in blue tentacles lay on his palm quietly.

Chapter 1121: Goodbye 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“This treasure resembles a type of parasite. Once it enters the body, it can use its supplementary state to form a layer of ice armor outside. Next, it will enhance the various qualities of the body. Moreover, it will also amplify them greatly!” Garen explained.

He spoke as he passed the Distorted Seed to the Two-faced Person.

The Two-faced Person took it with a steady expression on his face. The moment it touched his hand, he quickly began scanning and analyzing its composition with his Energy Machine Imprint. As for his task of coming here this time to punish the Scarlet Snow Sect, he had decided to pardon that minor incident some time ago. Since he was already at Level Nine Peak now, if this thing could really produce harmless increments throughout his body, Level Ten would truly exist if he could go any higher! When that time came…

A trace of nervousness flashed in the depths of the eyes of the woman behind the Two-faced Person suddenly when she thought of this as well.

Inside the banquet hall, the mummy and the two others were completely silent, save for the occasional cold sneers that escaped them. It seemed as though they were not giving the Two-faced Person any face at all. This was indeed true, considering the strength of their current alliance was already incredibly powerful. Since they did not have to yield to most of the large-sized sects, they were completely unafraid of the large-sized sects that were backed and represented by the Two-faced People Emissaries. If it was not for their positions as the Emissaries of the Alliance, these people would probably harbor intentions of striking out and getting rid of these Two-faced People.

The confrontational atmosphere in the banquet hall was clearly intense, despite being restrained by the three Level Nines.

“Indeed… This treasure possesses extremely powerful incremental abilities!” The Two-faced Person sighed in admiration and wonder as he put the Distorted Seed down. “However, it has a deformity.”

“What deformity?” One of the male Emissaries could not help but ask.

The Two-faced Person glanced at him and said, “Its attributes.”

“Attributes?”

A few Emissaries reacted and understood immediately. When they felt the chills that were being emitted by the Distorted Seed, they clearly understood what he meant when he mentioned its attributes.

“Its energy attribute is not bad,” The Two-faced Person looked at Garen and smiled. “However, although this treasure can increase powers, it will turn the attributes of its parasite’s hosts into frost-types. Moreover, it can even naturally collude with others of the same species through certain channels. In other words, after using this treasure, the user will theoretically be changed into a different race with a different type of genetic composition.”

“Lord Emissary is indeed amazing!” said Garen in a tone that displayed an uninhibited admiration. “You could see its core with just one look!”

“What about the side effects?” The blue-haired female Emissary asked softly. She was somewhat interested now as well. However, she did not have to worry about conflicts in this aspect at all, as her genes did not have any attributes.

“The side effects are very simple,” said the Two-faced Person quietly. “That depends on one’s personality. Your personality will be affected and manipulated into becoming slightly colder. It is related to this treasure’s energy transformation mechanics. Of course, in comparison to the functions, these side effects are simply negligible… Tch, tch, it’s truly the epitome of a marvelous treasure…” He could not help but praise it.

“Colder personalities?” None of the people who were seated here considered it as a problem. After living for too long, it was almost inevitable that their personalities had already become cold.

“Lord Emissary, what are you trying to say then?” Garen opened his mouth and asked again.

“Why don’t I test this treasure out first and see its effects? How about that?” The Two-faced Person smiled and looked at Garen. “After all, as a Level Nine Peak, it might be a problem whether this increment will be effective towards me. I’m unsure whether there are great quantities of these treasures either.”

“You don’t have to worry about the numbers. I only established this alliance because their quantities were too great. I was hoping to gather everyone’s powers to protect this secret that belongs to us, the Energy Machinists,” Garen said in a ‘calm’ manner.

“If that’s the case, I don’t have to worry then…” The Two-faced Person nodded before opening his mouth and preparing to swallow the Distorted Seed directly. It was clear that he only knew that this was the best method of parasitism after analyzing it.

“Hold on!”

The blue-haired woman spoke suddenly the moment the Distorted Seed was placed at the side of his mouth.

The Distorted Seed was suspended beside the Two-faced Person’s mouth before he placed it down again and looked at the blue-haired woman.

“Trisha Yuko, what do you think?” The Two-faced Person asked softly while furrowing his eyebrows slightly.

The gaze of the blue-haired female Emissary scanned across Garen and the few Guardians while her eyebrows were knitted together tightly.

“To be able to obtain a treasure like this so easily, it’s almost as though they are gifted to you. Can such a wonderful thing really happen in this world?”

None of the three Guardians made a sound. They merely minded their own business and sat in their seats without batting an eyelid.

Meanwhile, Ice-Ocean, who stood beside Garen, smiled faintly.

“Lady Emissary, you might have misunderstood something. In the beginning, we dared not believe that such a treasure existed either. However, after numerous tests, we only let our guard down after discovering that they were indeed no serious side effects. It was only after then were we able to take such initiatives, because of our selfish motives. If we could drag a few lords into our alliance, our forces would become even greater as well. In reality, we who have used this treasure are already essentially considered as another race. We can even use this treasure to naturally transmit messages and communicate throughout great distances without using other technologically-advanced means.”

“Is it similar to telepathy?” asked the blue-haired woman while furrowing her eyebrows.

“You could think of it like that.” Ice-Ocean maintained his gentle smile. When he stood beside Garen, neither of them looked abnormal at all.

“Do you have any more questions? Miss Yuko!” The Two-faced Person was already somewhat unhappy now.

“I’m worried about letting you use the treasure first. You should let me go first instead,” The blue-haired woman named Yuko reached her hand out to grab the Distorted Seed from the Two-faced Person.

The Two-faced Person’s gaze flickered. Nonetheless, he placed the seed down and allowed the other person to snatch it.

“I’ve known long ago that Miss Yuko possesses the Blood of Disintegrating Everything. This is a good opportunity to broaden my horizons. If this treasure can affect your genes and blood vessels, it’s truly a priceless treasure then!”

Yuko declined to comment and did not even look at him when she stuffed the Distorted Seed directly into her mouth.

The blue Distorted Seed resembled a reel of thread that rolled directly down her throat into her esophagus. It melted and disintegrated speedily before being absorbed into the surroundings of the tube walls of her throat.

Woo…

Yuko’s expression turned slightly strange. It seemed as though her body was undergoing some unspeakable pain.

Shrouds of faint chills began spreading across the surface of her body. This allowed Garen, who was slightly anxious earlier, to calm down now. After all, the Hellfrost Peacock was merely one of the Void Creature species. Since the universe was so vast, it was impossible for everything to pollute and invade it freely. He was suddenly worried after hearing the Two-faced Person say that Yuko’s blood was the Blood of Disintegrating Everything. The Distorted Seed might not be effective towards that.

However, it looked like this female Emissary’s genes did not seem to determine anything here.

Everyone waited quietly and looked at the changes that the blue-haired woman’s body experienced.

The chills became denser and more intense… The chills of the few other Guardians were also faintly aroused before the temperature of the entire banquet hall decreased by more than ten degrees. Layers of white frost froze on the bodies of a few normal people, whose entire bodies were shivering while they were standing guard outside.

With the passing of the seconds, shrouds of faint white gas spurted out of Yuko’s mouth quickly and dispersed throughout the air in front of her. She closed her eyes slowly. She could feel that thin layers of ice were currently covering her body continuously. These ice layers felt extremely strange, as they could twist freely. Unlike solid ice, they were not firm or fragile. Instead, they were as flexible as rubber but cold nonetheless.

“Such a strong, enhanced ice armor…” said Yuko while sighing in admiration slightly.

“How is it?” asked the Two-faced Person in a somewhat expectant voice while leaning his body forward slightly.

“Still alright. However, unlike my expectations, the effects are not as… Ooh!” Yuko widened her eyes suddenly before the chills around her whole body broke out abruptly. The chair that she was sitting on froze quickly and was covered by a thick layer of solid ice.

Whoosh!

A jet-black disc flashed in front of her eyes suddenly. The violent and powerful aura was about to surge out before she suppressed it forcibly.

“What… What powerful strength!” Yuko could not help but cry out.

The Energy Field around her body twisted violently. The moment she spat out a mouthful of cold air, it seemed as though the entire Planet Scarlet Snow could hear the sound of her exhaling.

Her every move could influence the turning of the planet. This was a sign of the Level Nine Peak!

Through her efforts within a few short moments, Yuko was apparently able to enter the peak of Level Nine from the lower stage directly! The Two-faced Person and the other Emissaries to stare at her blankly because of this.

“This… is really… a priceless treasure!” The Two-faced Person’s serious greed could not be inhibited anymore. His own gaze and those of the others were all focused on Garen’s body. “Sect Master Garen, I don’t know if this treasure…”

“Don’t worry, Lord Emissary. Everything has been prepared accordingly.” Garen’s voice echoed from beneath the helmet respectfully.

A few more Distorted Seeds appeared in his hand. Each of these Distorted Seeds resembled woolen balls that floated automatically. They separated themselves before flying towards the few Two-faced People.

*********************

On a yellow planet within a ring of planets outside Planet Scarlet Snow, three silhouettes appeared out of thin air suddenly on an ashen, stony meteorite that was a few kilometers large.

These three people stood on the stony meteorite and glanced at the gigantic, crimson Planet Scarlet Snow quietly. A few bits of dust and debris in the outer space dodged the sides of their bodies automatically, as though they were sentient. However, upon closer observation, an invisible yet powerful Energy Field layer could be seen beside the bodies of these three people. It could ward off all the external elements on its own.

“Looks like Jeros managed this pretty well,” Said a little red-haired girl, smiling.

“We should just get rid of him silently and consider it done,” A white-haired man on the side said helplessly. “Who knows what he’ll dare do if we delay this any further? This fellow has already separated himself from control.”

“The Wraith Royalty has always been chaotic. They’d even slaughter their own family members. I’ve recently received news that the new Wraith Monarch has already killed her father, Tasean. She has also released a declaration now, and will officially challenge His Majesty next month,” pouted the little red-haired girl. “From my perspective, she has a death wish. There were always some maniacs in the Wraith Royalty who were deviants that would not rest until they forced themselves to the brink of death. I heard them say that this was the fastest process to unleash their own potential.”

“Let’s go,” Chinande said softly. He flew toward Planet Scarlet Snow straight away. Although it looked like he was moving slowly, he had actually leaped across a distance of more than ten thousand kilometers within a few moments. He turned into a scarlet meteor that descended from the sky quickly.

The imprints of the Scarlet Snow Sect itself made it impossible for the sealed Crossfire Web to be rendered at all. Instead, it was coordinated to separate on its own immediately.

Three meteors descended from the sky rapidly and shot in the direction of the Scarlet Snow Headquarters directly.

********************

The Distorted Seed was completely swallowed by the remaining Emissaries respectively.

These few people closed their eyes one after another while feeling the changes that were rapidly occurring inside their bodies now.

“This feeling…” The Two-faced Person shut all four of his eyes tightly and muttered to himself as if he was slightly uncertain of the effects that the Distorted Seed had displayed. “Looks like there are still aspects that I haven’t analyzed yet.”

The energy chills of the Distorted Seed were quickly admitted into him voluntarily. He then released the chills, allowing them to surge through his own Sublime Board freely.

The Sublime Board that lingered in the depths of his mind was completely pitch-black. It emitted hints of strange, unknown suctions that quickly sucked in all of the strength of the Distorted Seed’s chills.

A thin layer of ice armor began to gradually cover the surface of his body.

The Energy Force Fields of Level Nine Peak appeared involuntarily and began to progressively affect the magnetic field on the ground of the entire Planet Scarlet Snow. The ground shook and vibrated faintly.

Inside the banquet hall, Garen and the few remaining Level Nines moved out at the same time and began releasing their own Energy Fields along with the Two-faced People’s forces.

The earth regained its tranquility and calmed down naturally.

Hum…

Suddenly, a subtle vibrating noise echoed from the sky in the outside world.

“Huh? This is?” Garen raised his head slightly as though he felt an indescribably enormous aura that was oppressing him in his current location now. That aura had already surpassed a powerful domain; it could only be described as something profound. It resembled a fountainhead that was spouting spring water endlessly.

Countless violent Energy Fields gushed out of the fountainhead frantically and collided against the Scarlet Snow Headquarters forcefully.

“Who is this?!”

Yuko, who had recently entered Level Nine Peak, was still familiarizing herself with this strength when she felt these terrifying forces that were pressuring her mightily. It seemed as though it wanted to suppress the auras of all the powerhouses here into submission. Despite being an Emissary of the Alliance, she had never seen such a major scene before. Therefore, she could tell immediately that the person who had arrived was a Level Ten Perpetual Motioner Holy Lord!

“It’s a Holy Lord Level powerhouse!”

Her expression changed rapidly before she stood up suddenly and opened the roof to look toward the sky.

One after another, the few remaining Guardians became angry and stood up as well. The few Level Eight Emissaries, who were recently elevated to Level Nine, were also firmly suppressed by this oppressive aura.

Chapter 1122: Goodbye 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The roof opened itself slowly, revealing the blue sky above. In the sky, three silhouettes were floating quietly, looking down at the group of people below. Among the trio, one of them emitted an extremely, terrifyingly deep aura in an unrestrained manner. This aura resembled a bottomless black hole.

“Three Perpetual Motioners?!” The expression on Yuko’s face became extremely contorted suddenly.

Aside from her, the faces of the remaining Emissaries of the Alliance changed immediately in succession, as if they had encountered a great enemy.

Garen stood and looked up at Carthage who was floating in the sky.

Perhaps it was more accurate to call him Chinande now. He had not expected that Carthage would suddenly arrive now. Garen suppressed the worries in his heart with determination, before opening his mouth and speaking calmly with a slight sneering tone in his voice.

“It is true and extremely offensive, that I, Garen of the Scarlet Snow Sect, did not come out and greet the celebrated Light of Justice and Perpetual Motioner Holy Lord who came here personally.”

His current identity depicted him as Jeros, and he was no longer the previous Garen or Nonosiva. Traces of his remaining evil aura dissipated out suddenly.

“Nonosiva, you broke the rules of the sect,” Chinande was unusually detached; he was seemingly colder than before. His voice did not even seem to fluctuate.

Garen’s face stiffened slightly beneath the helmet. When he raised his head, his eyes behind the helmet coincidentally met Chinande’s white pupils. Both of them stared directly at each other without flinching.

Although his powers were unlike the other party’s, Garen did not harbor any intentions of cowering.

After inheriting the will of all the seniors and founders of the Scarlet Snow Sect, he was destined to become the strongest person in the world! If he was too afraid to even face the Level Ten Perpetual Motioner before him, what honor would he have left to face the other higher Regent Levels?

Boom!

A shapeless Spiritual Light rushed into the depths of Garen’s soul through his eyes violently. An immense pressure as heavy as a hammer collided against him, blinding his eyes instantly and making everything blurry.

However, he kept his eyes widened determinedly.

Aside from him, everyone else that was currently here was also violently shaken by this Spiritual Light. The air stiffened and solidified. Everyone resembled insects that were stuck in an amber when they were suppressed and imprisoned by the enormous and limitless forces of the Energy Field.

The difference between the Energy Fields was truly this brutal. If you were stronger than someone else and your Energy Field stifled them, your opponent would lose even the ability to make a move.

“This is the Scarlet Snow Sect. As the Sect Master here, my decrees are the laws!” Garen could not see clearly anymore. He had never expected that Chinande’s powers would actually be so terrifying. His Energy Field suppression could make Garen’s Level Ten self pant for air. However, his honor as a Secret Technician made it impossible for him to have any intentions of compromising or cowering.

Although he could not see, he used his greatest power to release a loud noise.

He was not merely representing himself in this place now. Instead, he was doing this for the numerous Scarlet Snow founders who had sacrificed numerous things for him! If these numerous Soul Seed sacrifices yielded to submission easily under the weight of someone else now, how could he become Scarlet Snow’s strongest individual? How could he walk on the path of becoming the highest peak of the Secret Technicians!

The sound waves echoed in the empty space and reverberated between Garen and Chinande before suddenly jolting awake the nine other people who were confined to the sides.

Boom!

The terrifyingly abundant pressure descended from the sky and gathered before pressing down on Garen’s body firmly.

The white robe that covered his entire body danced and fluttered frantically while his golden helmet remained as cold and as solid as before. It blocked off the gazes of anyone who wanted to peep through it.

The dark section that represented his face looked up at Chinande unwaveringly. However, traces of broken, porcelain-like cracks were gradually appearing throughout Garen’s entire body underneath the helmet.

“Jeros has apparently entered Level Ten. However, there’s still a range within Level Ten, Captain!” said the little red-haired girl softly when she opened her mouth. “Otherwise, you could simply get rid of these people here and end it. Hehe, the Federation of Energy Machinists can’t even fend for themselves now anyway.”

“I think that’s fine. It’s merely the annihilation of a single small-sized sect and a few supposed Emissaries. It won’t matter if we just kill them. Since the plan has almost come to light now, do we still need to conceal it like this?” On the side, the white-haired man lifted a few strands of his hair while voicing his agreement.

Chinande remained silent.

************************

The strong wind whistled, as more people from all four corners of the earth realized that something was amiss. Most of the members of the Scarlet Snow Sect walked out of their dwellings and looked at the three figures that were floating in the sky.

Alice and Aloran walked out of their own residences and looked up at the sky before traces of shock appeared on their faces suddenly.

“That’s… the Light of Justice?!” Alice grabbed her own long hair to prevent it from being blown and sent flying messily by the strong wind. “That face… really looks like Great Senior Brother Carthage…”

She noticed that Chinande’s hand was already grasping the hilt of the sword at his waist slowly.

An indescribable fear surged through her heart suddenly. Alice looked at Aloran who was flying far away; she noticed a similar look of frightened panic on her face.

The same look of horror was apparent on the faces of the crowd of people around them who had walked outside too.

This was not merely their own fear, it was the fear of the entire Planet Scarlet Snow!

“The Light of Justice… wants to destroy the entire Planet Scarlet Snow?!” An unbelievable and frightening thought escaped from the depths of Alice’s heart suddenly. She felt as if it was getting slightly harder for her throat to breathe.

The tremendous aura seemed as if it possessed an invisible magic. It was clearly surging in front of her. She felt as though she could almost not breathe any air at all.

“This is… the Planetary Imprisonment?!” An ability that she had only seen at the basic level appeared in Alice’s mind.

Aside from her, everyone else around her was also experiencing breathing difficulties. Moreover, some creatures that did not even need to breathe could also feel this indescribably suffocating feeling.

Everyone on the entire Planet Scarlet Snow now felt as if their breathing was being suppressed, while their bodies grew weaker.

Shrouds of lifeless air started spreading throughout this entire planet. Some feeble insects and small animals in the forest were the first to die from suffocation. They were quickly followed by the sea creatures and fish species that were slightly larger.

More than a million lives were dying every moment.

“Chinande!”

Other than Garen’s own aura, another Level Ten aura burst forth suddenly.

The four eyes of the Two-faced Person that were tightly closed all this while opened abruptly. With him at the center, a strange and cruel aura scattered in all four directions ferociously.

The floors turned gold wherever the aura traveled. While the Two-faced Person remained at the center, the entire area of a few thousand meters turned into a bright, golden sea instantly.

Countless blocks of bright golden pieces melted slowly and flowed there. The banquet hall turned golden silently before it similarly melted. Everyone here was floating in mid-air. They were enveloped and protected by this golden aura that was contending with Chinande in the air.

With the crowd at the center, all of the gold in their surroundings melted into liquid and began turning around everyone. It rotated, forming a gigantic golden spinning whirlpool.

When looking down at it from above, the floor of the entire courtroom had turned into an enormous golden whirlpool completely. It was unusually magnificent.

Both the male and female faces of the Two-faced Person laughed cruelly.

“Are you thinking of obliterating the Emissaries? Would you actually do such cruel things despite being both the dignified Emissary and Light of Justice? You wanted to slaughter the entire planet?!”

The spinning gold shook the power of the Planetary Imprisonment suddenly, causing it to disperse and relax.

Garen stood behind the Two-faced Person but remained silent. After the pressure was eliminated, he allowed the Two-faced Person and Chinande to challenge each other head-on.

Chinande’s hand which was grasping the hilt of the sword loosened slowly. His lifeless eyes glanced at the Two-faced Person below him quietly.

“Holy Child?”

“A Level Ten Holy Child… This is slightly troublesome now…” The two people behind Chinande were faintly surprised as well.

The Holy Child primarily referred to the descendants of the Sacred People’s bloodline. Most of them were directly related because only the second generation of the Sacred People could be known as a Holy Child. Powerhouses like these would generally surpass regular experts greatly. Once they entered Level Ten, their lineages would overlay, allowing them to become even scarier. Their combative strength did not have to be mentioned, while their survival rates were definitely first-class. There were innumerable types of Holy Lord Level escaping measures. They were extremely difficult to kill when this was coupled with their initial state of being Level Ten Perpetual Motioners.

Although the powers of the three people greatly surpassed their opponent now, it would still be slightly troublesome if he wanted to kill a Level Ten Holy Child… Even if his opponent escaped alone…

The Two-faced Person below, who had already absorbed the Distorted Seed, now understood the relationship between himself and Garen clearly. Although he was slightly unhappy, he finally stood in front of Garen and blocked him while the latter stayed behind.

Both of them confronted each other with one on top and the other below.

The wind blew and made some whooshing noises. The Planetary Confinement was already removed, allowing the entire space to return to its original state.

“Chinande! Are you trying to rebel?!” Yelled the Two-Faced Person with a completely strict expression on his face. “The Holy Lords can neither strike each other freely nor use abilities of planet-destroying levels simply. Don’t tell me that you’ve forgotten all these rules?!”

Chinande’s hand stopped moving suddenly.

No one had said anything after that. Everyone could see that Chinande was hesitating because the appearance of one Level Ten Holy Child was a variable that he had not anticipated.

However, only the Two-faced People knew that once he made a move, everyone else except themselves would die!

Hence, once Garen died, the powers of the Two-faced People would fall back to its initial state. They would be annihilated by Chinande and the rest then.

In other words, everyone here would perish when he struck!

Time moved slowly. Everyone’s gazes were focused on Chinande’s hand that was holding the hilt of the sword weakly.

He loosened his grip slightly and finally put it down.

Chinande’s face looked expressionless, as though he did not feel defeated with the decision he made at all.

“Let’s go,” He turned around and flew towards outer space.

As the right-hand man of the White King, it was not time for him to reveal his identity yet.

“Hmph, I’ll let all of you live a little longer!” The little red-haired girl twitched her lips disdainfully and left with him.

The white-haired man sighed regretfully and followed closely behind. The trio disappeared outside the atmospheric layer in the outer space quickly, as the terrifyingly oppressive aura weakened and dispersed gradually.

Every single trace of their forces disappeared cleanly once the trio had left completely.

Only then did the Two-faced Person lower his head weakly; an extremely exhausted appearance could be seen throughout his body. Yuko and the other Level Nines inhaled a large breath of air violently as if they were just pardoned. They did not need air at all but did this because it was the quickest way for them to relax.

Garen was still looking on in the direction where Chinande and the two others had flown away and fled.

“As expected of a first-rate powerhouse that was able to nearly annihilate all of the Energy Machinists single-handedly that year! Despite having the assistance of his subordinate members, Chinande’s powers are still a bottomless abyss.”

Just you wait, we would meet again.

A deviation had already appeared in the general trend of events. Chinande, who was originally not supposed to come back at this time, had actually returned now…

Chapter 1123: Plot 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Ever since the Scarlet Snow Sect forced Chinande and the rest to retreat, its reputation swiftly spread from neighboring star regions to further territories. The Scarlet Snow Sect went from an inconspicuous little sect to a Scarlet Snow Alliance major sect with Level Eight and Level Nine experts dominating the entirety of more than twenty neighboring solar systems, forming an enormous energy force that could not be overlooked.

Yet, Garen’s name was suppressed by the Two-faced Person.

As an Energy Machinist that was recently promoted to the new Holy Lord, the Two-faced Person received grand and massive congratulations the moment he returned. The experts of the three major organizations had prepared the grand ceremony in his honor. The expert elders of his sect had organized an enormous celebration.

Within this short time frame, at the same time the competition was announced, the Two-faced Person had completely solidified his new position in the sect. He managed to secure the reins of the likes of Bone Metal Sect, eliminating dissidents immediately and resolutely, as well as promoting those who accorded absolute conformity.

Garen, on the other hand, continued gathering the various materials sent by the guardians of all sects. He placed his focus on practicing the Tempered Body Technique.

The big number of various materials amassed had enhanced the Nine-Level Tempered Body Technique to Level Seven. The final two materials required a high level of physical fitness. These sorts of materials were difficult to find, he could only play the waiting game. However, his vitality heightened by 28 points, bring his total vitality at 78 points. Garen wasn’t sure himself how much stronger he had become, as there was nothing around for him to test the limit. The strengthening of his body has reached to a terrifying stage where there seemed to be some sort of unique change after his vitality surpassed the 70 points mark, although it was increased by using the Tempered Body Technique to cover foreign objects.

The movement of the Scarlet Snow Alliance seemed to have triggered friction between sects. Seeing that the Federation of Energy Machinists was unable to attend, a few of the medium and small sized sects began to jostle at one another.

For a moment, there was a foul atmosphere surrounding the entire alliance. The Federation of Energy Machinists showed no signs of dabbing in.

Under such peculiar circumstances, the competition of the Energy Machinists, highly anticipated by the entire world, had finally begun.

*****

The City of Nagadako

On the surface of the entirely-red planet, white and blue fireworks were blasted all around. The fireworks oscillated in ripples of waves, blossoming a few layers of charm.

Around Planet Naga was the unparalleled dark space storm of the Negative Space. Eight silvery-white metal pipelines peeked through the storm, pointing towards Planet Naga.

The crowds in various outfits surged through each of the silvery-white pipelines. These groups of people were attended to by passing ships, headed towards Planet Naga,

“It is currently an uncommon phase, please forgive us as Planet Naga is going through a large-scale system upgrade. Hence, the surrounding space passageways are used as leaping points, instead of directly leaping onto the soil of Planet Naga. Please bear with us for any inconvenience caused.”

A man in red, emitting a bright red glow, was suspended in the air, attracting the attention of many. His clear, crispy voice was transmitted in all of the gateways so that everyone could obtain the message.

“To all guests and participants, please do not leave the regulated navigation range, or we shall not bear the consequences for any casualties caused.”

The man dressed in red calmly called out.

“It’s only a competition, what’s the need for there to be a nervous wreck?” A group of women dressed in white walked out of one of the pipelines. One of the women exclaimed in disdain. “We are forces at the Imperial Star level! Even if we were to go off course, what can he do about it?”

“Why don’t you try it then,” Another woman, who appeared to be the lead, dully remarked.

“I shall then!”

The earlier woman immediately saw red and flicked her finger.

With a swoosh, a dot of white light shot above the sun. The white light flew higher and higher. From afar, it resembled a white mechanic bird.

The white bird flew out of the tunnel’s safety range, yet it did not experience any abnormality.

“Return, White Phoenix,” The woman glared at the other woman provokingly. She extended her arm to catch the landing white bird.

Boom!

And it was at this time that the mechanic white bird exploded, burning all mechanical parts to complete oblivion.

“Let’s go. Stop causing a scene,” The leading woman commented, taking the rest out of the pipeline and heading toward the incoming spaceship. Only the woman who released the white bird was left sulking.

“Solomon of the Star Cloud!” She viciously glared at the man in red hanging high in the sky, “Humph!” She seemed to have placed the blame on him.

“Welcome, all representatives of Imperial Star region leaders,” A polite smile was flashed on the robotic face of the man in red suspended in midair.

The eight pipelines immediately radiated three bursts of white light soaring upward. Each white light shrouded the entering teams. These were the representatives of the nine Imperial Star level forces of the Human Alliances. Each Imperial Star was one Regent Level. They were nine of the human race’s strongest existences and the nine biggest forces against the Finite people. They each governed vast territories and were situated quite a distance away from the Energy Machinists’ star region. To have arranged a representative to come over, it was a display of an attitude. An attitude of respect.

Swoosh!

In one of the passageways, one team was holding flower baskets. A beautiful team dressed in fluttering white flew out with grace. This team was made entirely of males. Their bodies were lean and tall, strutting a shoulder-length long hair and having lush-red, vertical scars between their brows. They were fashioned with celestial-resembling outfits from ancient mythology, yet it was obvious they were men, yielding a peculiar vibe.

Still, it was their team ability that stood out. The most inferior of them was at the very least at a Non-falling Level. They were impenetrably strong. They were like a deep abyss, carrying an obscure aura.

“Welcome all from the Horn Scale Sect,” Solomon in the sky hosted the welcome. They were also an Imperial Star level force.

“The pleasure’s mine, junior Solomon,” A man who headed the team, with skin as white as jade and a face more delicate than a woman’s, gently answered. His pair of slanting eyes glistened with a light silver glow, giving out a sense of radiance and mysteriousness.

“This time, it’s Senior Noddy personally leading the team. Please move to the spaceship,” Solomon responded with a tone of respect.

The gentleman nodded and brought his team of juniors at a seemingly slow but realistically swift pace to the receiving entrance of the spaceship.

Their group attracted the attention of surrounding people, but the majority of them were locked on their appearance. These men had feminine looks. If one took no notice of their Adam’s apple and chest, then their gender wouldn’t be identified. instead, they would give a sense of androgyny.

“A bunch of queer shemales!” Out came two men in large builds exiting another passage afar. One of them spat and scraped the ground with his boot in disdain.

“The Horn Scale Sect has always been so. They transform to fight faster than anyone, get used to it,” The other man was wearing sunglasses. His light bulb of a head was a socket with a few blue aerials plugged in. He seemed to have failed in his body alteration.

“The nine major forces seems to have reached at the same time. We are all well-coordinated.”

“We just don’t see eye to eye, tsk!”

The duo swiftly walked toward a spaceship that came individually to pick them up.

Right behind them were a few individuals. Another group of people glistened in the white light and walked out of the passageway.

In the lead was a person in a white robe and golden helmet. Following closely behind him were the disciples in white. There was over ten of them, with a mixture of men and women, young and old.

“They’re from the Scarlet Snow Alliance, huh?” The moment this group of people appeared, chatters could be heard from the crowd from the front and back.

“Experts who dare challenge the alliance rules head-on!”

“Let’s see how the alliance is going to handle this!”

The small sect at the front instantly stood with wariness. Under the guidance of an elder, they stepped aside to give way, letting the people from the Scarlet Snow to leave first.

Garen lifted his head to watch the pitch-dark space. There was a red light straight far ahead. That was the shimmer released by Solomon of the Star Cloud to welcome all incoming guests. This layer of light was enough to protect all who were directly exposed to the space environment, and it forged a protective screen to isolate the invasion of the low temperatures and vacuums.

“So this is Planet Naga? How beautiful…” In the team, the white-haired Hong Guo and White Night were filled with curiosity. They had never seen Planet Naga in its whole. No matter how mature they were, they were still at a young age; seeing such a magnificent view naturally stumped them.

Apart from them, another who had yet to witness its beauty was Prism Light.

Prism Light was a mysterious person. He was not old, but he was one who was difficult to read. He was listed as the fifteenth among the Three Hearted. Garen sensed that he had huge potential, so he brought him along to broaden his horizon. In order to expand the Scarlet Snow Sect to glory, it was eminent to nurture the younger generations.

And Hong Guo, White Night and Prism Light were the geniuses selected by the Scarlet Snow Sect.

The rest that came with were, firstly, Alice that ranked first in the Three Hearted, followed by the three Ice Demon Generals, Ice-Ocean, Ice-Grand, and Ice-Crack, and finally Mandi, the expert in creating machinery imprints. The remainders were purely regular disciples in charge of daily trivialities.

“The Planet could be accessed directly through the leaping point at the volcano before this. Now, it seems we’re caught in a tense situation.”

Garen lowered his voice.

“Let’s go.”

Those from the Scarlet Snow Sect quickly entered the incoming spaceship. Once they entered, the spaceship displayed the names of all various sects within, and the name of the Scarlet Snow Sect was displayed in most prominence.

However, compared to the major sects at an Imperial Star level force that occupied an entire ship at the front, the Scarlet Snow Sect wasn’t that appealing. No matter how ravaging they were, it was not a region of an Energy Machinist. His reputation wasn’t at the stage of threatening other major forces.

Chapter 1124: Plot 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen and the rest sat in the rest area arranged. They were separated from the surrounding medium and small-sized sect. There were people specifically assigned to serve various beverages and fruits.

Although any discussion about him was unheard of, he could tell from the glances he received from these sect personages from time to time that they were quietly transmitting, communicating on the Scarlet Snow Alliance matter.

The Scarlet Snow Sect was considered a fierce major sect within in spaceship after all.

To develop at such a pace within a short time frame with the sudden emergence of bountiful experts had many spies prying intel. A rumor about the Scarlet Snow Sect obtaining some sort of treasure to raise its capabilities was also leaked from their internal affairs.

It was also unavoidable for Garen and the rest and despite his efforts to seal the news, this intel still made its way out.

Sensing the hidden sizing stare from around, Garen and his group minded their own business. They kept to reading and drinking while most of them rested with their eyes closed.

Hong Guo, White Night and Prism Light could not keep to themselves. They got up to engage with other sects.

Alice saw an old friend and went forth to have a conversation.

Truth be told, Garen was clear that the Scarlet Snow Alliance already has the resources and capability of a major sect. It was not completely exposed under the sun so everyone thought that there were only the Level 8 experts trios, Ice-Grand, Ice-Crack and Ice-Ocean as the face of the sect. Although their influences had risen, it was not too massive.

This time, they were counting on bagging one that lacked in skill. For one thing, it was to push the Scarlet Snow Sect to a new edge; and another, it was to get to the bottom of the scheme and plot for the Energy Machinist in order to finally snatch the Energy Machinist’s best masterpiece — the Combo and that would be ideal.

The Combo was having all Energy Machinists of the three major Energy Machinist metropolis to combine their energies. Each of them would scatter a bit of their free energy and focus them together to pour onto the champion of the competition.

The competition wasn’t between the experts within the sect but rather between disciples so this step could potentially shrink the discrepancy of cultivation length between talents and genius disciples from various sects.

It was the fastest accumulation to enter Level 8.

As normally the highest level would be the Non-Failing Level in competitions, there was not once a participating disciple that reached Level 8. The Non-Failing Level was the top in the completion, any higher would require a few hundred or thousand years of accumulation and ability to grasp.

It wasn’t just anyone that could achieve the Realm of Board after all.

The spaceship quickly entered Planet Naga and halted at a vast expanse grassland. A white snowy mountain could be seen afar from the nearby grassland.

The spaceship projected a light beam, transporting groups wave by wave.

There were assigned anti-gravity vehicles beneath operating transportation.

Once Garen and the rest gotten down, the first thing that caught their eye was the gorgeous golden anti-gravity vehicle.

Opening the door, a few young men dressed in gold were waiting in the automobile.

“The Sect Master has ordered me to welcome our fellow Scarlet Snow Alliance. Please!” A young lady smiled and said, carrying a tone of respect.

“The pleasure’s mine,” Garen knew that she was an expert from the Bone Metal Sect sent by the two-faced person. As one of the fifteen major sects, the Bone Metal Sect built a solid base. They have six Level 9 experts, over ten Level 8 experts but none on Level 10. Once the two-faced person marked his return and upgraded to Level 10, it gave a surge of confidence to the sect. The Bone Metal Sect finally met the requisite to battle a seat at Holy Lord level of force. They possessed hope to become the fourth Great Holy Lord level sect.

The disciples would naturally attach great importance to the orders of the current new sect master in hopes of leaving a good impression to the friends of the sect master.

Moreover, rumor has it that it was the treasure of the Scarlet Snow Alliance that aided the two-faced person to increase a level. If this were the case, then this Scarlet Snow Alliance really had quite a banking value!

Thinking about this, the disciples in charge of the reception revered in deeper respect.

The group sat in the vehicle and the door slowly shut tight under the envious glances of surrounding Energy Machinists and Mech Pilots.

The vehicle sent by the Bone Metal Sect, resembling a large frisbee, fired towards the faraway plain.

“We will be depending on you in this competition,” Garen sat in the vehicle and in front of him were the three genius sent by the Snow Scarlet.

Hong Guo, White Night and Prism Light.

These three met with the participating conditions that were no more than a hundred fifty years of joining the sect. Hong Guo somehow or rather inherited a teacher ancestor’s soul and energy, erupting his potential that could match with an Inherited Level expert. White Night has a solid Gideon Body. Although he wasn’t as good as Hong Guo, he excelled at the speed of light and presently resonated the Full-Moon Level.

As for Prism Light, Garen could not see through this little fellow. He could only sense that there was another powerful soul hidden within him. Moreover, he carried a peculiar constitution. Garen brought him to participate in this competition in order to size him up.

Although he was already at Level 10, it was not the pure Level 10 of this world after all. He couldn’t transform into a black hole nor could he link to the inverse space for relentless endurance. It was pure explosive force for him to reach the Level 10. He had the power of destruction but not the endurance.

No matter how terrifying the engulfing ability of his Hellfrost Peacock technique was, he could not beat the endless endurance of those Level Ten Perpetual Motioners. Garen knew that his advantage was to operate in the dark.

Utilising the distorted seeds to create more Level Ten Holy Lords to manipulate and reel into the alliance was the crucial key to expand influence.

Although there were only three Level Ten Holy Lords among the Energy Machinists, the number of Level 9 experts were not in the red. Those in the open and in the dark would have at least fifty in number. If he could just place a parasite in this bunch of people…

“Please do not worry, Sect Master. I will put forth my best effort to advance and gain a good name for our sect!” White Night responded solemnly with a hint of indifference.

“We will do our utmost. Please do not worry, Sect Master,” the same words from Prism Light’s mouth came out less solemn and leaned towards listlessness in comparison.

“Come what may. If I could I would. If I couldn’t then there’s nothing I can do,” Hong Guo was honest and always at ease. He hasn’t been that attached to the Scarlet Snow Sect before due to matters concerning Rainy. It was only when he started gaining attention of many and received major changes from upgrading that he forged ties to stay and joined the Scarlet Snow. He came because he thought well of Garen. Little One and Little Two who were taking care of his sister were people of Garen yet he allowed the duo to remain by him.

He had thought of Little One and Little Two as family from the days spent together. And for this, he would too put his best efforts to place in the competition for the Scarlet Snow Sect.

So although he was most light-hearted amongst the trio, his determination was the highest.

Moreover, in the inherited soul, it bore a recognition towards the Scarlet Snow Sect so if he were to compete, he would definitely put in his all.

“It’s a shame. My position has decided that I will not be participating the competition but staying on the sidelines. I really wanted to take part myself,” Garen sighed with remorse.

“For you to get up on stage, wouldn’t that leave other sects no chance of survival?” Osho Ice-Ocean shook his head and joked for the very first time.

“If Sect Master were to participate then it would be bullying the little ones. There really isn’t much to watch and everyone can just announce who is the winner,” Ice-Grand snickered.

“So this time the hope of our Scarlet Snow is on you three,” Garen returned to seriousness. “You may be up against Non-Failing Levels and once you do, immediately surrender and do not attempt to delay.”

“Understood,” White Night responded to heart. The remaining two nodded as well.

Garen took out three items. It was the shape of three little ice cubes.

“This is a little something I coughed up. It could erect an absolute ice wall at critical times, blocking off any fatal strikes. Do not use it unless it is critical. It exerted great effort to create this thing and it is for single use,” production tools materials to sustain such powerful energy were rare. The extent of its rarity would see major sects having only one or two of these. Moreover, it deemed useless after a single use.

It is destined that participants would not be winning the competition solely on high impact tools made by the powerful.

Garen did not hand over his distorted seed to the trio. The use of the distorted seed was better on a more solid foundation. If he were to offer them use, the most they would upgrade to would be the Inherited Level, which meant nothing to the Scarlet Snow Sect.

Once the trio received the item, Garen started to whisper important details to them. Having the advantage of memory, he could describe the points for attention exhaustively.

The vehicle reached its destination in a jiffy. It was a grand hotel in the City of Nagadako.

There was already a group of people staying there as vehicles were parked outside.

The group from the Scarlet Snow Sect exited the vehicle and entered the hotel. They swiftly settled in.

Garen returned to his individual room and opened up the Energy Machine Imprint, beginning his communication with the remaining alliance guardians.

Going through over a decade of repeated encryption, a communication channel was quickly established.

The miniature projection of over twenty people reflected in Garen’s retina, each of them occupying a tiny section.

“Alliance Leader, have you arrived?” One of the five Level 9 guardians asked.

“Uh huh, which of you have arrived as I am now at the Waysooner Hotel in the city of Nagadako,” answered Garen.

“Following the plan, we have already invited our fellow friends to join and organize a meetup. It’s starting to take shape at the other side,” a mummy of the three Level 9 Peak lowered his voice.

“I have received an invitation from a Level 9 Peak expert here and asking about the treasure. I am leading him on,” another female Level 9 Peak smiled.

“Be careful not to let anyone spot a flaw,” the last was also a Level 9 Peak. He was a white-maned wizened old man. There were layers and layers of wrinkles on his skin that looked terrifying as though his entire skin sagged, separating completely from its muscle.

“Relax, do you still need to remember this little detail after having lived for a few thousand years?” The woman casually remarked.

“Dare you not call for me an emergency call? Alliance Leader, are you being a stranger?” A sharp voice suddenly cut in the conversation. The projection of the two-faced person abruptly pushed away the vast projections of Level 8 Guardians, occupying a large section.

“I have received the invitation of three Great Holy Lords. Hehe, and another nine formal apprenticeship correspondence. These are all from various sect expert elders at Level 9 Peak.”

“All nine of them!?” Garen’s face laid hidden under the helmet with his expression not in sight but a sense of anxiousness from his tone revealed his current mood.

“Of course. I plan to discuss the price with them,” the two-faced person pulled a scratchy laugh. “This treasure comes with responsibility. It can’t be taken without any sacrifice. Anyone would be worried for anything to go wrong so a sufficiently heavy price is key!”

“That’s true,” Garen nodded. “Transport the resources directly to the Scarlet Snow headquarters. I’m not sure if you could contact the other Holy Children, it’s best if they’re Level 9 Peaks.”

“Holy Children… Doable,” The two-faced person was hesitant but nodded. “But for me to proactively head up would be suspicious. I will make my own arrangements so you need not ask more.”

Although he hosted the distorted seed, his mind and body were not affected. Even though there was an increase in his energy, the distorted seed could not completely manipulate the host but could link the energy increase with the parent body, nothing more. So it wouldn’t be wrong to say that it was a harmless alternation.

Although the host would automatically protect the parent body, it could not entirely be enslaved. Losing independence or even disobeying the instructions of the parent body was likely as long as it did not involve hurting the parent body.

Chapter 1125: Start of Competition 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

No sooner had he finished his sentence, the two-faced person immediately vanished with a slight disrespect. It seemed that even with the obligation to protect Garen and stick with him because of the distorted seed, as a Level 10 expert, he was unwilling to fall on his knees for him.

Once the projection disappeared, it struck an unhappy chord among a number of Level 9 Peaks.

“How outrageous,” a woman couldn’t hold her tongue.

“So he thinks he can just take flight, huh?” The wrinkled man chuckled in a low tone.

“Fine, let’s not bother about him and just handle our matters. Be careful not to leak the plan and do not rush to give out items,” Garen reminded.

“Understood.”

“Relax.”

They all responded. The projections immediately disappeared.

Garen sat alone in the room and started to carefully inspect the arrangement for possible loopholes. Should the plan succeed, the possible outcome could be fairly horrifying.

Holy Lord Level experts, especially Holy Lords of Energy Machinist has emerged in large quantities. This definitely would create an irreversible impact on Chinande’s plan. The more it was so, the more he as the parent body needed to hide in depth or if Chinande were to find that he was the source of all, he would reel in the highest animosity.

“It’s really… hard to execute…” Garen sighed and closed his eyes, focusing himself into a quiet meditation.

******

The competition went on as scheduled. There were a total of three completion arenas.

Representatives of various sects received the qualification notifications from the alliance. Osho Ice-Ocean was solely in charge of everything for the Scarlet Snow Sect and there was one who specially took care of any problem for the Scarlet Snow Alliance.

Garen directly received a VIP seat sent by the alliance in his room.

The sect master, as well as deputy sect master of a few major and medium-sized sects that paid him a visit similarly received the credentials of VIP seatings.

Talking and laughing with these bunch of people, Garen blended in within the high position crowd of medium and large-sized sects. They headed to the third competing arena together.

While on the way, he kept an observant eye. Although it wasn’t the break of dawn yet and it was still early, there were many that crowded the entrance of the competing arena. Many of them were still making way towards the entrance.

It was only discussions pertaining to the completion were heard while on the way. The entire city of Nagadako had transformed into a farmer’s market. If he didn’t transmit voice with his Willpower, he wouldn’t be able to make clear of the conversations.

Spaceships after spaceships came and went, transporting incoming representatives of major sects.

Garen and his group of higher level sect masters were also arranged transportation by spaceship in which they flew past the main gate and landed in a parking ground within.

Walking out of the spaceship, Garen could sense a furtive scent close by. If he didn’t keep a little of Jeros’ scent from before as well as absorbing the energy essence of the blood bead, he wouldn’t be able to sense this minute difference.

“They must know that I broke away from control and will strike during the competition,” Garen came to a realization while carefully detecting any possible suspects around.

The third competing arena was huge. The completion was on an elimination basis. It was between two competitors and the one that succeeded would move on. The winner would advance while the losers would compete again for the following winner to move on. This elimination process would continue on until a ranking was confirmed.

It sounded simple enough but the rules were complicated as the losers would continuously be determined and between the losers there would be winners. This way, it would be defined with precision. There would also be voting by the committees and referees involved.

Garen couldn’t care less about this rule. He was now at the twelfth section of the third competing arena. All around him were medium-sized and small-sized sects. Although the Scarlet Snow Sect had only recently made waves, they only showcased a sect of Level 8 experts so they were marked as small-sized. Being assigned to this competing arena was not out of the norm.

Garen swept his glance past all participating sects and found there was none worth the attention.

There was only one that was at Two-Moons Level with difficulty. He could be considered as a tough competitor.

He was sat in the middle of the VIP seats’ row. On his left was a female sect master of a small-sized sect while on his right was an elder of a medium-sized sect.

“I heard the Scarlet Snow Sect is recently expanding rapidly…” This elder from the medium-sized sect narrowed his eyes in laughter while twisting his mustache.

Garen was dressed in a white robe and wearing a golden helmet. It was uncertain what expression he carried as he showed no response.

“Your representative of the Aerial Upright Sand Sect doesn’t look too good,” a female sect master of a small-sized sect on the left remarked. She had earlier argued with this elder.

“Seeing the Scarlet Snow Sect Master like this, you must be confident in your disciples or else you wouldn’t be firmly sitting here without a finch. See, there are elders from certain sects who personally came down to boost their disciples’ morale,” this elder continued without any sign of rage.

“What is Elder Gong Neng trying to say?” Garen duly replied.

“Nothing, nothing of concern,” this elder continue to avoid eye contact and looked below at the two representatives preparing to take the stage.

Garen maintained his composure. He knew that Chinande’s original plan was to bring home the title and then when the three Great Holy Lords poured energy into the champion as an award, he would launch a revolt and trigger a string of explosion with the property of the combo to severely wound the three Holy Lords so being the champion was imminent.

The Energy Machinists’ higher positions must have predicted so regardless of the party, no one was going to let this competition go on with sportsmanship. There would certainly be some dirty tricks involved, and he as the troublemaker would possibly be eliminated at an early stage to prevent any variable.

He took one glance at the crowd and instantly discovered the peculiar scent that presented earlier.

Sitting in the grandstands were two figures in black capes within the shadows of the crowd. Many amongst the Energy Machinists that were unwilling to reveal their identities would drape all kinds of camouflage and black capes were a common choice. These two didn’t draw attention. If it weren’t for Garen’s detailed search, he probably wouldn’t trace them in the crowd.

After internally keeping a close watch on the two, Garen averted his attention to the two participants up on stage. In this competing section, only two representatives from the medium-sized sect that could barely match up with the trio of Scarlet Snow Sect.

And now one of them was on stage.

“Throne Sect versus New Aurora. Participants, please be ready,” a sweet female electronic voice was heard.

Two youngsters quietly took a stand on stage.

With a buzz, it began.

The two released their Energy Machinery at almost the same time. A black bear up against a green fox.

Strangely, the fox was larger than the black bear by a tad, doubling the height of its opponent. It looked like a huge monster, a giant fox.

Upon releasing their Energy Machinery, the two individually stood apart. It was obvious they were testing the waters of the another.

Up to a certain standard, the Energy Machinery would be able to sense the Willpower, degree of purity and endurance of their opponents.

Both of them had a go and with the testing completed, they abandoned the preparation works and welled up their Willpower to charge at their opponent for close combat.

One of them even opted for close combat with firearms as at times there were highly destructive laser beams discharged, impacting the protective barrier and causing ripples.

“Both of them are at the New-Moon Level. So they’re just some representative from unknown little sects,” The old man beside Garen whispered. Among those sitting here, Garen from the Scarlet Snow Sect was the only one he couldn’t read so he made attempts to probe Garen the whole time.

“The two of them aren’t that bad. They seem to be the kind that doesn’t spend all day cultivating in the sect,” the female sect master on the other side lowered her voice.

Garen gave a slight nod in agreement.

The competition continued on with a minute end result. Instead of triumphant between the Energy Machineries, it was a slight miscalculation from the female Energy Machinist that caused her the competition and her dreaded exit, earning New Aurora the win.

The second round started immediately. The winners’ winning counts decided the upcoming ranking distributions. This was a way to test their ability to reserve endurance in battle.

The contender of the second round appeared to be a disciple without any battle experience. He was nervous and despite his senior’s efforts to cheer him on on the outside, with one look, he didn’t react from being swept away by the tail of his opponent’s giant fox. He knocked onto the protective barrier and lost consciousness. He must have been mollycoddled in an overprotective environment.

Then it was the third, the fourth, the fifth. There was quite a bit of Energy Machinists without real battle experience. There were even those with high Willpower at Two-Moons Level but no one was spared from being taken down in a jiffy.

This sort of academic group of Energy Machinists researching theories was not a small sum. They made a large population in competitions annually.

Everyone was not surprised and many were already yawning.

Those up on stage at this time were only testing the waters. The actual strong representative of the sect hadn’t made their way up yet so it was the crucial moment when it came to rankings.

Normally, sects would place their strongest disciple at the back of the line. As long as one person out of three disciples was able to snag a higher ranking, the rest didn’t matter as the names were arranged by rankings.

It wasn’t long with a match after another, it was the turn of Scarlet Snow Sect’s White Night.

Garen had regained some of his spirits.

The opponent of White Night had already been through over ten rounds. Hence, her sect replaced her with another person.

White Night first bowed towards the direction of Garen and then proceeded to size up his opponent.

“One move! It’s all I’ll take you down with,” White Night gently raised his arm and did a slicing motion complete with a face of disdain.

His opponent was obviously enraged.

“Anyone knows how to talk big!” Even so, facing the representative of one of the three strongest sects in this competing arena, he brought his serious face. He slightly bowed and released an equally black giant fox in front of him.

The moment the fox was released, he felt a surge of cold air around. White Night who was earlier standing before him had vanished and the warning device he wore on him blared a sharp alarming sound.

Left!!

He immediately turned and saw a white shadow glided by.

“Snowstorm Palm!”

With the rupture of vast white snowflakes, White Night marked his palm on his opponent’s chest. Massive freezing palm force surged into his body, recklessly destroying all vessels and nerves in it.

Chapter 1126: Start of Competition 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Snowstorm Palm that could be used for far range attack was altered by him for close combat. Garen came across this palm technique due to its incomparable speed that couldn’t be dodged. Now White Night has indistinctly blended his technique into this palm technique, allowing the palm technique to guide his body to lightning bolt speed.

The Snowstorm Palm was one of the three consummate skill of the Scarlet Snow Sect. Having it displayed by White Night, the extent of its impact has reached its highest potential.

Far range attacks would have its energy loss after all while close range battles would burst out the strongest explosive force.

White Night played it out at a Full-Moon Level, at the opponent’s unguarded chest.

The outcome was determined.

Wham!!

That person lifted his head and spewed out fresh blood. His blood hung in the air frozen, landing crushed red ice chunks on the ground.

Stumbling a few steps back, this person went down unwilling with his head thrown back. His breathing stopped temporarily. He went through shock with one palm.

The people from New Aurora immediately opened up the entrance of the protective barrier to get on stage and removed him.

“Will the battle continue?” The referee asked.

The elder from the New Aurora tensed his face and decisively shook his head.

“No.”

“Scarlet Snow Sect wins! The next opponent, please get up on stage!” The referee immediately announced the victory.

This was a training tactic. If they were to continue the battle, wouldn’t that be giving a chance to those competitors that needed to head up on stage to exhaust White Night’s energy? Wouldn’t that give way to other sects? So the best strategy now was to wait.

White Night gave a contemptuous smile and turned to return to the area he occupied earlier. He nodded the direction of Garen with respect.

Garen nodded in response.

“He didn’t even release his Energy Machinery… Tsk tsk, what an amazing real experience fighting ability!” The elder beside Garen could be throwing sarcasm or praise.

“No one will think you’re a mute if you don’t speak,” the female sect master coldly blurted.

“I’m just afraid that someone thinks I’m mute,” the elder smiled with narrow eyes without throwing a temper. “This competition is for one thing, ranking; and another thing, is to have potential disciples see the real world and have an exchange. This blow by the representative of Scarlet Snow really shows no mercy… To vanquish that palm without the skill of a Non-Failing Level would take no less than a few days, tsk tsk…”

“Thank you for your compliment,” Garen dully responded.

White Night ended the next few rounds with one palm. No one could fathom on how quick he pushed forth the palm. The Snowstorm Palm was an undefeatable feat. Those behind simply threw in the towel.

It wasn’t long until the first course of the competing section ended and the Scarlet Snow Sect ranked first. The first immediate winner to complete the competing section and advancing to winners’ major arena grouping.

“I will excuse myself now,” Garen got up and left the arena with the three representatives. The value of the major area was not here but at a separate location.

It wasn’t that all surprising on the easy win for the Scarlet Snow Sect.

An additional effect on the Scarlet Snow Technique would happen for White Night to possess the Gideon Body. Moreover, he had a solid real battle experience so an easy win wasn’t something to be taken aback by.

Garen was slightly worried by the lack of activity from the two men in black. They didn’t make a move to assault him so it was unsure if there was a shift in their plans for his bonus appearance.

******

Within a pitch black abyss in Planet Naga.

“And the seeds?” A clear crisp female voice was heard afar in the darkness.

“In the competition. The three seeds are in the three competing arenas respectively. It’ll be all good as long as we win,” another young boy’s voice was heard replying.

“Be careful of the Red Skeleton, White Lion, Black Jade Dragon and Hell King Blade. These four are the eight most powerful with White Lion lurking the deepest yet the most powerful. He would be the biggest threat to the seeds.”

“Handle them first before anything.”

“And the matter concerning Jeros?”

“Captain has observed their participants. They’re not up to the level of threat to the seeds. Heed no attention. He wouldn’t dare to pull a stunt in ruining our arrangement.”

******

Wham!!

Black Jade Dragon brutally smashed his opponent onto the ground, sinking him to the point his flesh and bone were meshed beyond recognition.

He flexed the muscles on his tough upper body.

“I said I’ll come face on! One punch! You can’t even hold one punch. Just go home and suckle your mother! What a waste of my time!” The then Black Jade Dragon Beast has grown into a tan-skinned wild man.

The elder of the opponent rushed to the stage to move the wounded disciple. No one dared to glare at him in rage. Black Jade Dragon represented one of the top constitutions of special talent.

Without a body type of the similar level, no one stood a chance to face him on chance.

“Next!” Black Jade Dragon roared in insolence and boredom.

This was the hundred and sixth opponent he struck down. No one would take more than three punches from him. Most of them collapsed in one hit. This had Black Jade Dragon who was out seeking opponents in utmost dissatisfaction.

Black Jade Dragon was wearing some golden accessories all over. The shadow of the once dedicate little boy could indistinctly be seen.

The following opponent held off going on stage that Black Jade Dragon grew impatient and dug his ear.

“I said, next! Are you deaf!?” He glared and shouted in front of him.

A pale young man who was just prepared to head upstage fell on his posterior from this fright and couldn’t get up.

“I… I surrender…”

“I am surrendering too!”

“Me too!!”

Those lined up behind immediately raised white flags.

The round at the competing arena ended in an instant. Black Jade Dragon was dumbfounded as he swept his glance around. The experts from other sects couldn’t help but avoid eye contact with him.

Those that surrendered wanted him to swiftly triumph so they could reserve their ability for a better ranking.

“Patooi!” Black Jade Dragon didn’t manage to vent, “Since Strength Kaiser and Mammoth, there really isn’t any competent opponents! How unfulfilling!”

He may as well have left the stage.

The first winner of the first competing arena was then determined.

******

The second competing arena.

“Paw of White Lion!”

A gentle male voice was heard.

With that, a rumbling acute tremble ensued.

In the competing grounds, a black hole appeared on top of a white-clothed man and within the black hole, a terrifying large limb of a lion over ten meters thick extended out and crushed the opponent to the ground. It was an explosion of fresh blood galore, splattering onto the ground. Residues of flesh, blood, bones and intestines scattered all around.

“White Lion wins!” A female referee’s voice was heard.

“White Lion!!” An elder of a major sect scowled viciously at the man on stage. The beloved disciple that he took pride in was instantly murdered by him! Such enmity!!

“You better pray you do not end up in my hands…” The cold yet heinous voice of this elder was heard.

White Lion didn’t take it to heart.

“Thank you for your advice,” he gently replied with manners.

“The last round is won by White Lion!”

Ensued with constant gruesome state of each of his opponents, the reputation on the cruelty of White Lion in the second competing arena spread out.

The reputation on the strength of Black Jade Dragon from the first competing arena circulated. That terrifying strength to immediately smash in one punch no matter the attacking Energy Machinery far exceeded the Inherited Level range but rather at the peak of the Non-Failing Level. Black Jade Dragon only revealed the tip of the iceberg of his brutal force.

******

The third competing arena.

Up on stage was a graceful young lady in red facing a blue-eyed man dressed in black with a black mask.

The two’s whip intertwined heavily as the red and black whips lashed edgy weal. Each weal scratched the surface, leaving a deep gully.

“Resonate Rumble!!”

The young lady in red raised her arm.

With a rumble, a blue lightning was released from her whip. Carrying forth a mount of quake, it leaped meters in distance and fronted the man in black in the face.

“Resonate Sand.”

The man in black’s other vacant arm disappeared and reappeared between the thunderous lightning and his face. He erected his pointer and lightly dabbed.

Swoosh!

His finger penetrated the thunderous lightning and burst open an overcast of yellow sand that wrapped everything within. The yellow sand held up for half a second before disappearing after engulfing the thunderous lightning.

“Little Red!” The young lady in red seemed to have predicted this turn of events and while her opponent was busy attending to this move, she shot a red thread at the speed of light.

The red thread limbered out in mid-air, quickly transforming into a red-jaded skeleton as tall as a person.

The red skeleton barged towards the opponent. Its sharp claws swishing with sounds of cutting winds. Its speed far surpassed the whip by multiple thresholds as it emerged before the opponent.

“Leap Sand,” the man turned to lash his whip as quick.

Bam!!

He managed to cast it on the incoming red skeleton.

The lash burst open a vast amount of yellow sand, interweaving to a few seconds of standstill with the red blazing light on the red skeleton before separating in a loud crash.

It was a tie!

The long holding battle was still on the run, the two were already catching their breaths.

******

On the other end, the Scarlet Snow Sect sang songs of triumphant, bagging more victories and fewer losses. It was soon when they entered the third competing arena’s final battleground. It was a zone near Red Skeleton and the man in black’s ongoing battle.

More than half the sects had been eliminated by now. In the winner’s grouping, only twelve sects remained with three from the medium-sized sect and the rest were large-sized.

The Scarlet Snow was a member of the three medium-sized sects. His current scale was naturally considered a medium-sized.

When Garen led the pack to enter, he caught glimpse of Accord sitting amongst the selected participants.

The formation of the Scarlet Snow Sect lured the attention of Accord. He motioned his sight over in search of Garen but quickly averted his eyes with slight disappointment.

Once here, he could not transmit his voice out at his disposal. This was the arena’s final battleground. It was equipped with absolute isolating barrier.

Garen too temporarily shut his communications channel.

He could tell that Accord covered up his appearance and scent. Although it could not be concealed from top experts, regular people would not be able to recognize his identity nor appearance. The name he introduced himself with was Dark Light and not Accord.

Chapter 1127: Versus 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Both of them arranged to meet at the arena. With each of them concealing their identities and not revealing their true self, Liz was unable to contact them both. This place isolated lower wavelength of voice transmission communication.

“Where’s Garen and Accord? Are they not coming to such a grand event?” Liz leaned her arm on Dios’ and entered into the arena with team Black Blade.

Her gaze secretly screened through the seats of participants in the arena, in hope to find her two best friends.

“This is the winners’ grouping. If you want to find your two friends, you should go to the competing section. This is the place for experts that are due to enter the final arena,” Dios burst into laughter as he shook his head as a reminder to Liz.

“This is the winners’ grouping? I didn’t know…” Liz stuck her tongue out in a sort of naughty yet cute way. Dios was fond of this characteristic of hers. Ditzy, beautiful, dolled up, pouty and cute. Don’t all men like their women to be pouty and act all cute?

“You are not at the same level as them. They would probably have a hard time entering here. Only the winning representatives and elders can enter,” Dios smiled. “I can only enter in light of my grandfather.”

“I see…” Liz nodded with comprehension.

“Watch the competition. It is a not-to-be-missed real battle experience that will be an eye-opener to actual combats.”

“Alright,” Liz nodded in obedience. She scanned the people around her and all of them were experts with obscure aura. Apparently she herself has unconsciously entered a new height.

“I gave them a chance but they did not value it.” She still felt down in the dumps. They were friends that originally came together. Wasn’t it normal to depend on the strong when one did not have the capabilities? It can be tiring to fight alone, and with an outcome that may not be successful, was it worth it? Couldn’t they be like her, find someone great to rely on and live a blissful life without a worry? She had intended to introduce two female Energy Machinists from a strong family background to Dark Light and Garen… but it’s a shame that they did not strive for it.

“Quick, look! The three representatives with the most consecutive wins are coming out!” Dios’ voice trembled with excitement, “Senior Brother Hell King Blade from my team Black Blade is there!”

Liz was instantly pulled back from her thoughts and looked towards the direction he was pointing at.

“The final winners’ grouping of the competing arena: Red Skeleton, Dark Light, Hell King Blade and Crimson Ice.”

The final verdict from the referee was out and based on the number of wins, the four strongest was tallied. These were the four strongest of the third competing arena.

Four people with different temperament stood up and were prepared to accept challenges thrown by others in the winners’ grouping.

Anyone who was with confidence could get up on stage to challenge them.

This was also providing the losers one last chance. Thereafter there would a battle between them.

At present time, there were still competitions that hadn’t ended in some competing arenas for winners to come out, so the four were also waiting for the rest of the winners to challenge them.

Liz’s eyes swept past Dark Light but she did not recognize him. That dark aura covered up many of his characteristics.

“We will begin the second event of our competition. The Challenge. All challengers please head up to the stage base on nickname,” the referee announced.

“It’s going to start…my senior brother Hell King Blade will surely win!” A senior sister by Dios spoke with confidence.

“That’s right. If Senior Brother were to use his full potential, then no one can stop him!” One of the Black Blade juniors exclaimed.

“The final champion belongs to senior!” Dios nodded in agreement. No one was clearer than them on how terrifying Senior Brother Hell King Blade could be.

The four stood on an independently stretched platform, waiting for challengers to come up.

It wasn’t long when one leaped up.

The moment he stepped up, this person was immediately lashed with Red Skeleton’s whip. His clothes were stripped to rags from top to bottom. Through the sounds of teasing and laughter, this Energy Machinist was dragged down by his sect elder in embarrassment.

“How embarrassing! Really,” Liz couldn’t help but laugh. “Sister Red Skeleton is really good! She was top three in our year of assessment and she’s still that powerful now.”

“Of course. Red Skeleton is a genius that with the right nurture, how can she not end up to be one of the top experts,” Dios nodded. “With the condition that she doesn’t die.”

Another one went up to challenge Hell King Blade.

Almost sliced into half at the waist by one strike of his blade, the challenger held his wound as he was rescued down the stage in helter-skelter.

“Gotta give it to Senior Brother! One strike and done,” Dios laughed saying.

“Who is more skilled between Sister Red Skeleton and Senior Brother Hell King Blade?” Liz asked in a seductive tone.

“Senior Brother, of course. Red Skeleton just entered Inherited Level while Senior Brother is already at the Non-Failing Level and is the strongest in our Black Blade’s youngest generation. But I heard that there’s something uniquely dangerous on Red Skeleton’s that needs to be handled with care. I don’t know if it’s just a rumor.”

******

One by one, challengers went up on stage. Hell King Blade, Red Skeleton, Crimson Ice and Dark Light knocked them all down the stage.

As the challenge continued non-stop, Red Skeleton began to show signs of exhaustion. Beating the expert with the sand earlier had consumed a large amount of her willpower and skill. Now with this back-to-back challenge and being the weakest of the four, her face started to pale.

Dark Light remained at ease without feeling strenuous. He whacked each of his opponents with his dark gas scorpion tail. Any resistance proved futile. The difference between him and his opponents was far too wide. If they were of the same level, the opponent could put up a struggle, but his willpower was now hidden within the dark gas and could have possibly reached a higher stage. As challengers were defeated at first blow, gradually there wasn’t anyone who was willing to get up on stage as they saw no hope.

As for Crimson Ice, it was an alias. Crimson Ice was actually Hong Guo of Scarlet Snow Sect. White Night and Prism Light did not enter the final battle of the strongest as they lost one round. Hence, only Hong Guo who went all out was still standing on the battlegrounds.

It was as how Garen had predicted. Although Hong Guo nonchalantly responded but when it came to it, he was the one who put in the most effort.

White Night was the type that would analyze the strength and weakness of his opponent and if he felt he could not defeat them, he would throw in the towel immediately, whilst Prism Light responded the same as completing a task. Except for Hong Guo.

This fella was the one who would go all out!

Garen was sitting below and upon seeing this, he was satisfied. This sort of talent was the real backbone that Scarlet Snow Sect needed! White Night was overly selfish and carried the burden of his family’s vengeance. Prism Light was overly mysterious and his real intention remained unknown. Only Hong Guo grew up proper. He was the grandson of Senior Sister Rainy and inherited Frost Hell’s soul seed secret technique. He felt indebted to the secret technique teacher ancestor and developed a sense of protectiveness to the Scarlet Snow Sect.

With the Inherited Levels heading up one by one, Hong Guo was starting to struggle.

Garen looked at the statistical data and the accumulation wins on the Scarlet Snow Sect was enough to enter the final competing grounds. It was only that he couldn’t be the strongest representative but that didn’t matter as it was good that they were not attracting too much attention.

Seeing Hong Guo struggling on stage with no intentions to back down and intertwining with an Inherited Level Energy Machinist of a large bird, Garen decisively transmitted his voice over.

“Enough, Hong Guo. You have done enough.”

Hong Guo who was on stage was flabbergasted. He looked beneath at Garen from the platform.

“No, I can continue!” He saw the proud smiling faces of the sisters Little One and Little Two in the audience, Uncle Ice Fox shouting at everyone around while thumping his chest, a few companions as well as Conan, this young lady who has been supporting him was looking at him.

“There’s so many that’s supporting me. To leave that early while I have not given my all, I am not fulfilled!!”

Hong Guo casted Garen’s voice transmission aside and continued to battle his opponent.

Garen who was below wanted to transmit his voice further but found that this little fella was ignoring him. He did not know whether to laugh or cry. Would a boss of a company complain about a diligent staff? Of course not.

So he let him be.

Alice and Osho Ice-Ocean that followed behind had a funny look on their faces. They had never met such a peculiar little fella. The remaining experts have moved on to another arena to prepare their duties. Only two of them were left here to compete.

“See that?” Garen’s deep voice transmitted to the ears of them both, “This is the elite of our Scarlet Snow. The hope of our sect. Although Senior Sister Rainy has left, she did not leave behind merely memories.”

Alice silently nodded.

“If all of our Scarlet Snow were as such, then we need not worry of the decline of our sect,” Osho Ice-Ocean sighed.

“Emphasize on protecting and nurturing him,” Garen dully gave the lowdown. Once the Energy Machinist’s crisis was over, Hong Guo receiving focus in nurturing was evident.

“Understood.”

Osho Ice-Ocean nodded.

Witnessing everything on the side, Alice suddenly wasn’t all that resistance towards Garen’s power usurp. No matter what, they were still part of Scarlet Snow and they were all fighting for the rise of it.

She still remembered the words said by Garen when he took office.

“When the sect is in dire peril, I, Garen, will strive for prosperity and usher in thousands of years of outstanding hegemony!”

******

Bang!

Hong Guo took down another opponent on stage.

All of them could tell that Hong Guo and Red Skeleton was at the end of the rope and focused on attacking them both.

Another opponent went up on stage.

Hong Guo’s line of vision was already starting to blur and his sweat drenched all over yet the coldness emitted from his body condensed it to ice.

“You’re losing it. Isn’t it better that I take your place on this stage?” His opponent was a treacherous looking woman with a hook nose. Holding double blades, she teased Hong Guo.

Hong Guo noticed the sect emblem of his opponent. It was the Melting Tool Sect, one of the fifteen major sects with a solid background. It was going to be another tough battle.

“You can try it out yourself to see if I’m losing it or not.” Hong Guo has always been intractable who responded only to reason and not force. He arched his back and gave a nonchalant attitude.

Swoosh…Clang!

Their two figures clashed into each other with sparks of snowflakes and flames counteracting and melting, sprinkling all over the platform.

Chapter 1128: Versus 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On the other hand, Red Skeleton finally gave in as she was hit off from the stage before passing out by a young man with a shamed look on his face.

“I’m sorry that I didn’t have a glorious victory.”

The man apologized to Red Skeleton’s elder respectfully.

“You have a sense of propriety during the fight and this is her limit by far. It’s fine.” The female elder shook her head as she carried Red Skeleton tenderly out of the place. Since both of them did not manage to win the battle, they were dropped out from the throne reserved for the best.

The remaining competition would then decide the best among the remaining three.

Dark Light looked as relaxed as ever. He finished off his opponents quickly, beating them off the stage and injuring them seriously. He was not afraid of anybody regardless of their strength and background as the Star Cloud was the local tyrant in this area. No one was a rival to them and the Sect Elders could only stare at him in anger and were not able to do anything even when his opponents were seriously injured.

Dark Light stood alone on the stage as his arrogance was off the chart.

“A bunch of trash! Are you guys that afraid of coming up on stage?” He stood above everyone as he looked down at the challengers, giving a disdained look at them.

Although all of the challengers were furious at his taunt, none of them dared to go up on stage and challenge him.

“Weaklings. How sad…” Dark Light showed no sign of hiding his contempt.

He then he looked to his side at the young man who had just won against Red Skeleton.

“Do you want to have a match?”

A sense of secrecy flashed across the young man’s eyes as he smiled gently and shook his head.

“I do not wish to embarrass myself.”

Dark Light scoffed as he sat cross-legged and rested quietly.

Then, a mysterious voice came from the young man’s body as it traveled to the audience sitting far away.

“I’ve dealt with the Red Skeleton. The next one shall be Black Jade Dragon.

“Understood.”

A black shadow figure then flashed over the audience’s seat.

*********

“What a boring battle.”

Hell King Blade struck once with his blade. After the black knife took a few changes in directions here and there, it then pierced into his opponent’s chest at lightning speed.

Stab!

Fresh blood was drawn. His opponent was unable to catch up to his speed as he could only see the blade flashed about in front of him and pierced into his chest.

“Next.”

The fatally injured challenger was carried down the stage. He who bore the title the Strongest Black Swordsman had made the challengers lost hope in fighting him. The tactic of fighting him by taking turns seemed to be ineffective as one person fighting him didn’t seem to tire him out at all.

“The challenger has forfeited.” The referee sounded.

The time to challenge had ended and the two who were still standing were Hell King Blade and Dark Light.

This was within everyone’s expectation as they were the representative of the two major sects, Black Blade and Star Cloud.

The highly ranked sects were indeed something else and the result was not out of the norm at all.

“The battle to determine the victory shall be Hell King Blade of the Black Blade against the Dark Light of Star Cloud.” The referee announced again. This would represent the wills of the Three Great Holy Lords and no one would be able to defy it. This was because the referee was a manifestation of the Three Great Holy Lord’s wills fused together.

Then, the two tall stages shifted to merge together.

Heh.

Dark Light opened his eyes and stood up. He adjusted his posture before walking towards the Hell Blade King.

With each step towards his opponent’s stage, black gas started to emerge from his body. It seemed like a fog of black gas was flowing towards the number one black swordsman, Hell King Blade.

“Hell King Blade… hehe. I’ve heard of this name for a long time…”

“Dark Light, the second strongest and youngest powerhouse of Star Cloud.” Hell Blade King’s expression was calm as an enchanting purple-black flower patterned line appeared on his forehead, giving off a cold yet enchanting vibe.

“Rumor has it that your Stellar Hand is very powerful. I wonder if it can break my Hell King’s Exhalation.”

“Won’t you test it to find out?” Dark Light clenched his fist as he grabbed hold of a viscous black gas which appeared out of nowhere. The black gas then turned into a puddle of sticky black glue. As the black glue dripped onto the stage, it corroded holes of various sizes on it.

It was the Stellar Hand, which was famed to be the number one Killing Move in terms of corrosion. Since Dark Light had decided to use his Killing Move at the start of the battle, it was obvious that he was taking this match very seriously.

Buzz!!

Two auras in the form of black gas emerged from their bodies at the same time as it rose up into the sky, piercing through the clouds.

In that instant, every audience stood up.

“Non-falling Level!! They’re both Non-falling Levels!!”

One man shouted.

A person who was just at the disciple level was already at the Non-falling Level. This high level was simply unimaginable!

The invigilators’ face from the VIP seats turned for the worse as a mere single division would elevate to such a level. One could only imagine what level of battle one could see after this! This competition…may exceed everyone’s expectations…

“Looks like we will have a good show…” A middle-aged woman beside Garen squinted her eyes as she reacted.

“Kill!!” Dark Light moved as the black gas around him gathered and formed into a giant black scorpion, which immediately pounced towards the opponent.

Kaboom!!

The Scorpion’s stinger stabbed into the flat surface, creating a one-meter wide crater.

A black shadow figure then shot out from the edge of the crater at lightning speed.

“One slash.”

Boom!!

A black light flashed as the inconspicuous trace of the blade moved across space and instantly reached the side of Dark Light. It then silently cut the Scorpion’s shell opened and pierced its innards.

“Wavering Light!!” Dark Light started twisting his body and rotating at high speed as if he had turned into a gyroscope. The scorpion’s stinger started to rotate quickly as well as they went towards the Hell King Blade’s attacks.

The entire battlefield was covered in black smokes and it was hard to see the event unfolding clearly. Two black clouds of smoke fused together and no one could identify who’s who. They could only vaguely determine that they were still fighting it out from the black smoke’s heated turbulence.

Suddenly, the black gas spread out, revealing the battle between the two men. The speed of them exchanging their blows were so quick that their hands and legs had turned into muddy shadows and one could only see the powerful shockwaves when their fists and legs came in contact.

The black gas had dispersed away by their purely condensed Non-falling Light.

“Extreme Slash!”

Out of the blue, Dark Light turned his body and released a crescent-shaped attack with his black blade, cutting everything in all directions.

“Raining Swallow!”

Hell King Blade countered it by pulling out a black sword to attack it head-on. The sword gave off a swallow-like cry as he mysteriously evaded the Dark Light’s incoming attack with a strange maneuver. The sword then directly appeared behind the attack and slashed towards him.

The black blade took a shift in its direction and bypassed Dark Light’s right hand which was trying to block it, piercing directly into Dark Light’s left shoulder.

Pew!!

Blood was drawn.

“Extreme Slash! Ten times!!”

As Dark Light experienced pain, he erupted as circles of black crescents appeared around his body. The crescent-shaped attack covered everywhere from top to bottom and left to right, turning him into a black sphere.

Kaboom!!

The black crescent covered the entire sky as it spread out in all direction.

In that instant, the entire stage was so black that nothing could be seen clearly.

“Eat my Dark Light Extreme Slash!!” He roared.

A blade which spanned tens of meters tall appeared from the chaos.

“Osprey. Hell King’s Exhalation!” Hell King Blade knew that it was not a good idea to take this attack head-on as his opponent released his full strength. He would suffer fatal injury if he were not careful with his approach. He took the conservative approach and gathered the Non-falling Light around his body and turned it into a light sword of a similar essence.

He then threw the slash in front of him!!

Roar! A tall muddle humanoid figure in a black armor vaguely appeared behind his body and it looked like the legendary mysterious Hell King!

Hell King gave off a deep roar as he pounced forward along with the light sword while releasing a half transparent black gas.

Boom!

The two light swords clashed but Hell King Blade surprisingly collapsed in that instant. He was stunned as he didn’t expect such strength from his opponent.

“This…” He suddenly felt something was wrong with the aura coming off from the opponent’s light sword.

“This is!?” His pupils widened but it was already too late.

The giant black sword slashed across his front body.

Slash!!!

This attack slashed across his body from his left shoulder to his right leg, opening up a large wound.

Blood immediately spurted out from the wound like a geyser!

The Hell King Blade’s Non-falling Light was weakened immediately.

He lost.

He lost in such a strange manner that no one could comprehend it!

The Light Sword carved a deep scar into the ground and it far surpassed the residue strength from the Non-falling Light.

“This is my strongest attack…it can absorb the opponent’s strength and increase my own attack. I called it the Dark Light’s Extreme Slash! Hell Blade King? Hehe. I would be slightly more worried if I’m fighting the Black Jade Dragon Beast.”

He then turned one round as he glanced at the crowd before he stared at the seat of the Scarlet Snow Sect.

“Garen! Come and fight me!” His voice reverberated, and the entire stage trembled.

With a slash, Dark Light pointed his sword at Garen who was sitting on the VIP seat. He pointed at the chairperson of the Scarlet Snow Sect!

The crowd went wild as no one would expect him to challenge the recently infamous leader of the Scarlet Snow Alliance!

Dark Light, who had just gotten out from a concise and tyrannical battle wished to challenge a powerhouse who was a Sect Master Level without any rest!? Has he gone crazy?!

The people from Black Sword Sect among the crowd were still in disbelief.

“Senior Brother Hell King Blade was defeated!!? How is that possible!” The group of junior brothers and sisters’ faces turned pale. The Hell King Blade was considered one of the strongest disciples among them. How could he lose without a clear explanation? It was entirely incomprehensible! How could the last strike give off such a phenomenon!?

“How could he lose!?” Dios’ face paled as he muttered to himself.

The person who was more shocked than him was not the rest but Liz, whose eyes were wide opened as she looked at the battlefield.

“Is that…Accord!!??” Liz’s eyes widened to the point where her eyelids seemed to be tingling in pain. “How is that possible? How is that possible!!?”

She kept looking at the man standing on the stage as she wanted to assure herself he was probably somebody similar. However, based on his attitude and even the minor characteristics, this so-called Dark Light was without a doubt Accord!

“Isn’t Accord a normal disciple in Star Cloud? How could this be?” She tried to recall the time when Accord and Garen separated and the vague sensation of disdain in his gaze. ‘One will never improve if he keeps relying on someone else. You better learn to be independent.’

This was his final word towards himself before he left.

Dios, too, had already recognized Accord. His eyes widened as well as he was one of the two people Liz wanted to introduce to him when they gathered.

“Leader of the Scarlet Snow Alliance, Garen! Do you dare to come down and fight with me!!” Accord’s voice reverberated once more. Everyone could hear his words loud and clear!

“That Garen? Perhaps!!?” Liz and Dios recalled a terrifying possibility as they looked at the VIP seats at the same time.

Chapter 1129: Temporary 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s face was hidden under the helmet as he looked up at the stage. His expression could not be seen and the honored guests started to whisper among themselves. He was the only one who sat straight up, not moving an inch.

“According to the rules, the final victor is qualified to challenge one of the honored guests. Alliance Leader of the Scarlet Snow Alliance, please comply.” The referee voiced out. As this was the will of the Three Great Holy Lords, not a single Energy Machinist was allowed to defy it.

“You only get to challenge once.” Garen’s calm voice could be heard from the helmet. “You don’t have to waste it on me.”

“Haven’t we both been concealing our strengths for this exact moment?” Dark Light dispersed the black gas around his face and revealed his young, common-looking face which was rather pale and strange looking.

“Come! Let’s prove it now which one of us is the true genius!!” he unsheathed his sword as he activated his terrifying Non-falling Light, which set off a series of shockwaves trembling through the air.

He stared at Garen fiercely as he had already suspected that this Garen might be the Garen he knew back then. He was the best friend that he couldn’t get in touch with. He had searched the Scarlet Snow Alliance thoroughly and couldn’t find a second person called Garen. The only person who was called Garen was the rumored leader of the scarlet Snow Alliance. Hence, the suspicion within him rose. His best friend, who had always revealed his strength that was weaker than the Inherited Level had suddenly become a topnotch Sect Master powerhouse. The strength between these two was too great, which was the reason why he wanted to make full use of this opportunity to challenge him and place himself in the light of the whole situation.

He had been wanting to fight against Garen ever since he found out Garen had hidden his true strength!

Garen remained still in his seat.

However, the Judge’s Light Barrier could not care less how he reacted as the area he sat alone had turned into the battlefield.

The surrounding honored guests were isolated on the outside, leaving Dark Light and Garen together within the barrier.

The air twisted as Garen’s seat was directly sent towards the stage, forcing him to sit directly in front of Dark Light.

As Garen realized he could no longer push the issue away, he sighed.

“You, are no match for me.” He did not stand up as he did not wish to reveal his identity so soon. However, he did not expect the situation to end up like this.

“We will fight to see if I am no match for you!” Without saying another word, Dark Light unsheathed his sword and it immediately turned into a giant black scorpion and engulfed him. He then transformed into a black figure and lunged towards Garen.

“Dark Light’s Extreme Slash!!! Double!”

Two streaks of black blade’s marking in a cross shape were shot out into the air and were sent directly towards Garen’s position.

Garen’s Non-falling Light spread out, shaking the battlefield’s protective screen greatly.

“It’s useless.” Garen sat in his original position as he looked at the blade’s markings flying towards him quietly.

“My Absolute Energy Field, Faded Creation can absorb every external energy as nutrients. Your attacks are useless.”

The two blade markings became slower and smaller. By the time it reached Garen, what was left was two thin black lines struggling to move forward. Ultimately, they disintegrated and popped apart like burst bubbles.

“Interesting!” Dark Light’s revealed a ferocious smile on his face but his gaze had become more serious than ever.

“We have known each other for so long and I thought I had hidden a lot of my true strength. However, I didn’t expect you to be this terrifying and acted as someone more innocent than I am. I can finally reveal your true identity!”

“Aren’t you the same?” Garen was speechless under his helmet. “Don’t you feel ashamed that you’ve acted as if you’re a Resonance Level even though you’re at Non-falling Level?”

Two of them exchanged words quickly between the Non-falling light at an advanced. Hence no one could hear what they were talking about. Although a low-level communication was not allowed, an advanced one would be hard to restrict.

“Why did you come here and challenge me all of the sudden?” Garen asked without beating around the bushes.

“What do you mean? I suspected your identity and decided to test you out. I was still on the fence about it but I didn’t expect you to admit it.”

“Take this, Sky Shadow Slash!! Ahh!!” Accord shouted crazily as he changed his tune. “At least respect me and attack me! Won’t winning against me by just sitting there make me look bad!?”

“Alright alright…” Garen was helpless. Accord had never understood the concept of being polite and had always reacted on impulse. Hence, Garen decided to abide by his wishes.

Do it. Let’s Do it…he thought.

He raised up his right hand, hesitated and switched to his left hand. He then placed his hand forward and… pointed out… with his thumb…

As Accord approached him with his sword, envy was written all over his face.

“Ah!!!!” His cry had become more miserable and everyone could hear his true cry.

His swung his sword with all of his might but it came to a halt in front of Garen’s thumb.

Boom!

Accord’s collapsed as if he deflated like a balloon. He crawled on the stage as all of his energy had been absorbed by the Faded Creation…

He stared at Garen weakly. “You merciless bastard!!”

His eyes rolled as he passed out.

No one could see Garen’s face under the golden helmet. He sighed strangely as he gently tapped on his seat. Then, he started to levitate and went back to his VIP seat without moving at all.

He had never once stood up from the beginning until the end.

The whole battle lasted for only tens of seconds. Those people who wished to see Garen’s true strength were disappointed. However, since Garen was a Sect Master Level powerhouse and one of the recently popular strongest people around, they understood deep down that the other powerhouses would no longer require to mingle around in this world if a Non-falling Level was able to force him to use his full strength.

“The challenger has failed.” The referee announced calmly. “The overall schedule of the competition will start now…”

A rumbling similar to an earthquake came from underground and everyone present could feel the ground shaking.

Garen looked around. Although everyone was notified beforehand and prepared themselves for this moment, everyone seemed to not be able to hide their excitement from such a massive migration technique.

“This is amazing! To be able to migrate tens of thousands of people, including the crowds into a perfectly new stage for the final match. This delicate migration technique is not something a typical powerhouse can perform.”

However, Garen felt uncomfortable for some reason. He felt a strange unease around this boisterous competition.

“Which part of this feels off?” He kept looking around but he didn’t notice any suspicious target. The most crucial thing was that he could not sense any sign of the men in black earlier on.

“Have they completed their mission? Or are they about to create an even greater trouble?”

Garen’s mind analyzed quickly for every possibility.

“The divisional competition has been fully merged. Today’s competition has ended and the finals shall start at five o’clock in the morning. It will be an elimination from one Sect to the other.”

The referee spoke again.

The competition itself was very pure and transparent. Although it was filled with people, the competition was only held once every few years. While there would be a lot of people participating in it, Energy Machinists were people who cared about efficiencies so it would not be dragged for too long.

The merging had been completed.

The blue sky above the arena turned red in a blink of an eye.

Everyone participating in the competition had already been placed into a huge circular arena. Surrounding them were the audiences and there was a huge amount of camera equipment planted among the audiences, broadcasting the event live to the districts far away from this region.

“Black Jade Dragon! Black Jade Dragon! Black Jade Dragon! Black Jade Dragon!!”

A uniform cheer covered the entire sky. Similar to of a tidal wave, everyone chanted Black Jade Dragon’s name in unison.

The people from the third competitive zone had finally realized that they had been moved to a huge arena. The entire zone three competition zone, including the participants and crowds, had only covered a third of the extremely huge arena. The remaining two-thirds of the arena had already been filled with people.

The arena was a circular and tall stage. There was a tall and muscular copper brown man raising both of his hands up as he walked around the stage with a gleeful look.

The Magnetic Field’s Black Jade Dragon.

There were a few fanatics raising and swinging their metallic signboards with the words ‘all the best’ written on it high up in the air.

“Wilder!!” Black Jade Dragon shouted as he patted his own chest.

“Black Jade Dragon! Black Jade Dragon! Black Jade Dragon!!!” The crowd cheered louder. Some girls screamed.

“What’s with his attitude?!” Garen and the other honored guests were rather unhappy about it.

“He’s the strongest man from the Magnetic Field so it’s natural for him to be arrogant.” One man responded.

“White Lion and Dark Light were not as wild as him!”

“Young man, what’s bad about being wild?”

“What do you make of this, leader of the Scarlet Snow Alliance?” The female elder beside Garen looked at him.

“It’s their freedom to showcase themselves. I have no right to judge them.” Garen said calmly.

Black flying ships were densely packed in the sky above everyone’s head. The ships were moving about slowly, giving off a terrifying and oppressing Energy Field. It was obvious that there were some very powerful powerhouses sitting inside these ships.

Among these ships, the largest one was as big as a mini city. It was hexagonal and was fully black, levitating in the sky freely.

The emblem of one of the three major Sect, Magnetic Field, could be seen imprinted on it.

Garen raised his head and looked at the Magnetic Field’s ship. The blackhole-liked Level Ten presence could be clearly felt and there was at least ten Level Nine presences entangled about among each other as well. The oppression from the Energy Field was very immense as it covered the entire sky.

***********

Inside the Magnetic Field’s ship.

The floor was beautifully furnished with black flower texture. There was a lady in a full body dress which spanned towards the ground, she had a black top hat on her head. Her low cut dress was pitch black and the skirt had merged with the ground, which made her seemed like a giant tree growing from the metallic floor.

Her skin was extremely fair, her almond-shaped eyes were sharp, giving off a cold and seductive elegance.

A few males and females sat in front of her. They seemed to have just finished reporting to her, waiting calmly waiting for her orders.

“Magnetar Holy Lord, my household’s Saint had determined that the opponent will make their move in the finals. Do you want to attack together with us or insist on your desire? Please give us a response.” A man with a stern face said softly.

Magnetar Holy Lord shut her eyes without reacting to his question at all. She seemed to be pondering as she crossed her little snow-white hands on her abdomen.

“We’ve come to this situation and you’re still doubting the other Holy Lords? If we don’t unite together and fight against the threats towards the Energy Machinists, we will die in the hands of those greedy people hidden in the shadows! Holy Lord your Highness, have you not make up your mind?”

The man seemed to be the leader of these people. His presence was immense as he carried along the aura of a Level Nine. He looked extremely handsome and extravagance in his black suit.

The atmosphere turned dull all of the sudden.

Chapter 1130: Temporary 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The lady in the black dress, Magnetar Holy Lord remained silent.

“Mother, I have been your son for millenniums. Would you please let go of the past grudges?” A male voice that covered the entire ship came from the back.

“Black Blade Holy Lord…” The woman in the black dress sighed as a sign of tiredness could be seen in her gaze.

“It does not matter if I have become a Holy Lord. You will always be my mother.” His tone was sincere.

“Uncle Huaer is currently trapped and will not be able to break free within five days. It’s obvious that the Pilots will make their moves in these five days. If we don’t unite now, we may possibly not be able to protect our last foundation!” The voice said, slightly emotional.

“My brother Ma Nong is currently trapped as he had unexpectedly encountered a new type of giant Space Storm and had been sucked into an Inverse Space far away from here. I believe the Backlight Holy Lord is currently in the same situation. Our opponent has started to move. They’re currently cutting away those Regent Level powerhouses who are willing to lend us a hand. We really need to kill all of them in one sweep!”

“We have no idea how many they are inside these major Sects. They seem to be everywhere.” Magnetar Holy Lord said softly.

“The three of us are their main targets. In order to fight against us, they first have to eliminate the Modified Demon Lord Team that serves us. Hence, I believe that we can command the Modified Demon Lord Team to attack so that we can lure out some of the opponent’s strength. We will then eliminate them.” Black Blade Holy Lord explained simply. “Naturally, the plan is much harder than it sounds.”

“…” Magnetar Holy Lord didn’t respond as she shut her eyes.

“Mother, can I take your silence as an agreement?” Black Blade Holy Lord asked.

“Do what you want…I do not wish to meet Backlight ever again no matter what.” As Magnetar Holy Lord waved her hand, a terrifyingly powerful transparent Energy Field instantly repelled Black Blade Holy Lord’s Projection Energy Field.

“The Holy Lord had already considered this.” The Level Nine male leader who had reported to her earlier spoke. “He had sent an item through his subordinate and said that you are sure to change your mind after seeing it.”

“An item?” Magnetar Holy Lord asked curiously. ” Show it to me?”

“Yes.” With the utmost respect, the man took out a small box from the Space Ring. It was square in shape and had a ferocious black dragon’s image imprinted on it.

He released his hand as the box levitated and moved towards to Magnetar Holy Lord’s hand automatically.

“This is…” Magnetar Holy Lord opened the box and boom!!

Her eyes widened.

Slowly, she lowered her head and looked at her abdomen.

A black, short and extremely sharp spear had pierced into her abdomen. The short spear was pitch black and was unexplainably cold. Then, the body of the short spear started disintegrating and turned into throngs of huge, black worms drilling into her abdomen through the wound.

These worms were like miniaturized black beetles the size of a nail. However, their quantity was simply too many.

“Black Blade…” Magnetar Holy Lord was in disbelief as fresh blood started to flow out from the edge of her lips.

Boom!!!

An intense Energy Field tried to flare up but a solid and firm Spatial Barrier had unknowingly activated beforehand around her.

The face of the man who spoke earlier changed. After a few twisting here and there, it transformed into the stiffed face of Chinande.

“Magnetar Holy Lord, your son has submitted to the empire a long time ago. Backlight and you are the only ones left who are still delusional.”

“Chinande…” Magnetar found it difficult to speak up as her whole body started to tremble. She could not seem to tolerate the pain from the worms eating her out from the inside.

The Energy Field changed in a complex manner as it shifted into all sorts of attributes. However, it had no effect towards the black worms.

“As expected, the most dangerous person is the person who knows you best…” Magnetar smiled wryly as she understood that this was her son’s actual intention. He knew everything about her, from her response, reactions and hidden strength.

“You’re the only one I fear when it comes to fighting face to face. It’s rare to encounter a powerful opponent but…” Chinande said in remorse. “Everything is done for His Highness. I have no choice but to sacrifice my personal hobby.”

Boom!!

Magnetar exploded in an instant as a huge amount of black worms covered the entire sky and poured inside the mothership’s hall.

As the Spatial Barrier had surrounded the area, the Level Nines outside could not sense anything happening at all.

A humanoid appeared on Chinande’s body and shot out to where Magnetar was standing. It transformed into a new Magnetar Holy Lord, looking exactly like the original.

“Is Magnetar dead?” A female member behind Chinande asked lazily.

“No,” Chinande replied coldly. “She was ambushed by Black Blade’s black worms and had been cut into twenty-five thousand pieces. Although her body is destroyed, her Ultimate Board has yet to be discovered.”

“She has lost her battle body that she had successfully crafted through thick and thin. What use can a soul which lies in the Ultimate Board do? Although she can find another body at will, she can no longer bring her actual strength into play anymore.” The female member casually spoke. “She will never be able to get back on her feet without putting in thousands of years of effort again.”

“That is indeed true.” Another member agreed as he nodded.

“Let’s leave. We have already planted our mole.” Chinande ignored their conversations as he dispelled the Spatial Barrier. He then gently bowed towards the new Magnetar Holy Lord before turning around to leave the area.

“Send the emissary away.” Magnetar Holy Lord said in a cold, female tone.

One of the few Level Nine whose head was covered in silvery hair appeared as he glanced at Chinande.

“Let’s go.”

He did not realize that the Holy Lord had been replaced. Furthermore, he had yet to realize that the man in front of him was the real Light of Justice Chinande, who was also a Holy Lord Level powerhouse.

**************

The competition had stopped temporarily.

Black Jade Dragon slowly backed down from the main battle arena after flaunting his prowess for some time.

On the other hand, White Lion had gone to rest a long time ago and did not bother himself with the Black Jade Dragon.

Dark Light was beaten senseless by Garen and was currently receiving immediate treatment. The final was temporarily held off and the battle to compete for the rankings would be held on the second day. Although the top three had been finalized, there were still other rankings to be determined. Hence, there were still many days of fighting even after the main event, which was what the other candidates were aiming for excluding the three major sects.

The three major sects, namely the Black Blade, Star Cloud and Magnetic Field were always in the top three. It was a norm for everyone and no typical Energy Machinists could hope to compete against them.

Garen, who was at the battle arena, felt a sense of alienation for some reason.

It was already night time as he brought along the disciples of the Scarlet Snow back to his hotel. After making the arrangements and settling down Hong Guo and his subordinates, he waited for the final results.

As he had nothing better to do in the hotel, he decided to bring Ice-Crack and Ice-Grand out of the room for a stroll.

As he walked out of the elevator to the main elevator hall on the first floor, he saw Dark Light leaning against the door as if he was waiting for him.

“Let’s go for a stroll?” Dark Light glanced at Garen. Wisps of light green smoke curled gently out from the cigarette in his mouth.

“Sure,” Garen spoke through the helmet.

“Sect Master, at this crucial moment…” Ice-Grand frowned as he reminded and tried to discourage him.

“It’s fine.” Garen raised his hand. “Both of you won’t be able to do anything if someone really tries to harm me.”

Ice-Grand and Ice-Crack exchanged glances. They knew that Garen did not compromise easily hence they lowered their heads and took a step back.

“Sect Master, please return as soon as possible.”

“Both of you can enjoy yourselves. I’m sure there are old friends that you need to catch up with, right?” Garen said calmly.

“Yes.”

Dark Light then led the way as Garen walked from behind.

Liz was already waiting at the entrance of the hotel when both of them walked out of the building. Her boyfriend Dios was beside her and their expressions were rather awkward.

“Senior Brother Dark Light!” A few disciples from the Star Cloud Sect bowed and greeted Dark Light as they saw him.

“Alliance Leader!”

The newly formed crowd filled with students of the Scarlet Snow Alliance bowed and greeted Garen as well.

“No need to be so formal everyone, relax.” Garen and Dark Light said as they walked out of the hotel.

Walking in front, Dark Light turned his head around and looked at Liz.

“Want to go together?”

Liz was holding Dios’ arm tightly but she was urged by her boyfriend.

“Go,” Dios whispered, but he was not able to hide it from Garen and Dark Light.

There was a loud and sonorous singing coming out from one of the music halls nearby. The woman’s sharp and powerful voice spread far away during the night as it carried a mysterious and ethereal rhythm.

Liz gritted her teeth and followed them.

***********

At a riverside near the hotel, a row of green willow trees grew arranged by the river bank.

Dark Light stood at the top of the willow tree.

“How much percent of actual strength have you used today? Be honest!”

Garen took off his helmet gently, revealing his face which had not seen the sunlight for a very long time. His face was cold and valiant as there was a white V-shape imprint on his forehead, giving off an extremely intimidating and superior vibe.

This was the presence of a Level Ten with an infinite amount of amplification. At that level, he was like a sun where his presence would not go unnoticed wherever he went. Once the Ten Thousand Gravitational Force had reached a certain extent, it would naturally attract the souls of others.

“None…” Garen said honestly.

Dark Light’s expression immediately turned depressed.

“Are you saying that you stood there and let me attack you freely without fighting back?”

“Isn’t that what you wanted?” Garen laughed. “Stop being irrational.”

“Damn it!” Dark Light punched at the willow tree. “Is our strength really that big of a difference? I will have you know that I am a genius!”

“I can’t even hit you even if you let me…” Dark Light gnashed his teeth in frustration. “You’re really insane! People have always called me that in the past! I didn’t expect myself to say the same thing to someone else!”

“I really do not wish to kill your self-confidence. However, this is the truth and there’s nothing I can do about it.” Garen was speechless. “I promised that I would lead the Scarlet Snow Sect and revive it once more. I can’t go back on my words.”

“How do you plan on reviving it? The main competition will only test the disciples’ potential and the competition for territory repartition is not going to happen…” Dark Light asked with a bitter face.

Then, he seemed to recall something out of the blue, and as his expression turned rather strange and surprised.

“Are you planning to…”

“Yes. I’m going to do that.” Garen nodded his head in affirmation.

“It’s the Sect’s Hegemony. Any sect that is not satisfied with their ranking may challenge the sect which ranks above them. It’s a final match where one fights to the death!” Liz spoke from the side.

“They would often hold an exhibition competition after the main competition as the main competition decides the ranking of the sects. According to the rules, if anyone is unsatisfied with the result, the Sect Master or the powerhouse from the sect may represent the sect and go up the stage. However, the representative must use their sect’s technique.” She added quickly.

She and Dark Light looked at Garen with a complicated expression.

The strength difference between them and Garen was simply too great! It was so great that the phrase ‘a world’s apart’ could not be used to describe it.

Dark Light might have been a genius, but Garen was already moving forward to become an Overlord. The term genius could only be used to describe a potential seed that had yet to sprout. Garen, on the other hand, was no longer a genius…

Chapter 1131: Great Change 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Okay then… I’ll wish you good luck in advance.” Dark Light said reluctantly after being quiet for a moment.

“Believe in yourself,” Garen smiled.

The three of them strolled by the river. They chatted about their past and future plans. Most of the time, Garen was the listener and he paid attention while listening. After all, there was a huge gap between him and the two of them. The astonishing abilities of a transmigrater alone were enough to change him completely within a short amount of time.

In fact, for most of the common topics, Garen already knew the answer and where it will lead to. However, he was patient and continued to listen quietly to what Dark Light said.

Perhaps, it may no longer be this peaceful after a short while.

Garen could feel his own distorted seed growing rapidly and silently. One after another expert was being polluted and became a parasite. Almost all of them were Level Nine energy machinist. Among them, two parasites of the distorted seed broke through to Level Ten. Also, there were more than ten people who broke through from Level Eight to Level Nine.

This was an extremely brutal power and he believed that it will definitely surprise Chinande…

******************

Boom!!

Huge, red fireworks were being continuously set off throughout Planet Naga in the sky. It seemed like a huge, flower garden in the sky, each fireworks’ flower petals were so life-like that even the fine textures on the petals could be seen.

As the flower fireworks scattered naturally after its explosion, it turned into countless red light sparks.

Garen sat quietly at the honored guest seats during the finals. He was a contestant who represented the Sect Master to participate in the competition. Both Ice-Grand and Ice-Crack stood behind him.

Similarly, those around Garen were Sect Masters of medium-sized sects and large-sized sects. Each one of them had an imposing manner and a huge aura of someone with great power. Even the waiters who served the refreshments could feel their overwhelming presence.

It was not the pressure from a force field, but the pressure from someone with great power which gave people an oppressive impression.

As compared to the quirky image of the other Sect Masters, Garen’s white robe and golden helmet was nothing special.

The competition had started for some time. When Garen arrived with his people, three rounds had passed and it was now the fifth game. The two competitors could barely express the strength of an ordinary energy machinist under the 1,600 times force field pressure. They were both setting all kinds of traps since they both had a sinister characteristic. There were all kinds of tricks and schemes. Although it was not a hot-blooded scene, it was an extremely sinister and evil one.

Garen closed his eyes, none of the Sect Masters took the initiative to talk to him. The Scarlet Snow Sect violated the rules set by the Federation of Energy Machinists. Before the Three Great Holy Lord could fully come to a conclusion on this matter, any unknown reckless actions will affect each Holy Lord unfavorably. Therefore, to avoid trouble, everyone avoided speaking to Garen.

Garen and the both of them were quite happy about it.

Match after match went by. Garen was no longer interested in all these normal class matches, his main focus was on the distant Nebula headquarters.

Over there, all the distorted seeds inside each parasitic expert were being sold at a high price to friendly allies through a scheme. The Level Nine experts were being constantly engulfed one after the other.

Buzz!

There was a buzz in Garen’s head. Another Level Ten was born…

The terror of the distorted seed was evident.

This was the true fourth Level Ten among Garen’s parasites.

“Basically, those who can be infected through contact had been infected. The others are very cautious, so we will not succeed anytime soon.” The Double-Faced Man’s voice was transmitted through the distorted seed.

Part of Garen’s focus was on the matches and part of it was on the inside of the City of Nagadako. All kinds of strong parasites had their aura densely and evenly distributed almost in the entire City of Nagadako.

“Do you have any news about the Three Great Holy Lords? Especially the Demon Lord Team.”

The Demon Lords that he referred to were the modified humans. They were the Holy Lord Level modified humans. The biochemical pool and energy machinist platform of a Holy Lord Level cannot compare to those of an average person. Modified humans created through such technology were far more powerful than what ordinary people had imagined. Moreover, they can provide resonance and also increase their Holy Lord’s power tremendously.

This was also the reason why people would want to get rid of the Demon Lord modified human team before dealing with the energy machinist Holy Lord.

“There has not been any news and it is very peaceful. Strangely, the Magnetar Holy Lord seems to be way too calm about our actions. Could it be that they do not care or they are unaffected by it?” The Double-Faced Man said in a dubious tone.

“What about the rest of them?” Garen was asking about the other Level Ten Holy Lords. The few newly promoted Level Ten did not believe when Garen talked about how serious the crisis was. However, they still did all kinds of preparative jobs just to be safe. At the same time, they went around to investigate and gather information.

“After they understood your involvement in this, they went everywhere to investigate about it. It seems like they discovered something. They might have made a move on the other party secretly.” The Double-Faced Man laughed creepily. “Since they are not cooperating, it would be great if they suffer some losses.”

“Be careful, they’ll make a move within these two days…” Garen said lightly.

“Rest assured. I know my boundaries.” The Double-Faced Man said casually. “Based on my initial estimation, they must have used the power of five Perpetual Motioners and Level Nine experts from the North Pole. They even sent the direct subordinates of the White King from the North Pole. Moreover, they also sent the Royal Star Force and Spirit Deity from the Scarlet Mourning Hall Union… it seems like they are really worried that we are not fully doomed…”

“It’s good that you understand the situation.” Garen had a calm look on his face. “We will have no choice but to abandon those who don’t listen to our commands.”

“Four of us should be more than enough. Together with the other two Holy Lords, I doubt that they can do anything about it!” The Double-Faced Man’s voice gradually got weaker and he slowly disconnected.

Garen remained expressionless under his helmet. Even though all the parasites were not able to hurt him, including the Double-Faced Man, but they were starting to show signs of disobedience towards his commands. However, this was within Garen’s anticipation. Although the distorted seeds were able to greatly increase the power of the parasites, due to their chaotic nature, the parasites will not necessarily obey their parental orders.

“Soon… very soon…”

Matches passed by, and it was the finals. All the Non-Falling Levels were showing off without any reservation. The first three divisions were still on the low-profile side. Then, the aura of the Non-Falling disciples filled the air. From time to time, two Non-Falling Light Pillar will appear and draw everyone’s attention.

The elites of the bigger sects were all at the Non-Falling level. There were also a few Non-Falling Levels from the medium-sized sect. Hong Guo and his team had just gone up and they had no choice but to throw in the towel and give up. As compared to their previous below the average ranking, they were able to increase their rank above the average by entering the finals. There were a large number of energy machinist sects and the variously sized sects summed up to about a hundred sect. It was already a huge achievement to be able to rank above average under such situation.

After Hong Guo and his team left the stage, the entire Scarlet Snow Sect had completely become audiences. They sat quietly in their seats to observe the remaining matches.

Dark Light, Jade Dragon, and White Lion charged in with a victorious gesture one after the other. Taking center stage, no one was able to stop them.

There were also a few rare geniuses among the crowd who were previously unknown to the public. This time, they appeared with a skyrocketing potential. They had an endless variety of rare killing moves. Some of it was created by the disciples themselves and some were ancient secret tactics found from the ruins.

Although the secret tactics were fairly weak, some of it was useful even to experts like Garen. Therefore, everyone paid much observation and attention in anticipation of their performance.

Time went by gradually and soon, the day was over.

Nothing happened overnight and the entire Planet Naga was abnormally quiet.

The competition went on as usual the next day.

Soon, the champion was chosen among all the players.

Somehow, Jade Dragon was heavily injured last night and remained unconscious still. Whereas Dark Light forfeited his participating right and disappeared without a trace. There was a rumor saying people saw both of them fought due to some disagreements and they were both heavily injured.

That rumor was oddly convincing since it was being described with great detail.

Garen was not able to contact Dark Light even after transmitting a few voice messages to him. Gradually, a clear conspiracy theory started to form.

White Lion, a brutal young man with a head of wild white hair was the champion of this competition.

The mayor came forward as one of the Three Great Holy Lords, Backlight, and awarded White Lion with a trophy.

White Lion’s magnetic field began to celebrate. The elders from the other sects represented their sects by giving a speech on the stage. All the sects seemed to be in a joyful mood. The magnetic field experts and disciples started the huge celebration by distributing invitations to all the influential experts. The sky was filled with celebratory pink petals and a cheerful music was played.

White Lion went up the stage with a smile and was prepared himself to receive the energy instillation from the joint efforts of the Three Great Holy Lords.

The Three Great Holy Lords appeared. From left to right, it was the Magnetar Holy Lord, the Backlight Holy Lord, and the Black Blade Holy Lord. Their faces were distorted under a white light, and only their silhouette and postures could be seen.

Everything went on in an orderly manner.

Layers of strong barriers continue to rise as Planet Naga began to draw one of the three greatest treasures of the city, the Union.

No one knew where the location of the Union was. It was an extremely tyrannical equipment made by energy machinists. It can only be created by gathering countless experts, elites, geniuses, and energy in one place. Its greatest role was to forcibly raise the Level of all the energy machinists to any Level below and including Level Eight. It also had a terrifying ability which allowed their owner to instantaneously combine forces with the power of the same type which was within the range.

This meant that as long as the treasure was still in the hands of the Three Great Holy Lords, there is no need to worry of an enemy attack. The Union will instantly link the willpower and energy of all the Level Nine, Level Eight, Non-Falling Level experts together with the Three Great Holy Lords to form a strong body of energy that was beyond compare. This body of energy was extremely strong even among the Regent Levels, and an ordinary Regent Level will not necessarily be able to beat it. Together with the other Regent Levels who had a good relationship with the Three Great Holy Lords, the status of the energy machinist can then be as stable as a mountain.

This treasure can only be actively drawn by Backlight. Therefore, Backlight was appointed as the Mayor of Planet Naga.

Garen had a feeling that his plans can no longer keep up with the changes when he saw how fast the situation was developing. Instead of following the usual sequence, the pilots had eliminated Dark Light and Jade Dragon out of the competition.

Chapter 1132: Great Change 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A terrifying sun-like aura began to spread in the direction of the Three Great Holy Lords. The Union will soon befall…

“It seems like it’s not possible to wait for the Championship. The Union will befall soon…” Garen transmitted a voice message to Ice-Grand and Ice-Crack who were both standing behind him. Receiving his message, they both left quietly.

Soon, they left the stadium slowly together with Hong Guo and the others.

Bang!

With a loud bang, a huge Scarlet Light Pillar appeared out of thin air and descended down from the red sky. The metal-like Light Pillar landed on the ground heavily, surrounding the White Lion and the Three Great Holy Lords in it. It was almost impossible for the others to see clearly what was happening inside.

All the spectators were amazed at the Scarlet Light Pillar. No matter how many times they look at the Light Pillar, they could feel a strong, holy aura radiating from it.

Gasps of admiration could be heard continuously. There was a buzz around Garen as everybody started to discuss about the Union.

Except for Garen, whose eyes under his helmet were staring intently at the inside of the Light Pillar.

The Energy Machinist Extinction War had finally started…

A red light quietly lighted up on his index finger. It seemed like something was being contained in his fingertips.

As time went by slowly, Garen’s finger slowly pressed downwards. The red light on top was showing a tendency to turn dark.

*******************

In the depths of the Finite Nebula.

A huge celestial body whirlpool was in the middle of it. There was also an immensely huge white palace which looked like it was built during the ancient times. The structure and the stone pillars on the palace implicated its long, ancient history.

The palace’s sharp edges had worn off by the traces from thousands and thousands of years ago.

At this time, the shadow of a blood-colored flaming figure appeared on the palace’s long, white staircase.

The figure’s silhouette was burning in a red-colored flame. Countless, thick and dense black gasses encircled the figure. Each black gas had a twisted and painful human face, screaming in grief.

“White King.” The figure’s face was revealed. It was a young woman, with a glamorous face and strong features.

“The trajectory of fate can’t decide everything. The universe should be ruled by me, Wattana Gersa!!”

Her figure suddenly hopped on the stone steps. With every leap, the space surrounding the entire palace shook violently.

The women’s figure was like a dazzling red light. In a flash, she landed directly on the highest point of the stone steps in the large white square outside the palace. A white figure was already waiting there.

Without wasting any words, the woman in red light stretched out her arms. Her five fingers instantly turned into the sharpest terrifying weapon. Her entire body turned into a dazzling red-color and she lunged forward.

Two rays of light, one in white and one in red crashed into each other.

Boom!!!

Bang.

A drop of clear water dripped down onto the wooden table underneath the delicate and beautiful red rose.

“The Wraith Royalties finally made a move on the White King.”

A man in gold clothing at the side of the table had a serene and calm look on his face. It seemed as though he was talking about something extremely common.

“The White King of this generation is a man with great talent and bold vision. He has the ambition to unite the two great races.” An off human figure was floating in the air behind the man in gold clothing.

The head of the human figure was distorted and transformed constantly. It was a dark mist without a fixed shape.

“It depends on whether the Wraith Monarch will succeed in the challenge…”

**********************

Garen gently tapped his index finger which was glowing with a red light on to the table.

“Do it!” A subtle voice transmission was being transmitted to somewhere extremely distant through the distorted seed.

A slight ripple appeared on Garen’s white robe from being blown by the wind.

With a ‘swoosh’, the red light was slightly stunned. It seemed like something was happening inside it.

Almost at the same time, Garen jumped into the air from the place where he was sitting at.

Bang!

The chair shattered into countless fragments. A large amount of terrifying aura and energy field gathered at where Garen was formerly sitting.

Beneath the helmet, Garen’s face changed slightly and he quickly retreated backward. He was holding a black space jumping ball in his hands and just when he was about to smash it downwards.

In a flash, a white shadow suddenly appeared right behind him.

A huge energy field instantly locked Garen in place. His entire body was being forcibly held still.

The experts around could not even react to the series of sudden changes. By the time they did so, they found that the terrifying energy field of the shadow that trapped Garen was as deep as a black hole.

All the experts around left quickly. No one dared to stay at the scene since everyone could tell that the shadows were obviously going after Garen.

“What are you guys doing?” Garen’s deep voice came from under the gold helmet. It sounded hollow yet deep.

The white figure behind him laughed gently.

“Jeros… or Garen?”

Garen turned around to look at that person, who was removing the white headgear.

“You are…!” Garen was stunned.

Swoosh, the headgear ripped apart. It revealed a woman’s delicate and pretty face with a hint of boyish charm. Her short green-colored hair was flipping being blown by the wind.

“Do you still recognize me, Nono.”

The woman grinned, showing her white teeth.

“Celine…” Garen did not expect an encounter with Celine on such occasion.

Celine?! How did an ordinary Inherited Level appear in such a place? Moreover, she had such a tyrannical aura fluctuation. It was impossible!!

But if it was not Celine, then who could it be…? Suddenly, the most possible explanation popped up in Garen’s mind.

Swoosh-swoosh-swoosh-swoosh!

Four consecutive white shadows flickered and four white human figures appeared on Garen’s four sides, encircling him in the center.

Each figure was holding a sparkling crystal lamp in their hands. The wick of the lamp was burning with a subtle white flame. The small circular boards that slowly appeared right in front of them were the reason why the four figures were strong. It was a circular board that was as pure as a milky-white color.

“The Sublime Board!! Oh God, all of it are top-class Sublime Boards! They are from the North Pole!!”

A stunned honored guest suddenly stood up with a horrified look on his face.

“Level Nine… four Level Nine experts!! This is a planned assassination!! Quick, call the police!!” Someone shouted loudly.

That man’s voice echoed throughout the entire venue. There was a sudden chaos once everyone heard about the Level Nine experts.

Level Nine experts! What was the concept of it? They were the horrifying beings who were two levels above the Non-Falling Level. Four of these experts actually appeared together in one place. They were the top experts who were able to move the entire planet’s foundation!! However, four of them actually appeared in one place, together at the same time!

“We must inform the Three Great Holy Lords!”

Clang! Suddenly, countless Destruction Lasers exploded in the crowd unknowingly.

It was havoc as the crowd stood up and tried to escape frenziedly. Many ordinary people were trampled to death as the packed crowd rushed to escape.

Only a small number of great personages with guards were able to forcibly open a path through the crowd and leave.

“No…you are not Celine.” Suddenly, Garen who was at the center of the field said. “You are… Chinande!!”

Garen looked at his surroundings. Even he was frightened by the overwhelmed undisguised fluctuations of the several Level Nine experts around him.

“… What a… huge scene…”

“How can you be so sure? Your sensing ability really does live up to its reputation.” Celine was slightly surprised. He could sense the firmness in Garen’s tone. His face started twisting and instantly transformed into a countless number of faces. There were elderlies and youngsters. Also, there were men and women.

Soon, his face changed and turned into a cold yet familiar face — Carthage!

His entire temperament instantly transformed into Carthage’s cold temperament. It seemed as though every face that he changed into will have a unique personality match. This momentary change in the temperament and traits gave people a feeling that he had split personalities.

“I actually did not manage to fool you,” Chinande said coldly and emotionlessly. “Surrender yourself. For the time being, I don’t want to kill you.”

“It’s not up to you whether you kill me or not…” Garen grinned, but no one could see his smile under the helmet.

Swoosh!!

Suddenly, beams of white light descended from the sky. It surrounded Chinande and the rest of them from all directions.

One after another tyrannical aura rushed into the sky. A white circular board clearly appeared on each of their bodies. All of it was Level Nine Sublime Boards!

“So you want to fight? No problem!” The Double-Faced man’s gold armor appeared in the white light. The aura around his body was ambiguous. He did not fully release his Level Ten aura, but it was faintly enough to suppress all the Level Nine auras.

Chinande looked at his surroundings.

“Pointless struggle.”

“What about us?”

Before the sentence was completed, four black hole-like auras suddenly appeared around Chinande and the rest of them. The one leading was a tall woman with four arms.

Four Level Ten experts?!

Chinande’s lifeless pupil suddenly shrunk.

*******************************

Inside the huge, red light pillar.

The Union was an exquisite scarlet key which was descending slowly from the sky above the light pillar. Then, it headed towards the Backlight Holy Lord who was standing in the middle among the Three Great Holy Lords.

A faint buzzing vibration sound filled the air. The buzzing sound had a strange rhythm which gave people an extremely sacred feeling. If the most powerful Regent Level expert was present, the expert might be able to hear the thoughts of countless people hidden within it. It might be anticipation, it might be a prayer, or it could be anger. The willpower of countless energy machinists was linked and gathered on this exquisite key.

Apart from the Three Great Holy Lords and White Lion, only the three representative examiners who witnessed the ceremonial were inside the Light Pillar. The three of them were the representatives elected by the other sects, excluding the three major sects. They were all at the peak of Level Nine and were three extremely old elderlies. The youngest one had lived for more than 4,000 years, whereas the oldest one had lived for more than 9,000 years. He had witnessed the rapid development of the technology and the war between humans and the Finite people.

The three of them looked extremely old. They had long, braided, white beards, and were dressed in white robes with subtle blue fluorescent patterns on top.

The Backlight Holy Lord took the Union key and gently walked towards White Lion. He looked at White Lion who was kneeling on one knee.

“On behalf of all the energy machinists, I grant you the greatest honor.”

The Backlight Holy Lord reached out his hand and gently stroked White Lion’s head.

Right at that moment, a sudden change occurred.

Chapter 1133: Beyond the Plan 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Countless blinding, white light exploded out of White Lion’s body.

It seemed like numerous gold spear-like terrifying swords. Suddenly, it started spreading in all directions. One of it with a subtle secretive filthy aura shot towards the front of the Backlight Holy Lord’s chest.

“You!!” Backlight’s surprised voice was heard. A transparent Space Whirlpool appeared in front of his body. Its horrifying power constantly disrupted the gold sword from exploding. The two forces refused to give in and remained still for a brief moment.

Suddenly, a palm as fair as a white jade quietly pressed against Backlight’s back.

Pff!!

Backlight spat a mouthful of blood. He looked at the Magnetar Holy Lord unbelievably.

“Magnetar… you!!”

Boom!!

Only then, the power of Magnetar’s hit heavily exploded. Backlight was being thrown into the air in another direction.

“Are you okay, Backlight? Do you know what are you doing, Magnetar!!?” The Black Blade Holy Lord shouted furiously and rushed over to catch Backlight. However, he secretively thrust his wrist forward and pierced into Backlight’s back.

Clang!!

A crisp yet piercing sound of a collision was heard. Two white shadows suddenly grabbed his wrist.

“Black Blade Holy Lord, we didn’t think that you would betray the energy machinist.” The two old examiners suddenly appeared on Black Blade’s side, one on the left and one on the right. They brutally restrained his movement.

“You… you guys!!” The Backlight Holy Lord instantly regained his senses and took a few steps backward. He walked painfully to a safe distance, looking extremely pale. Then, he walked towards the last examiner.

The situation suddenly became oddly strange.

First, White Lion made a surprise attack on him. However, Backlight blocked it. The actual sneak attack was the hit on his back from Magnetar. After injuring Backlight, Black Blade wanted to give him a final hit by pretending to save him. Nonetheless, it was being blocked by the two examiners.

These series of changes happened as quickly as a flash of lightning and a burning flint.

Pff!

Backlight spat a mouthful of blood once again. The blood seemed to be dark and foul.

“I didn’t expect… I really didn’t expect this… I almost died at the hands of my companions…” He removed the white light around his face and revealed a fair-looking middle-aged man. He looked just like an ordinary man. There was no difference between him and the ordinary people on the street. He did not have an extraordinary temperament or features. There was nothing special about him.

“I also didn’t expect it.” The Black Blade Holy Lord smiled coldly while he stared at the two old white-bearded examiners standing in front of him. “I didn’t expect three experts of Perpetual Motion Level to be hiding here… Dean Pasym, when did you surpass Level Ten?”

His gaze turned towards the oldest white-haired old man who was standing beside Backlight.

The old man lowered his eyes with an indifferent look on his face.

“It’s been a couple hundreds of years already. Is that important?” The old man, Pasym, had been the Dean of the three cities’ Central Sect for thousands of years already. Almost everyone thought that he was restricted because he was nearing his end. It was absolutely impossible for him to break through to the Perpetual Motion Level. He will be stuck at the peak of Level Nine.

He did not expect the old man to quietly break through Level Ten.

“What do you know about our plan?” Black Blade asked coldly.

“I know everything that you think I should know.” The old man smiled, turned around and looked towards the Magnetar Holy Lord. “Sir, Light of Justice Righteousness. Since you’ve come, why are you still pretending to be someone else? Could it be that that the Light of Justice, Finite’s General, dare not reveal his true identity?”

“The Light of Justice?” Backlight’s pupil constricted and he instantly looked towards the Magnetar Holy Lord.

As expected, the Magnetar Holy Lord’s body melted into slime and quickly reshaped into a new human form. It was Chinande, the Light of Justice.

However, Chinande’s eyes were no longer a withered ghostly white. One of it was red and one of it was blue in color. Both of his eyes had a mysterious and glamourous colorful rainbow glow.

“It’s really you!” The Backlight Lord was the one who was being kept in the dark. After witnessing the series of changes and the appearance of the Light of Justice, it could only mean that the pilots had actually made a move on the energy machinists.

They had truly started a war.

For a moment, he was furious when he thought about how chaotic the rest of the world will be. Since the pilots had decided to make a move and make a sneaky plot against the three Great Holy Lords, the rest of the world will definitely be worse than this!

He had finally understood the situation completely.

Chinande had an ever-changing transformation ability. He disguised himself as the Magnetar Holy Lord to make a sneak attack on Backlight. After he had succeeded, he did not expect the three Perpetual Motion Level experts to appear.

At that instance, both parties were in a stalemate.

However, both parties understood that the energy machinists will be truly doomed… If Chinande was not able to solve the problem, a second Chinande will make a move. It will continue until they get rid of all the energy machinists.

This was the overall trend of the entire pilot world and it cannot be reversed. The reason being the energy machinists had occupied way too many resources.

“Unexpected variables… Pasym, who delivered the news to you.” Chinande asked calmly. The strange shape of his right and left eye gave people a feeling that his aura was expanding continuously.

“There are still more variables that you didn’t expect…” The old man lowered his eyebrows and said calmly. He single-handedly supported Backlight. “Backlight, are you okay?”

“I’m okay. We can deal with the two of them together with the other two examiners. Either way, it is three against two. It won’t be that bad.” Backlight answered forcibly. In fact, the hit from Magnetar was not as simple as it seemed. A highly toxic metal went into his body and he was being poisoned. At the moment, his body was decaying and festering rapidly.

************************

Outside of the Light Pillar.

Garen was surrounded by Chinande and their surroundings were filled with Level Nine experts. During such a significant moment, a large number of rarely seen Level Nine experts appeared continuously. It was as though their appearances were as common as the cabbages found on the street.

Those below Level Nine will not even be able to stand still.

Garen and Chinande were at the innermost area, followed by the White King’s four Level Nine experts. Whereas the Double-Faced Man and the Level Nine experts that he brought formed a circle around them. Lastly, the four newly formed Level Ten parasites were at the outermost layer.

The scene had completely frozen still. No matter how strong Chinande was, that was just his clone. His actual power was being put into the inside of the light pillar. At that moment, the light pillar was being split into inside and outside. Therefore, the situation had reversed instantly and he became extremely fragile.

“Do you believe that I’ll retreat because of your few, normal class Perpetual Motion Level?” Chinande said calmly with an indifferent look on his face.

“What about your teammates? I’m afraid that they are still suppressing the Three Great Holy Lord’s Demon Lord modified team?” Garen said plainly.

Boom!!! Right after he completed his sentence.

The entire ground started shaking and waves of an earthquake were coming from afar. It was as if two huge forces collided with each other from afar.

“Look, the Demon Lord modified team is not that easy to deal with…” Garen was clear at a glance.

The look on Chinande’s face became slightly gloomy.

“Who the hell are you?” Even Jeros would not know that much insider information.

“It doesn’t matter who I am…” Garen said in a low voice. “What’s important is what can I do?”

He looked at the various types of spaceships and levitating airships around fleeing in all directions. The people from the Scarlet Snow Sect had left earlier with their own people.

Dark Light and the rest of them had also retreated in advance.

“Say Chinande, if we were to keep you here, who knows whether the Star Emperors would be willing to lend a helping hand?” The Double-Faced Man sneered coldly.

“The Star Emperors?” A trace of sarcastic look flashed through Chinande’s eyes. “Do you think that the people from the Star Emperors are here to help you?”

The Double-Faced Man and the rest of the Level Ten experts were stunned.

The contradiction between the pilots and the energy machinists had always been the same. The reason why there was an outburst was that the pilots were being suppressed for way too long. However, with such a huge move, the pilots will not give up that easily. The force of the Star Emperors might be the second move that they planned.

So much so that they might have divided all the energy machinists’ resources.

At that moment, both parties dare not act rashly. That was because when they reach such level, no one will be able to control affected range of damage if they start fighting. They might even cause the Planet to collapse by having a small fight.

That was something that neither the pilots who wanted to divide the resources nor the energy machinists themselves would wish upon.

Garen clearly knew that such a weak balance was like the nuclear chain balance of the Earth. When everyone had the power to destroy everything, nobody dared to act too rashly. If they were to make a reckless move, everyone will lose everything.

“Just give up, your plan has failed,” Garen said calmly. “As long as one of the Perpetual Motioner is not trapped, they can still easily destroy the entire energy machinist planet. In the end, everyone will lose everything.”

His words showed a slight hint that he would like to compromise. People cannot defy the overall trend, but they can make changes in somewhere small. If the energy machinists do not extinct, the contradiction will not be resolved while Garen’s aim was to protect something within his capabilities. That was it.

The fall of energy machinist was the choice of the generation and it cannot be avoided. Therefore, he had no choice but to protect himself.

Everyone’s gaze was fixed on Chinande. His decision at the moment will determine whether all the experts will fight or call a truce. If they were to start fighting, all the Level Nine experts present will not be able to back out from it. This battle will without a doubt destroy the entire Planet Naga.

The destruction of Planet Naga will most likely trigger a space storm in the inverse space area.

Not to forget that Planet Naga existed in a special environment, it was located in the Inverse Space instead of the Positive Universe. Everything will be the exact opposite compared to the Positive Universe.

It was surrounded by violent space storms. Anyone could be in danger if they were not careful.

The stagnant airstreams were intertwined with the force field of all the experts present. Even the smallest space particle would not be able to pass through this place. Excluding force fields, everything else will be repelled. The Level Nine experts’ tens of thousands fold of gravitational forces were intertwined together. All of them were concentrated on Chinande and the few of them. Whereas the strong qi’s dynamic of the Double-Faced Man and the remaining Level Ten experts were fixed on Chinande. They dare not lose focus for even a second.

As a Royal Star, Chinande was far greater than any other Perpetual Motioners. If he were to start fighting recklessly, the rest of the people might not be able to win.

However, this was a special situation.

“Make your decision, Chinande.” Garen sounded as though he had everything in control. The situation played out just as he had expected. Be it inside or outside the light pillar, it was almost the same as he expected.

“The only thing that I can’t figure out is that you would actually gather people to make a move on me. Moreover, you actually see me as a target? I don’t understand.” Garen stated his doubts.

Chapter 1134: Beyond the Plan 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

At this moment, the ground and sky had already been completely cleared. The entire city within their sight was entirely empty and it was dead silent. Garen’s voice echoed slowly and gave people a tangible feeling.

“Wraith Royalty, it’s just you alone now…” Chinande said lightly.

“Wraith Royalties!!??” After he said that, it caused a commotion among the rest of the people.

Garen was actually a Wraith Royalty!? What was that? The Wraith Royalties was the noblest race in the history of the universe. They were born with an extremely gifted power. After they become an adult, they will reach the Inherited Level and possess an Inherited Level wounding power. Before humans and the Finite People had grown stronger, they ruled a corner of the Milky!

They were the oldest and strongest clan! They also had a magnificent glory and history!

They were the ruler of the previous generation and they signified the ancient nobles. Most importantly, the Wraith Royalties were at the Finite People’s side! Both parties joined forces to turn against the humans!

“Unfortunately, I have now confirmed that you are definitely not Jeros,” Chinande said in a low voice. “You don’t even know that your sister, the Wraith Monarch, is challenging the White King. Do you think anyone would believe that you are a Wraith Royalty?”

“Why does it matter if he’s a Wraith Royalty or not?” The Double-Faced Man said indifferently. “It’s fine as long as we know that he is standing on our side!”

“Talk after you’ve solved the current problem!” The four-armed woman sneered. “Chinande, this is not even your actual body. Be sensible and leave, or I, Torona, will not have mercy!!”

“The Forest Light Holy Child, Torona? A Level Ten Holy Child is indeed very troublesome. However, it’s solely just troublesome.” Chinande reached out his hands and stretched it lightly.

Instantly, a blinding white light ball started expanding from his palms and rapidly exploded in all directions.

“He actually dared to make a move!!” Garen was surprised. It was just his clone, but he dared to make a move against five Level Ten experts!!

“Chinande! Are you crazy?!” The Double-Faced Man said furiously.

“I’m not crazy. It’s a pity that you all missed a point. I don’t need any Energy Mechanists’ resources…” Chinande smiled slightly for the first time. “Goodbye… all of you.”

Sss!!!

The radius of the incomparably dazzling white light expanded instantly and swept through everyone. It frenziedly flew towards all directions. All the surrounding buildings were sliced in half by the white light as if it was being cut up by a big, sharp blade. The surface of where the buildings were cut in half was as smooth as a mirror.

Everyone gradually began to resist the force field. However, the more they resisted, the larger the amount of Star Core Power was drawn. It caused the entire Planet Naga to shake violently.

“No, stop using too much power. Otherwise, it will trigger a space storm and everyone will die!!” Torona shouted. Even though she was a woman, no one treated her like a woman because she had a rougher voice than a man.

“We’ll die faster if we don’t resist!!” The Double-Faced Man said furiously.

One after another terrifying force field light rushed into the sky. The massive Star Core Power was like the transparent tentacles of a jellyfish which constantly drilled out of the surface of the planet. It poured into the body of all the Level Nine and Level Ten experts present to help them resist the sharp white halo.

But, the more they extracted, the entire Planet Naga shook even harder.

At the moment, if someone were to look at Planet Naga from the outer space, they will see rings of thin, white ripples spreading from a center. The ripples spread directly to the entire surface of the planet and formed extremely huge white rings.

Several colorful light pillars intertwined together in the middle of the ring and rushed into the sky. It directly shot towards the black space storms outside of Planet Naga.

Bang!!

A satellite which orbited around Planet Naga was shattered by this massive rainbow light pillar. It caused a large number of metal fragments to spatter. The colorful light pillar went through it and directly hit the black space storm behind!

Bang…

A loud gloomy sound was heard from the black storm. The space storm was like a black ink tide surrounding Planet Naga, constantly tumbling around violently. The rainbow light pillar struck it. It was as though a drop of water fell into a pot of boiling oil, instantly disrupting its fragile balance.

A gigantic, loud rumbling sound could be heard continuously. Suddenly, a large amount of black ink-like dark clouds flooded in through the crack made by the light pillar. Dark clouds rushed into Planet Naga.

****************

“Go!!” Garen roared with a low voice through voice transmission. He took the lead and rushed into the sky.

At that moment, the faded creation force field kept him from being confined. Instead, he devoured the energy of the attack and rushed into the sky.

The remaining Level Nine and Level Ten parasites were fighting against the people from the North Pole.

Chinande ignored him. Since the balance was broken, the space storm will arrive soon. If they do not retreat, they will all die right there.

All the experts present were experienced and farsighted. They rushed into the sky without needing Garen’s reminder. They went to search for a dimensional Long Distance Space Jumping Tool.

Garen flew into the sky without caring what was happening to the Double-Faced Man and the rest of them. It was already good enough that he gave them a reminder.

His body figure shot towards the Union light pillar like a flash of lightning. Garen had estimated the time accurately. Just as he flew towards there, he felt the light pillar getting weaker. With a slight force, the red light pillar in front of him tore apart like a cloth. It exposed an opening to the inside of the pillar.

There was another Chinande inside. The Backlight Holy Lord and a white-haired old man were standing together. The Black Blade Holy Lord was confronting two Level Ten experts and both parties’ qi’s dynamics were intertwined together. As soon as an opening was being torn open, the horrifying pressure from the qi’s dynamic turned into actual transparent blades and shot towards all directions.

Sss!

The blades that flew towards Garen were being naturally devoured soundlessly.

“It’s you!” It seemed as though the Chinande inside the pillar did not know what was happening outside. When he saw Garen, he was slightly confused.

Without saying a word, Garen reached out his hands and grabbed the Union key. The key was currently in the hands of Backlight.

“Give the Union to me!” It was the first time in a long time since Garen broke out with his full strength without holding back.

“Destructive Fist!!”

The violent force field around him was distorted and started vibrating. His horrifying force field instantly elevated into an abnormally powerful level, causing the surrounding red light pillar to spread open as though there was an explosion.

With a loud bang, Garen flew towards Backlight. It seems as if he turned into a mountain with his oppressive unmatched enormous force field.

“Don’t even think about it!!” Pasym who was standing beside Backlight sneered coldly and raised his hands to block Garen.

But right at that moment, the other two examiners actually let loose of their qi’s dynamic. By doing so, Black Blade’s qi’s dynamic went straight to Backlight who was heavily injured. At the same time, the both of them made a move and directed their qi’s dynamics towards Backlight to keep him oppressed.

“Dean, give it to him! We must retreat immediately!” One of the old men transmitted a voice message. “Planet Naga will be destroyed soon! This is the overall trend!”

The look on Pasym’s face did not change. He continued to stretch out his hands to grab Garen.

Boom!

Suddenly, something on his body exploded. This explosion disrupted this power and he was rapidly weakened.

The force field on top of Garen was weakened along with the loud bang.

“Go!!” Garen transmitted a voice message to the two examiners. The reason why the two of them were able to reach Level Ten was due to the distribution of his Distorted Seed. The reason why the old dean appeared here was that the two of them were spreading the news. They were part of the plan that was arranged by Garen.

The force field did not harm the elderly dean the slightest. Its speed decreased quickly and wrapped around the key in the Backlight Holy Lord’s hand. Then he flew into the air once again and left through the opening of the light pillar.

After Garen got what he wanted, he left without any hesitation. Everything was done.

Dark Light and the people from the Scarlet Snow Sect had left in advance using the jump portal. At that moment, they should be back in Planet Scarlet Snow already. They should begin to migrate along with the entire sect.

They could no longer stay among the human race.

Since energy machinists could no longer co-exist peacefully with the pilots, all they could do was retreat and wait for the right time.

To rebuild Scarlet Snow Sect, they will not need to blindly rush into a battle. Instead, they should have the ability to protect themselves during a crisis.

After the Energy Machinist extinction, it will be the White King’s battle of unity. The flames of war will spread all over the place and there will be changes in the overall trend that will last for hundreds of years.

What Garen wanted to do was to avoid the limelight, rest and build up his strength. To strengthen Snow Sect and set up an empire that will last for generations was not just a lot of talk. Together with the Union key, the Scarlet Snow Sect will be able to rapidly increase the potential strength of the elite disciples. After resting and building up their strength, they will definitely surprise everyone during their next reappearance!

By that time, it will truly be a brilliant achievement.

As Garen flew into the sky at a high speed, he felt the sky getting darker and darker. A countless amount of ink-like clouds gradually invaded the atmosphere of the entire Planet Naga.

Most of the people below did not know what was happening. They raised their head to look up at the odd changes in the sky.

During an outbreak of a war, the ordinary citizens were the innocent bystanders. When the higher-ups were in a battle, they did not even have the chance to escape. All they could do was to wait for their death. When the space storm arrives, all the people will be completely killed.

Sss!

A black round ball suddenly expanded right in front of Garen. The intense aura of the Void Battlefield was filling the air.

Garen turned around one last time to look at this chaotic planet. More and more black clouds gathered in the sky and the ink of the space storm frenziedly dyed the surface of the planet. It gradually pierced through the atmospheric layer and the magnetic field of the earth. It was as though devils were being released, rushing straight down onto the ground.

“This could be the end of the world mentioned in the fairy tales…” Garen knew that other experts might have their own means to escape. However, those below the Non-Falling Level will be in trouble. In the end, he was not able to prevent the destruction of the planet. Nonetheless, he had achieved two of his targets. The two Holy Lords who were supposed to die in the original overall trend were still alive. Moreover, there was not supposed to have that many Perpetual Motioners. There were so many of them now and they will be able to divert the attention of the pilots. This will increase the chances of survival for Scarlet Snow Sect.

He took one last look at this prosperous, urban planet.

“Goodbye, Planet Naga.”

He stepped into the black round ball. After a burst of rainbow flares, Garen’s body was frozen.

The first thing that he saw right after he regained his sight was not the deserted plains of the void battlefield. Instead, he saw a gorgeous, white towering palace. The figure of a young man dressed in white had his back facing him. He stood by the fencing around the palace while he overlooked the scenery outside.

“Welcome, the Destiny Destroyer.”

The young man dressed in white turned around with a gentle and pure smile on his face.

“White King…” Garen’s pupils constricted instantly.

Chapter 1135: Confinement 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s skin instantly tightened. An extremely great sense of threat gushed out of the soul seed inside his mind. How could it be!!? What happened!?

He should have gone straight to the void battlefield! The people of the Scarlet Snow Sect were waiting for him there. How did he teleport to the White King’s headquarters in the North Pole!??

He could not understand what was happening. His mind was a mess and he was caught off guard by the sudden dramatic change.

The White King! He was the terrifying being that dominated more than half of the galaxy! He was the best of the Regent Level!

Garen was just an ordinary Level Ten Perpetual Motioner! It would be as easy as killing an ant if the White King wanted to kill him.

The gap between the both of them was too big. It was utterly incomparable!

Garen tried very hard to calm himself down. However, he could not stop his heart from beating rapidly.

“According to what you’ve gone through, all the sudden changes and climaxes, coupled with my judgment, 25 percent of your real name is Nonosiva, 6.2 percent is Jeros, and above 60 percent is Garen.” The White King looked like an ordinary young lad with a very pure smile. His skin was delicate, like a good milk-flavored jelly. His serene eyes seemed to be smiling. It felt as though he was smiling constantly.

“Am I right?”

Garen’s heart tightened once again.

“What… do you want to do?” It was the first time that he felt his voice was so hoarse.

Even though the White King had not reached his prime yet, he was still far from someone who Garen can compete against.

“You’re not the only one who saw Destiny…” The White King answered in a low voice, while still smiling.

The entire white palace was surrounded by an endless amount of nebula vortex. A large number of meteorites were revolving around the palace at a high speed. This place was like the Eye of The Storm. It was extremely violent on the outside but peaceful on the inside. He could tell that this was the center of a huge meteorite whirlpool. However, he did not know he was located in which part of space. Being isolated by an endless amount of powerful whirlpools, this place was like a different world. An average expert will not even be qualified to enter this place.

“Everything in the world has a definite number. You and I are also involved in it. Many years later, I will be killed by the Red King, even though he will become my only bosom friend in the future. However, that is fate.” The White King lifted his head to look at the rotating meteorite flow. One after another huge gray meteorite flew across the top of his head with a tremendous sense of oppression. It seemed as though it might hit on this palace any time.

After Garen realized that the White King did not seem to have any plans on making a move, he relaxed slightly.

“If you knew that you will die in the future, why not make a move in advance?”

“That is my destiny…” The White King revealed a pure smile. “I was born to follow my destiny.”

Garen knew the dream of the White King. He wanted the world to be free from struggles and war.

Since he had seen the overall trend, he would have understood that after the Red King killed him, the human race will unite. After that, there will be an unprecedented prosperity and peace which will last for a very long period of time…

“Since I’m disobeying destiny, how are you going to deal with me?” Garen asked calmly.

“Initially, I was going to kill you.” The White King said softly. “However, after seeing you, I am hesitant.”

“You’re hesitating?” Garen secretly sighed in relief. “Why?” Nobody would want to die if they were given a chance to stay alive.

In fact, he did not agree to the ideals of the White King. The Universe and the Milky Way were way too big. All the Finite People along with the human race only occupied two nebulae. All of them only ruled tens of thousands of habitable planets and hundreds of thousands of inhabitable planets.

That looked like a huge number. However, compared to the size of the hundreds of billions of stars and countless nebulae in the Milky Way, it was like a small crevice at the side of a pond.

They had already discovered hundreds of billions of galaxies about the size of the Milky Way in the Universe. Each one of them had hundreds of billions of solar systems. It was a terrifyingly huge scale, let alone those that have yet to be discovered. Moreover, there might be another Universe other than this Universe.

In a mere human-mech civilization, a regent level expert who was able to destroy a planet was just as common as a drop of water in the vast sea.

Either way, he still respected the White King for going as far as becoming a martyr just for his dream.

“That is because you’re not the same as what I thought you would be…” The White King said gently. “I’m a rational man. You’re destined to die in the hands of Chinande, so you shouldn’t be killed by me.”

“Didn’t you choose to resist your destiny?” Garen asked. “Why did you accept it now?” He tried to start a new topic, but he involuntarily brought that up.

After hearing what he said, the White King shook his head.

“Since destiny is going towards the overall trend that I long for, why should I change it?” He replied with a smile.

He stopped looking at Garen and walked towards the stone steps leading to the Palace Square and started to walk down the steps.

Garen looked around him. It was utterly deserted and empty. There were vague traces on the ground from the aftermath of a battle. The entire place was filled with dents and openings.

He glanced at the White King, who walked further and further away. Then, he chose to keep up with him.

On the long stone steps of the white palace, the both of them were like two small dots which slowly moved downwards one after the other.

After they walked to the bottom of the stone stairs, the White King walked to a blood-colored gravestone that stood on the ground obliquely. He stood still and reached out his hands to gently touch the texture of the gravestone as if he was caressing his lover.

Stopping behind him, Garen frowned looking at him. He did not know what the White King was planning to do.

“You know what?” The White King suddenly said.

“?”

Garen stared at him quietly and waited for him to continue.

“I twisted destiny with my own hands so that it is how it is now…” The White King said calmly.

“What are you planning to do by catching me here?!” Garen frowned and said in a low voice.

“Have you heard of a saying?” The White King turned around and smiled. “One day in Heaven is one year on Earth…”

He lifted his finger and sparkles of gold shimmer lighted upon his fingertips.

As the faint light scattered, Garen found that anything below his legs was frozen on the ground.

It was not a block of ice that froze him, but an extremely clear, dark gold crystal.

Crack…

The dark gold crystals grew slowly and crawled up to Garen’s legs as if they were living organism. It continued to spread out to other regions. It absorbed the cold air that released naturally from Garen’s body and became powerful rapidly.

“This is!!?” Garen tried to move his legs, but the power of the crystals was extremely strong. “Gold Void Crystals…! The strongest confinement substances?”

This idea flashed through his mind. Garen soon felt his body losing control. The more he struggled, the faster the dark gold crystals spread. Soon, it covered his chest and was about to trap his throat.

Icy cold…

Ever since Garen learned the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, it was the first time that he felt cold.

A piercing icy cold chill constantly tried to penetrate to the deep parts of his skin and bones.

Chi!!

The shadow of the Hellfrost Peacock struggled and wailed behind Garen. Then, it let out a final scream. Numerous white ice crystal vines tried to spread behind Garen and form a giant ice net to assist him.

However, nothing can act as a leverage in the void.

“Do you know that?” The White King lifted a finger once again. “A lot of people address me as the Absolute Distortion…”

The dark gold shimmer disappeared.

Boom!!

All the ice crystal vines shattered. It turned into countless white light spots and gradually fell onto the ground.

Garen was completely sealed in the dark gold crystal. He was not able to move and all he could do was stare at the White King with his eyes wide open. The terrifying force field around his body constantly tried to condense. However, it was being disrupted by an odd distortive power. Each time his force field tried to condense, it will be broken up.

Even the power of his soul seed was completely destroyed by his distortive power. Everything inside Garen was in a mess.

“Distortion… this was an absolute concept! As long as you’re within this area, all the living things will only have one concept, and that is distortion…” The White King explained quietly. “Without your own concept, it will be pointless no matter how you struggle.”

As usual, he had a pure smile on his face.

“You shall stay here and quietly wait for the arrival of your destiny…”

He turned around and slowly walked towards the upper part of the white palace. His figure gradually went further. He slowly disappeared in the stone steps and he was nowhere to be seen.

Garen looked at the direction where the White King left through the crystal. Only until he completely left, his distortive power weakened slightly.

“Distortion, huh?”

He tried to condense the Hellfrost Peacock Technique to restore its body. However, the Living Secret Technique could not absorb the void power from outside through the crystal. There was a huge devouring force that continuously absorbed the chill air from his body.

Along with the devouring power, the massive accumulation of chill air on Garen’s body was declining rapidly.

Pop!

A blue silk string that was trying to reach out from his palm immediately exploded and broke.

“This is troublesome…!” Garen’s heart sank as he felt like he might be in danger. “The devouring power is not that strong. It’s considered weak compared to mine. However, because of this distortive power, I am unable to condense my devouring power!!”

At the moment, he had confirmed that the White King had no intention of killing him. However, because he was stronger than the White King had expected, he might change the overall trend. Therefore, he was being confined here to wait for his inevitable future.

“If the White King did not lie to me… then this should be a place with an unlimited fold of gravitational force… the gravitational force here can even distort and change the flow of time. The so-called one day in Heaven is one year on Earth… So he was planning to do this…”

Garen seemed to have understood the White King’s plan.

At that moment, he looked outside through the crystal. The meteorites on the sky seemed to have moved faster and it was gradually speeding up.

Suddenly, several streams of light descended from the sky and headed directly towards the white stone steps. Soon, it arrived at the stone steps and flew towards the surrounding meteorites.

There were white and blue streams of light. It seemed as though there were shadows among it. However, it was impossible for Garen to see clearly with his vision.

The stones on the ground around the crystal started cracking and gradually became smaller. Finally, it turned into sand particles and condensed into the soil under the moist water vapor.

Boom!

Shooting stars of various sizes fell from the sky. The larger shooting stars repeated the process once again and turned into soil.

Gradually, Garen felt that the soil around the crystal was getting higher and greater. It rose up from the bottom of the crystal and quickly reached his waist, almost drowning half of his body.

After seeing all these changes, Garen finally realized something.

“As expected, he even distorted time…”

He felt as if only a few hours had passed through the crystal. However, it seemed as though a long time had gone by outside of the crystal…

Chapter 1136: Confinement 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Time ticked away… Garen could feel his strength weakening.

He was quickly drained from Level Ten and soon reached Level Nine…

Level Nine was also rapidly absorbed and directly dropped to Level Eight…and Level Eight was rapidly weakening.

“This is his purpose?” Garen calmly pondered the countermeasures. “If it weren’t for that distortive power which interfered with my condensing strength, how could this devouring force be compared to mine?”

Level Eight quickly weakened and the time on the outside world flew by swiftly.

Garen finally fell back to Level Seven.

“Am I going to bow out this way!?” Garen was starting to get anxious. Watching one’s own strength declining rapidly, anybody would become increasingly restless too.

He was not afraid of death, but he could not resign himself to it!! Being inexplicably confined by the White King, not accomplishing anything yet, and being deterred before he could truly unleash the powerful strength he had, this indescribable feeling of grievance and repression made Garen even more dissatisfied.

“Stay calm…only by staying calm can I find a way!” Garen forced himself to calm down and carefully looked for possible ways to break through.

Hiss…

While in reverie, Garen suddenly realized that the dark golden crystal around him was actually slowly releasing a subtle hissing sound.

Not knowing when did it started, traces of dark golden airstream began to flow inside the crystal.

As time went by, the airstream in the crystal began to gradually condense, forming a fuzzy misty mass like a snake.

“This is?” Garen was stunned.

Hiss hiss…

The serpentine air mass twisted its body and became clearer, swimming slowly in the dark golden crystal.

A faintly familiar yet unfamiliar aura rose from the body of the snake and spread into Garen’s Soul Seed Ring. It immediately caused subtle waves of ripples.

“This is…Void Creature!!” Garen suddenly recalled the essence of this aura.

*******************

The outside world

One hundred and fifty years later…

In a red desert, a white figure walked slowly and steadily on the sand, leaving a deep footprint and another shallow footprint. The figure held a long crutch in his hand. He was barefooted, exposing his dry and darkened instep skin.

A slender curvy shadow constantly moved around his feet and slowly swam in the sand. Even though the sun in the sky was bright and hot, one could only see the fuzzy outline of the shadow. It was a rope-like thing.

“The Energy Machinists have been extinct for more than a hundred years! Why is the environment still this bad? Didn’t they say the root cause of the environmental pollution has been resolved? This group of warmongers who only knows how to bluff!”

The figure raised his head, revealing a dry, dark, old face.

Some parts of his cheeks were scorched, leaving some white patches of skin as if they had been smeared with flour.

After complaining a few sentences, he lowered his head and touched the black rope below. The rope was also very cooperative, willingly raised what was considered as the head for him to caress.

“Such a good child. Come on, help your dad to see where to find water next!” The old man was talking to the rope like a pet.

The rope actually seemed to understand him. It circled the ground, raised its head and began to shake it for some unknown purposes.

Suddenly, a shadow flashed through in the sky, fleeting swiftly past the old man’s overhead.

Whoosh!

“Huh?” The old man lifted his head and looked puzzlingly above his head. There was nothing at all. “Looks like I’m so thirsty that I’m having auditory hallucination…”

He again lowered his head and stared at the snake-like dancing movement by the rope.

Whoosh!

Another dark shadow flashed past him, like a big bird zooming over his head.

The old man looked up sharply and still saw nothing.

“What the hell!!” He muttered.

Just when he lowered his head once more.

Whoosh!

Another dark shadow flashed by.

Almost instantaneously, he immediately looked up but was still a step slower. The sky was empty as if it was ridiculing him that his movements were too slow.

“Sh*t!”

He cursed and bowed his head.

Whoosh!

This time, he looked up instantly and there was nothing at all in the sky but blueness. The hot and blazing golden sun made people unable to open their eyes.

Lowering his head.

“Ha!” He immediately looked up again but nothing flashed by. “Could it be that I really have an illusion?” He touched his face and gave up wasting time here. He looked down at the rope.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh whoosh!!!

In an instant, countless dark shadows flashed past overhead.

The old man and the rope were startled and he flopped down onto the hot sand, looking up quickly. But all he saw were countless black silhouettes like that of big birds fleeting with lightning speed above him.

“You can’t run away, Clint Beza!!” A cold woman’s voice came down from the sky.

“No one can stop me from going anywhere in the Milky Way!!” Another arrogant man’s voice sounded throughout the sky.

“After robbing my Scarlet Mourning Hall’s treasure, you still dare to come back to Mars. I really don’t know if you are conceited or stupid!” The woman’s voice teased. “Perhaps you really thought that Baylon would come to your aid? Just give up. The two great Spirit Officers from my Scarlet Mourning Hall had already gone ahead to intercept and finish her off. Even the Almighty Woman, Baylon, is not likely to come back alive!”

“What a joke! Do I still need reinforcement? Is there something wrong with your brain or are you having a brain fart?! Do you speak without observing the situation?”

The sky was suddenly clear. All the dark shadows stopped instantly. One of the dark shadows removed its hood, revealing a young man’s handsome face. Behind him was a vaguely transparent stream of transparent particles. It was this stream of particles which helped him to achieve a high-speed flight.

Opposite the man was five women’s figures, headed by a splendid blond with blue eyes. She held a large, silver-white laser cannon in her hand, her stony face was full of murderous intention.

“Stupid Martians!” The man opened his mouth and lambasted. His savage expression made people want to beat him up. “Put down your weapons and surrender! You have been surrounded by me!!”

The man wrapped his arms around himself made a confident posture.

This immediately caused the five people on the opposite to react as if they were confronted by a great enemy. They became alert and observed the surroundings, carefully watching out for the dangers which could arise around them.

The hot wind was still ravaging. There was nothing but silence in the desert.

The expression on the man’s face seemed to be not able to hold it out anymore. His face twitched a few times and he quickly glanced around. Still unable to see his ambushing companion, he immediately panicked.

“Another empty threat?!” The blonde-haired blue-eyed woman glanced around and when she did not find any threats, she immediately settled down. “Did the ambush you mention referred to that good-for-nothing on the ground?”

She moved her arm.

Zzzz!

A thick white laser was suddenly shot downward.

It was aimed at the black thin old man who had slumped to the ground in fear.

Such laser cannon caliber was enough to melt several meters of alloy steel plate in seconds with just a simple shot. How could an ordinary desert traveler resist such a large-scale sophisticated weapon?

The old man only felt a white radiance on top of his head. In a trice, there was an intense barbecue-like heat coming down on him from the head to the toe.

Zzzz…!

Only then did the prolonged laser sound slowly drift over.

“Killing the innocent indiscriminately, die!” At the same moment, a cold female voice rang out in the man’s ear.

“Unparalleled Sword.”

The expected hot scalding did not come. Instead, it was an icy coldness which was so cold that it could cut through the heart.

A beautiful woman dressed in white stood in front of the man. She held the sword in one hand and blocked the lasers completely. Numerous white spots of light were continuously sliced and shattered, turning into solid-like ice cubes and falling to the ground.

“Peacock!” The woman’s voice was also cold and filled with a killing intention.

Zzzz Zzzz Zzzz Zzzz…!

Four consecutive slicing sounds like that of a lightning.

The figure of the woman with a ponytail had leaped up high and landed on another spot on the sand.

“You!!” The blond-haired blue-eyed woman in the sky shuddered as she stared at the woman on the ground. “Almighty Woman!! The two Spirit Officers couldn’t even…”

Pooh!

A blood hole suddenly opened up at the throat of the four figures behind her. They crashed to the ground like fluttering black butterflies, splashing broken bits of sand waves.

“Spirit Officer?” The ponytail woman lifted her icy and pretty face and opened her hand. There were two blood-stained delicate scarlet rings in her palm. “Do you mean this?”

Without any hesitation, the blonde spun around and fled. Her figure turned into a dark shadow and flew towards the distant with lightning speed.

“Unparalleled Sword…” The ponytail woman once again raised her rapier. “Die!”

A silver-white sword-light twisted and caught up with the opponent, penetrating the blonde woman’s back without any hindrance and exiting from the chest, bringing out a large bloody shower. Only then did it quickly flew back into the ponytail woman’s sword.

“I’m becoming less than you…” Clint came to the woman’s side with a look of pain in his face.

“Let’s go.” The ponytail woman ignored him, kept her sword and was ready to leave.

Clint looked at her back and felt helpless.

“Since the death of Big Brother, you have been constantly like this. It’s been so many years, can’t you let it go? Energy Machinists have been extinct for more than a hundred years. We will definitely take revenge for Big Brother, but you…”

“I’m different from you.” The ponytail woman stopped in her tracks, but she did not turn around. “You do not understand.”

“Baylon.”

Clint looked at the other party’s original black hair which was already mixed with some white color. As a powerful pilot who had integrated with one’s Mech, white hair was already appearing in just a hundred or so of age. One could imagine how much pain the other party was in. How did she live through this past hundred years? Perhaps only she herself knew.

“Sacrificing life in exchange for power, is it really worth it?”

“I think it’s worth it.” Baylon did not look back and walked away.

With her family gone, she could still look up to her older brother. Now that her older brother was gone, there was no one else to depend on. When she first received the news, it was such a huge blow to Baylon that she went berserk.

From the outbreak of his terrific strength in Scarlet Snow Sect to older brother changing his name to Garen, leading Scarlet Snow into the highest level and bringing the people of Scarlet Snow to flee, when she finally received the grievous news and that Scarlet Snow was mourning for him, all of Baylon’s pillars instantly collapsed.

In this world, her last family member had also died. He had died in the conspiracy of White King. After waking up, what had left in her heart was only an endless hatred –a hatred towards White King!

Chapter 1137: Variable 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Nebula border, Public Galaxy R-Wasteland.

In the dull cosmos, everything was dark. Only Public Galaxy’s sole star, Evallier, was still emitting a soft gigantic golden glow.

Whoosh!

Suddenly in the void, there appeared a circular ring made up of metal sheets. Each metal sheet was a few kilometers long and resembled a sharp bone spur. They were arranged together and continuously rotating, forming a huge dozens-of-kilometers ring.

In the silence, a transparent distortion emerged in the middle of the ring.

Hiss…

A disk-shaped grey-black spaceship slowly emerged from the middle.

The spaceship was like a black mushroom with a dense array of folds on its surface and had a metal statue of an old man in a robe erected on the top. At this moment, the eyes of the statue were clearly shining a white light. They were like a searchlight, illuminating the surrounding environment one by one.

On the side of the spaceship, in a scallop-type window among the numerous folds, one could see two bald-headed man and woman standing shoulder to shoulder, quietly watching everything on the outside world.

Both of them looked indifferent and solemn from the windows. Their heads were bare and a few pieces of silver metal were implanted on it, giving off the sense of a Modified Human and Robotic Human.

“Is there any news from Finite that side? Evan.” The bald man looked out of the window and asked solemnly.

“What news do you want?” The bald woman Evan wrapped her arms around her chest. A silver metal antenna extended from the back of her head. The bottom of the antenna continually spread out blue electric arcs to the top.

It seemed that her body was constantly generating electric arcs and passing them out through the antenna.

“The General Military Department has sent two legions out. Only one legion is left behind to safeguard the entire Human Race. Prince Thunderbird from Finite’s side will definitely not let go of this opportunity easily. Once there is an accident on the eastern battlefield, the entire Human Race is likely to lose power. We must be extra careful.” The man spoke in a low voice.

“Now, it’s impossible for Thunderbird to free up his forces to deal with this side. Only three of the Twelve Golden Merit Blue Princes are guarding the headquarters. Are they not afraid of our counterattack?” Evan was perplexed.

“Of course they are. But…do you think they will come to attack us by surprise?” The man asked in reply.

“This…is unlikely…” Evan shook her head.

The man suddenly laughed.

“See? Even you don’t think so. If they act in reverse, then the risk of danger is very high…”

“But we have Sky Fortress.” Evan argued, “We can combine our strengths that are above the Non-Falling Level as one. Even if they come, they won’t be able to break through easily.”

The man shook his head.

“How many Non-Falling Levels are there? The individual’s strength is not too important now unless the Regent Level personally move in. If I were Chinande, I will come here the first moment to get hold of the key loophole at any time. So long as once a little gap is gotten hold of, then even though we are just a minor clash by the edge, it will still have an extremely serious effect on the overall situation.”

He then looked at the outside world again.

“Alright. When we reach the destination, call up White Winter and the others. We should go and check it out. We must be swift, make it a quick battle. We will return immediately after positioning the jump.”

“Understand.” Evan gave a salute, turned about and left quickly.

A few moments later, on the mushroom-shaped gray-black fortress, several black triangular metal spaceships flew straight to the Public Galaxy’s only star, Evallier.

It had been more than a hundred years since the Energy Machinist Extinction. The world was not completely without any Energy Machinists, but as most of the Energy Machinists had lost their legacy due to their levels being too low, they had lost the original powerful strength and became purely auxiliary logistics units.

The Energy Machinist Sect only existed in the legends and was called the Ancient Energizers, in order to distinguish the current occupation of Energy Machinists. One hundred plus of years was not a long time to the powerhouses. However, to the ordinary people, it was already equivalent to much of their life or a lifetime. The legend of Energy Machinist very soon faded as the years passed.

After White King defeated the Wraith Monarch and exterminated the Wraith Royalty, it took only a few years for him to unify the entire Finite, thus aiming his spearhead at mankind, who was on the opposite side.

The real confrontation between the Mother Planet and Finite people finally broke out.

Among the nine great Royal Star Forces, the most powerful Thousand Pillar King led the other eight Regent-Level mankind to form a formal strategic alliance and jointly fight against Finite’s White King’s wild ambition.

Throughout these more-than-one-hundred years, Thousand Pillar King and Mo Luo and Mo Guang the two top Regent Levels spearheaded and led the Three Armies in a direct confrontation with Finite’s Twelve Golden Merit Blue Princes. Both sides suffered casualties.

White King had personally fought for several times but was resisted by the Star Emperors using the Sky Fortress, which was a unique Willpower joint installation. This technology was learned and invented from the data in the hands of the Energy Machinists back then.

Mankind, whose origin was from Mother Planet, had similar Willpower features. It was like the gene. There were always many common points in the gene strand.

Finite was different. There were the universal unified ethnic, made up of hundreds of different universal ethnics. The composition was complex. Even if this technology was available to them, they could not apply it too.

In this way, mankind had Sky Fortress, this kind of joint installation; whereas, the overall strength of the Finite people was much stronger. After the high-level forces from both sides confronted each other in the Inverse Space for a while, no one was able to bring harm to the other party and things had to be halted temporarily.

After the strategic level of attack and defense had stagnated, the crucial point lied in the stealth warfare which was similar to the boiling frog syndrome.

War, to a certain extent, was the fight of resources and economy, so the great conflict between the two key communities, which was the conflict of resources, resurfaced once again and became the confrontation point of a new round of war.

Now, the human army fleet, which had always holed up, took the initiative to attack because it discovered a brand new gaseous mineral planet. Once this planet was occupied, mankind’s increasingly stricken energy crisis would be temporarily alleviated.

For this reason, the scientists had also named the planet as the Lord of Hope – Cameron.

And now, this mushroom-like spaceship was headed toward the Cameron Star, which was located in Public Galaxy.

The news had not spread yet. The Finite people did not yet know that this planet was a rare gaseous mineral planet. The entire planet was full of various types of mineral dust and gas which could be utilized. This was also the key opportunity for the Human Race.

Therefore, the two legions positioned a similar planet and pretended to occupy it, but the real team that would occupy the planet was secretly moving in.

The mushroom spaceship slowly went forward. It released several small insect-like flying ships that flew silently toward Public Galaxy. A huge khaki-colored planet over there was spinning slowly, and a huge yellow star ring was suspended at its waist.

“It’s here! Found it! Haha!!” One of the small flying ships spread out an ecstatic voice. “It is it! Cameron! Hahaha!!” The mad laughter continued.

“Immediately determine its position. Prepare to extract samples!”

“The collection knife is ready. Begin.”

Two small flying ships quickly approached the khaki-colored planet. They jumped halfway and quickly crossed a large distance, immediately appearing at the edge of the star ring. They extended their robotic arm and began to collect samples.

At the same time, a swarm of mechanical bees was densely dispersed. They flew in all directions to detect the surrounding movement at any time.

The khaki-colored planet rotated slowly as if it had been slowly rotating as such since numerous years ago. The enormous volume was comparable to a star not far away. It was totally unknown why it was confined by the star’s gravitational pull to revolve around it.

As the robotic arms began collecting, a strange aura gradually diffused all over Cameron Star.

Above the planet, endless khaki-colored storms raged wildly, and the black spots in it were like fruits hanging in the storm. They were extremely dark and were floating in the void.

Pooh.

Suddenly, a black spot exploded and transformed into a dark small hole. It began to devour the surrounding khaki-colored airstream.

Very soon, a beetle full of compound eyes on its entire body climbed out of the black hole. It lifted its head to raise its ferocious mouthparts and looked into the sky, which seemed to be just in the direction of the acquisition flying ships.

Hiss hiss…

The subtle cry began to travel through the storm.

It was a huge variable which no one had expected. It seemed that it was finally triggered due to an unknown reason…

**********************

White King’s Central Palace.

Garen could not remember how long it had been.

Since he was confined in the crystal, everything in the outside world had become extremely fast. But as time went by, the distortive power finally began to weaken.

The distorted time was also finally beginning to return to normal again.

Garen’s concept of time was also turned around again. However, although the distortive power no longer distorted the time, his body was still firmly confined. There was no possibility for the slightest struggle.

His current strength had been confined and devoured, reducing to Level Seven, the Non-Falling Level. This seemed to be the limit, a point set by White King.

Garen knew that he hoped he would die in the hands of Chinande in a way that was consistent with history. The time was coming soon. Everything was just waiting for the Battle of Ice Age to break out. That was the time when he would officially meet his death.

Through the dark golden crystal, Garen vaguely saw that the outside world had accumulated a lot of dust and sand, almost completely burying this Void Crystal of his. Only a glimmer of light vaguely shone from the overhead.

“Snake, come here.” Garen transmitted the voice from his mind.

Soon, a dark golden snake slowly condensed from the crystal. It wriggled its body and slowly crawled to the front of Garen. The Confining Crystal seemed to have no effect on it.

Hiss hiss…the little snake made a slight hissing sound as if asking what was up.

“How much dark energy have you absorbed?” Garen asked bluntly. An aura of the Void Creature, Hellfrost Peacock, was exuded from his body and stirred in the crystal. That immediately made the little snake felt warm and happily spun a few rounds in the atmosphere.

It generously gaped open its mouth and spit.

Hiss…

Large plumes of ink-like dark energy quickly spread within the entire crystal. Only a small part of it came into contact with Garen and was absorbed by the Devourer Ability in his passive body. The other part was wasted and dispersed throughout the crystal, making the crystal stronger and more horrifying.

Chapter 1138: Variable 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen seemed to have accustomed to this kind of life. After absorbing the dark energy, he once again converted it to pure Cold Energy and released it as plumes of substantial white airstream.

The little snake cheered and rushed over with hissing sounds. It absorbed in a trice all the white Cold Energy released.

After being refined by Garen, although the Cold Energy was not the most suitable type of energy for the little snake, but compared to the dark energy which contained many impurities, this high-condensation-purity energy suited its appetite more and was more suitable for its growth.

In its opinion, this big guy in the crystal who could not move was its own mother and friend. This kind of dependency started from a long time ago.

More than a hundred years’ time was just three months plus at Garen’s place. Both the human and the snake had gotten along this way for two months plus.

“You want more?” Garen was amused by the little snake’s discontented expression. “Then go and absorb more dark energy…more than seventy percent of the universe is dark energy. It’s infinite. Only you can absorb, collect and condense it into an actual substance.”

Although he knew that this fellow could not understand him, but Garen still transmitted his voice out of habit. When a person was bored, he or she would definitely find ways to kill time.

The Cold Energy he released was actually only ten percent of the total amount. But even with this, it was enough for the snake to gladly toil for it.

Watching the snake slowly disintegrated and disappeared into the crystal, Garen’s heart was calm.

“White King…perhaps you did not expect it too. In the Void dark golden crystal, there actually was the existence of a Void Creature’s egg. And it was not an ordinary egg, but the egg of Dark Shadow Dragon, a void giant beast that ranked even higher than Hellfrost Peacock Queen…”

Even the Dark Shadow Dragon in its infancy would reach the standard of hatching and hatch out after devouring a large amount of Garen’s body strength. It had the inherent ability to absorb dark energy.

As the third mighty existence in the ranking of Ancient Endor Void Creatures, the Dark Shadow Dragon was also known as the Dark Spirit Dragon, the Dark Night Dragon, the Lord of the Night and so on.

Although this Dark Shadow Dragon was still very small, if it was not for Garen’s power to incubate it, perhaps it would have died in the crystal and become a fossil after thousands of years. Even if it hatched now, this little dragon might also encounter many terrifying creatures’ attacks and dangers in the process of growing up.

The current little dragon had little ability, but it had been a very important help to Garen.

It could provide Garen with very little but extraordinarily precious energy from the outside.

Garen’s power was confined by the distortive power and could not be used. The crystal had also sealed the path for him to devour and absorb energy from the outside world. He could only rely on this young little Dark Shadow Dragon by continually encouraging it to go out and absorb dark energy in exchange for a strand of the extremely little Cold Energy in his body.

The Cold Energy released could quickly stimulate the growth of the Dark Shadow Dragon, allowing it to absorb more and darker energy.

Whew…

Garen let out a breath slowly. That was the pure Cold Energy converting into a trace of white mist. It moved difficultly and slowly in the crystal.

By observing the way the Dark Shadow Dragon moved, Garen had already vaguely understood the basic principle of this crystal confinement. Letting go of the little snake’s help, he himself gave impetus to the Cold Energy to move inside the crystal. This was the little of what he had achieved thus far.

“What is the essence of confinement actually…” Garen was immersed in his thoughts. All this time, he was constantly reflecting and observing the movement of the Dark Shadow Dragon, in order to try to comprehend the most critical hurdle between Level Ten and Regent Level.

That is the concept of essence.

This could not be grasped easily grasped. But as time was distorted by the distortive power, Garen could also feel that his thinking speed had become abnormally rapid and horrific. This peculiar phenomenon seemed to be caused by the acceleration of time. Each of his ideas could almost get a rapid answer. After all, every second here was equivalent to a long time on the outside world. This kind of thinking speed was also normal.

The most crucial part was that the essence of the Void Crystal was actually the Void Creature’s Crystal Core. Moreover, the toughest dark golden crystal was, in fact, the most powerful Void Creature Crystal Core. And it just so happened that one of Garen’s own identities came in handy at this time.

— Void Pursuer.

He was the inheritor of the Ancient Endor civilization and was a powerful hunter who was responsible for hunting and killing Void Creatures. The biggest advantage of this identity was that he could use the Void Crystals, which could not be used by others, to turn it into a powerful driving force for the analysis and deduction of his mind.

Back then in the Blood Breed World, Garen used the Void Crystal Core to deduce the study of martial arts. Now that his whole body was encased in this dark golden Void Crystal Core, which was the Void Creatures’ strongest crystal core and the probably-ranked-third Dark Shadow Dragon’s crystal core, to Garen, this represented an almost endless resource for analysis.

At this moment, there was the best concept demonstrator – the young Dark Shadow Dragon. It inherently possessed the essence of the concept of confinement. This crystal was actually its best protective shell, which was equivalent to an eggshell. It was extremely rigid and capable of confining almost everything in the world.

There was also the best energy reserve for after exhaustion – Void Crystal.

In addition to the acceleration of time with the help of the distortive power, apart from Garen’s strength dropping at such a significant rate, he really had a unique and excellent secluded environment for cultivation.

“To get out of the confinement, I must first understand the essence of it.” Garen’s mind was spinning slowly. The three Soul Seeds were constantly rotating and releasing traces of the Soul’s Strength. Although the maximum effect could not be achieved due to the distortive power, he was no longer completely immobile as before.

Closing his eyes slowly, Garen immersed in his thoughts gradually. Every possible analysis was gradually screened out; every terrifically complex computation and inferences were negated one by one; various new possibilities were established repeatedly. New models would continue to be produced and collapsed.

At this moment, Garen’s computing power had reached an extremely horrific level.

Suddenly, a thought rolled out in his mind.

“My Cold Energy has the Hellfrost Peacock’s most terrifying and pure chill, but the Dark Shadow Dragon was not afraid of it at all, and even toiled for it gladly…is it just because the Dark Shadow Dragon is ranked above the Hellfrost Peacock Queen?”

Various new possibilities once again came into his mind.

“If, say, a huge distortion or the most extreme distortion fluctuation could speed up the flow of time, then can complete quiescence, which is making all forces completely quiescent, produce absolute confinement?”

“And in reverse, can absolute confinement produce absolute quiescence? Including the quiescence of time and space?” Garen’s heart skipped a beat.

After deducing for so long and attempting to grasp all this while, the result was very minimal. But at this moment, the reversed idea which suddenly popped up caused him to faintly have an idea.

“My Cold Energy can reduce the movement of matter, and it is infinitely close to quiescence, but it cannot really freeze the energy field. All matters are brought together and condensed due to the energy field. It is the balance between the forces of atoms which forms the structure of matter. If I can freeze the energy field, then the matter will cease to exist because of the energy field, but that it will exist due to my freezing. This…is no longer the scope which could be affected by temperature…”

Garen continued to generate new thoughts and ideas.

Looking at the sturdy dark crystal around him, he suddenly had an extremely crazy and bold idea.

“For me, this crystal plays two roles at the same time. First, the essence of the Void Crystal Core is accelerating my thinking speed. Second, its conceptual essence is confining all my activities. However, this confinement did not reach the point where it affects my soul’s thinking. From this point of view, his concept of confinement is weaker than the concept of accelerated analysis. Perhaps it can be understood that his confinement cannot restrict the accelerating ability granted to me by Mother Stream due to my identity as a Void Pursuer. If all goes well, this should be the distinguishing of the level between the essences of concepts.”

“Void Pursuers use crystal cores to accelerate their thinking, which is a higher level than the Dark Shadow Dragon’s Confinement Power. Interesting…it is a little like the differentiating of the power levels in the myths.”

“If…I crazily strengthen this Confining Crystal and even cause it to reach the highest degree of confinement, will it really confine my consciousness?” A whirl of crazy thoughts sparked up in Garen’s mind.

“Will it naturally evolve into a balance due to the different concept levels, or will it completely raise the lower-level concept to a higher level?” A brand new model emerged faintly in Garen’s mind.

The possibility of this model was based on the speculation under his unique conditions.

If the model was unsuccessful, he might die thoroughly, not even leaving a Soul Seed behind. He would completely perish and be no more. But, if it was successful…

“So, how can we bring the crystal to the height of confining everything?” Garen turned to this question.

There was only one answer.

Dark Shadow Dragon…

Even though the Dark Shadow Dragon was a young dragon, it also had the special ability to shuttle between the Shadow World and the normal world. The shadow energy was actually the so-called dark energy. This was the most extensive force in the universe. And so, compared with the normal world, the Dark World was a more enormous and extensive place.

What maintained this shuttling capability was derived from a connecting core in the Dark Shadow Dragon itself. This core connected the Dark World and the normal Physical World both sides. As the Dark Shadow Dragon, its most fearful ability came from this core. Regardless of the infant body or mature body, they all have this ability.

That was self-detonation.

This was not a simple self-detonation, but it was to completely blast open the fragile balance in the connection core and to completely open the door of the Dark World to the Physical World.

Garen had read from the inherited knowledge memory of the Ancient Endor civilization that the innumerable Dark World terrifying creatures flocking into the Physical World, and the massive horrific dark energy rushing into the entire Physical Universe was the brief connection of the areas of two different worlds. The Dark World was much bigger than the Physical World. The creatures in it do not need light as they themselves were made up of dark matter. Seeing light was like water encountering fire and a cat spotting a rat. It was even more like humans seeing something which made them fearful; that kind of fearful thing which could destroy them all including life.

Under such fear and realizing the other party was much weaker than themselves, the end result was that they hysterically want to eliminate light forever.

“The Dark Shadow Dragon’s self-detonation should temporarily open the door of the Dark World, allowing the entire Dark World’s energy to strengthen this crystal core at the highest speed, completely pushing it to the apex. This crystal core was originally left behind by the Dark Shadow Dragon’s mature body. There should be no problem to return to its peak.”

After finalizing his plan, the only thing left was implementation…

There was a subtle, killing intention in Garen’s eyes.

“Snake, come out.”

He transmitted his voice gently.

Chapter 1139: Sublimation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The dark golden snake slowly drifted out and converged into a tiny body in the crystal.

Although it was still a Dark Shadow Dragon in its infancy, it already had some fine black scales and a series of slender, long dragon whiskers on its back. The long, black dragon whiskers were like its hair and they slowly undulated in the crystal.

The young Dark Shadow Dragon at this moment had a faint reflection of a dragon and was no longer the form of an ordinary snake.

“Come to me…” Garen exuded a slight aura of goodwill and chill. The Cold Energy he absorbed earlier was once again released by him, covering the surface of his body.

The young dragon was truly attracted and slithered over hurriedly. The slender body wound one round like a snake and its head leaned against Garen in an affectionate manner. It stuck out its tongue and licked the back of Garen’s hand.

Hiss hiss.

It began to carefully devour the Cold Energy as if eating the best grade of food.

Garen watched it tenderly, constantly emitting his accumulated Cold Energy, letting it devour continuously.

Apart from being able to slither in the shadows, the young Dark Shadow Dragon’s lethality was in effect not even up to that of a poisonous snake. The only harm it could bring about was the self-detonation of the demarcation point of the two worlds in its body. That was the core which was connected to the Dark World.

Now, its most dangerous means of protection had become a real deadly threat.

The invisible Cold Energy continued to spread into the young Dark Shadow Dragon’s body.

A faint red light gradually appeared in Garen’s eyes and the blood-red glow in them shone onto the young dragon. An extremely sharp chill was released slowly and invaded the young dragon’s body.

The red light transformed into a big hand and gently stroked the young dragon. The touch was extremely soothing and soft, without any malicious intentions.

The young dragon also let out a comfortable moan, almost closing its eyes in comfort.

Suddenly, Garen increased his strength. The strength formed by his Willpower Field instantly seized the young dragon so that it could not escape from his control.

Hiss!!

The young Dark Shadow Dragon was pinched by the huge force field strength, and it struggled in desperation, shrieking frantically.

However, its weak strength simply could not resist Garen who still had the power of a Non-Falling Level. Even the little power Garen had accumulated during this period of time was enough to kill the little things that were not hidden in the shadows.

The young dragon whined and struggled. Both its eyes were swelling and bulging. Its slender black body was pinched by the energy field in the air, which was getting increasingly tighter and stronger. Numerous black smokes discharged from its body and spread out into the surrounding.

What Garen radiated from his eyes was not only a glaring red light but also a cold killing intention.

He watched quietly as the young dragon struggled and pleaded for its life.

Boom!

The young dragon finally could no longer withstand it and exploded right away, turning into a cloud of black smoke and floated before Garen in the crystal.

With a tear, a pale eye suddenly opened from within the black smoke, and the eyeball twitched nervously up, down, left and right.

Garen looked at the eyeball calmly, his mouth slightly curved up.

“Come on… All of Dark Shadow. I need your help…” He murmured.

The white eyeball arched forward slowly. It was impressively grown on top of the head of a pitch-black bird type of creature. The second this black bird with a white eyeball on its head flew out of the black smoke, the first thing it saw was the red light radiating from Garen’s eyes.

Caw!!

The Dark Shadow Blackbird immediately made an ear-piercing cry of horror. It seemed to be fearful, and it also seemed to be roaring. It darted at Garen’s eyes without any regard of its own safety, as if it would do its utmost to destroy everything relating to this red light.

But just as it was separated from the black fog, it was immediately restricted by the power of the crystal. This crystal was the strongest protective shell the Dark Shadow Dragon’s larva used to protect itself during its infancy. At the same time, it was also once the crystal core of some matured Dark Shadow Dragon. The speed and ability to absorb the dark energy were not something that could be resisted by a small Dark Shadow Bird.

Almost immediately when it thrust forward, the blackbird exploded directly, turning into a vast black fog and was absorbed by the crystal.

Boom bang!!

Almost at the same time the blackbird exploded, the black fog violently surged into a large stream of black torrent and rushed toward Garen. It seemed to want to destroy the only source of the red light in the crystal – Garen’s eyes.

Garen’s mouth gaped open, allowing the massive black torrent to freely dash into his mouth. The ferocious inertial impact of the massive torrent made him trembled slightly.

Around the torrent were countless more dissipated parts which were rapidly absorbed by the crystal.

“Come on, come on…give me more…hahaha…!!” Garen felt the long-absent energy in his body increasing more and more. The dark energy was unceasingly being converted into Cold Energy by the Hellfrost Peacock’s devouring essence and madly filling his body which had been dried up for too long. A never-experienced-before kind of joy and satisfaction incessantly overflowed within his heart.

His eyes widened, and numerous Cold Energy was slowly emanated.

But what he absorbed was only a small part while a majority of it was absorbed by the crystal. As time progressed, the black torrent grew thicker and more ferocious. Occasionally, one could see some insect organism kind of strange dark shadow stuff mixed in it.

These black impurities rushed into Garen, and a large number of various toxins also rushed into Garen’s mouth following the impact.

He did not refuse them but madly swallowed them. The power in his body quickly grew like a dry sponge quickly absorbing all the water around it. These dark energies were second only to the purity of the energy tide he had absorbed. Although ferocious, they were of no harm to him, whose body had been transformed into the Hellfrost Peacock.

Numerous dark energies were constantly being converted into Cold Energy and absorbed by him. The long-awaited final stage of Hellfrost Peacock Technique had started to progress again.

Garen stared at the attribute changes within his field of sight.

‘Secret Technique – ‘Hellfrost Peacock Queen is growing: The three Army-Level Soul Seed’s Dimensional Dream Ability has triggered the Hellfrost Peacock’s ultimate form – Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s evolution, but the evolution requires an unimaginable energy growth…progress is now 7%.’

Ability gained – Peacock Transformation.

Ability gained – Devoured Energy Field 5.

Ability gained – Distortive Seed 5.

Ability gained – Cold Chaos 5.’

The inexhaustible energy of the Dark World emboldened Garen to devour completely. He allowed the black torrent to gush wildly into his mouth, swallowing big mouthfuls of it. It was almost directly infused into his stomach, was quickly devoured and converted into cold energy, nourishing the growth of the Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s evolution.

The crystal became more and more solid and countless Dark Shadow energy rushed into it. It was continually strengthening its own solidity in an extremely rapid manner. This kind of strengthening was escalating non-stop, and the Confinement Power was increasingly becoming greater.

The constant surge of a black torrent, the increasingly solid dark golden crystal, and the blurred human form glimmering red light in both of his eyes in the crystal; all these were hidden in the depths of the ground underneath White King’s palace. No one realized it.

Time passed slowly…unwittingly, the black fog fluctuated increasingly greater, and it seemed that as time went on, its surging speed would increase continually.

Garen had gradually forgotten the passage of time…he was only madly devouring again and again. The surrounding crystal was also wildly absorbing the dark energy, and the Confinement Power was becoming more and more powerful.

The great impact of the dark energy went against the Confinement Power, but it was also being absorbed by the Confining Crystal incessantly, turning into the purest essence power and transforming the disposition of the crystal itself.

This was a kind of contradictory combination. The crystal absorbed the dark energy to strengthen the Confinement Power, and the Confinement Power gradually started to naturally block the influx of the dark energy, causing the impact of the dark energy against him to be increasingly lesser and lesser.

When the Confinement Power of the crystal was strong to a certain extent, it would be the time when the dark energy could not rush into the crystal. That would also be the time when Garen could no longer devour the dark energy.

He did not know how long this demarcation point could hold out. But now, he was watching the progress of the evolution of the Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s ultimate form gradually rising in his Attribute Pane…

7%, 8%, 9%…

Little by little, the distortive power did not affect time anymore. Garen sensed that his flow of time at this moment was normal. And so, he completely settled down and recklessly competed with the crystal to devour the dark energy. Even the dark matter contained in it was directly converted into Cold Energy by him.

Unconsciously, he was gradually left with only one thought… devour…

Without knowing how long it had been, Garen’s consciousness gradually blurred. Even the strongest consciousness would have a time of drowsiness. Unwittingly, he fell asleep…

******************

Endless white space.

Garen stood alone in a white space, surrounded by nothing. It was all white.

He looked up. It was completely white above and the edge could not be seen.

He then looked beneath his feet. There was only white, and it looked very pure. There was nothing around and nothing was to be seen. Apart from white, it was still white.

“This place is…?” Garen frowned slightly. He clearly remembered that he was still madly devouring innumerable dark energy the previous moment, but he had now suddenly appeared here.

He lowered his head and saw that he had a red rose in his hand. When he looked up again, he saw a huge, red rose the height of a person which had appeared in front of him unknowingly.

It was the kind of single rose that was plucked out. Bright and tender, the side of the flower also had a prominent, thick lip. There seemed to be a fuzzy face as well.

“Hey buddy,” the mouth on the rose spoke up. “Do you know one plus one equals two?”

Garen was stunned.

“Didn’t you just say that one plus one equals two?” He did not know why he answered this question but just said out the answer naturally. He did not even think that there was anything wrong in speaking to a rose.

“Hey buddy,” the rose spoke again. “Do you know why one plus one equals two?”

Garen thought for a moment and answered seriously.

“This is a very complicated question.”

After finishing his words, he ignored the rose and turned about, walking aimlessly towards another direction.vd

Chapter 1140: Sublimation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There was no direction and no distance in the endless white space. Only the voice of the rose that was gradually getting softer behind could be used as a guide so he knew he was indeed moving forward and not walking on the same spot.

He walked and walked… Not knowing how long it had been, Garen himself almost forgot about time and was just walking unconsciously as such.

He knew that at this moment, he should be asleep and was probably now in a dream.

The Ancient Endor civilization and Void Creatures both had the ability to control dreams. Although he was now being distorted and confined, this kind of essence seemed to be more advanced than the two other concepts and so he was still able to control the dream.

“Disperse.”

He said to himself.

However, the surrounding space was still white and there was no response. Clearly, this was not a disguise, but the dream itself was white.

He had not encountered this kind of uncontrolled dream for an extremely long time.

Many of the things which appeared in dreams were irrational and there was no logical reason for them. However, some things suggested a certain kind of wonderful essence.

Garen did not know why he dreamed as such, but he was slightly curious. According to logic, as a master of controlling dreams, the identity of Ancient Endor civilization and the Void Creature, Hellfrost Peacock, would not enter into a dream involuntary. There must be something which was subconsciously hinting him, causing him to enter into a dream.

Not knowing how long he had walked, Garen suddenly saw a swan in front.

The pure white swan had no variegated color on its body and was almost one with this space.

What was even more bizarre was that there was only one white swan.

He was wearing a black tuxedo and had two human legs underneath. One wing was like a palm holding a staff.

“Young man,” the swan’s black beak opened and closed, making a sharp voice. “Do you know where Balloon is?”

“Balloon?”

“Yes, it’s the name of a flower,” the swan-gentleman turned his staff.

“I don’t think I know,” Garen replied randomly. Just as he was preparing to leave after answering, he found himself stopped by the swan-gentleman.

“Mother says, we must be honest,” Mr. Swan was very angry. His chest continued to rise and fall as his voice became more terrible.

“I’m sorry,” Garen suddenly felt that the entire dream was shaking violently.

“Baby… Baby, wake up. It’s time for lunch…” A gentle voice seemed to come from the sky and continually stirred in the entire white space.

Garen was suddenly enlightened. This should be a child’s dream as it was such a simple dream it could only belong to a child.

He opened his eyes and abruptly awakened. It was still the dark golden crystal before his eyes and he was still in the Void Crystal.

“It really had been…a very, very long time since I last dreamt…” Garen sighed in his heart. “I almost forgot that I still have this ability… The natural ability as the inheritor of the Ancient Endor civilization…”

“Perhaps it was the advancement of the Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s evolution which led to the dream losing control and so, inadvertently entering other people’s dream.”

“Since the confinement and distortion cannot affect my ability to enter a dream, this may be a good breakthrough point,” Garen had a new plan in mind.

Looking at his own attributes, the degree of completion of the evolution had reached 12% and the solidity of the crystal had reached an unimaginable state. Garen’s current Cold Energy could not be spread out at all, and could only slowly flow under his skin.

This kind of confinement was still escalating madly.

Garen continued to devour, while the crystal was constantly enhancing. Everything seemed to have no end.

Not knowing how long had passed, perhaps a year, perhaps a decade. The surge of the dark energy had gradually lessened more and more. From the size of a person’s head at the beginning, it had reduced to the size of a fist.

Large amounts of dark fog had just emerged and was absorbed by the crystal.

Unconsciously, the dark energy that Garen could absorb was getting smaller and smaller but it was getting increasingly purer. The energy that could rush through the crystal was often the purest, most powerful and densely condensed high-density dark energy. This, in turn, gave him a faster advancement speed because the digestion speed was quicker.

Finally, one day, after devouring an unknown amount of energy, the Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s evolution eventually reached 100%.

*******************

Ten years later, in the center of the palace, on the white jade platform which was surrounded by numerous stone columns.

White King appeared instantaneously and sat directly on a large white stone ball. The stone ball hovered in mid-air it was full of scratches and various ancient patterns and holes.

After more than a hundred years, White King still had the same young look. There were almost no changes in his appearance.

Boom!!

Suddenly, a small muffled sound came from outside of the palace, as if something inexplicable had exploded. A wonderful aura rose and slowly diffused outside the palace.

White King’s seemingly closed eyes were immediately opened and he looked puzzlingly at the outside.

His Willpower instantly spanned the palace and extended in the direction of the sound from the outside world. The changes in all these things were present in his spirit. No subtlety was able to be kept from his eyes.

His Willpower immediately came to the crystal where Garen was at. Everything that was happening inside the crystal directly came into view.

“Void Crystal…” His eyes narrowed slightly.

With a swish, his body disappeared from the floating white stone ball right away.

Outside the palace, the ground surrounded by meteorites was slowly shaking.

The ground gradually bulged and a dark, irregularly-shaped golden crystal slowly rose from the earth.

The crystal stone was the height of two people. The center of it was a black vortex rotating at a high speed. It was spewing and emitting large amount of dark fog. There seemed to be a person standing on the edge of the black vortex.

The figure of White King in a white robe suddenly appeared in front of the crystal.

He looked face to face with Garen through the crystal.

He seemed to have realized the change in Garen.

“Purposely causing a commotion, you are forcing me to kill you in advance…” White King said quietly.

The surrounding was silent and there was no second person around. A tremendous distortive power slowly vibrated on White King, distorting all the physical laws around, whether it was space or time.

Numerous meteorites had also slowed down their circling flying speed. The rising distortion from White King’s body turned into a huge transparent giant human outline, enveloping the island in the center of the meteor stream.

The red light in the human eyes inside the crystal became brighter.

“You can’t kill me,” Garen’s voice transmitted through the crystal. His face was calm. “This will also be a part of fate…”

In had been ten years. He had absorbed the dark energy for ten years. The Confinement Power of the crystal was completely absorbed and saturated, reaching its peak level. Especially with the boost brought about by Garen, this which was once the Dark Shadow Dragon’s crystal core had been combined with Garen’s Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s Cold Energy. The freezing from the extreme cold was actually a different kind of confinement attribute. When superimposed, it intensified the Confinement Power of the entire Confining Crystal.

The current Confining Crystal had sublimated to a point close to another kind of essence, which was the most powerful essence of the Dark Shadow Dragon.

The reason why Garen took the initiative to alarm White King was because it was time to corroborate everything.

There was almost endless dark energy which had been absorbed by the crystal. At this moment, it was time to witness the Confinement Essence of the crystal and White King’s Distortive Essence and see which concept was the stronger in the end?!!

“Interesting,” White King’s voice softened. He seemed to be more mature than before, but there was a trace of anxiety and coldness between his eyebrows. Although his face was still smiling, it was no longer as firm and pure as it was at first. There seemed to be an additional trace of suspicion instead.

“We’ll give it a go.”

Suddenly, he reached for the dark golden crystal. He spoke no nonsense.

On the white slender hand, the blue veins on the back of the hand could be clearly seen.

Garen heart’s immediately pounded. After so many years of strengthening the confinement, it was now the time to see if the Dark Shadow Dragon’s Confinement Power or the White King’s Distortive Essence was stronger.

Pap!

The palm lightly touched the surface of the crystal.

*******************

Mars, Red Desert City

White high-rise buildings formed this huge and bustling desert city.

The buildings were several thousand meters high and some were directly suspended in mid-air. There were countless space-cars and spaceships shuttling back and forth in between. Their sizes varied and they projected numerous shadows on the ground.

The ground was completely empty, without any vehicles and there were only pedestrian on the streets.

Baylon tightened her white windbreaker and walked to the right side of the pedestrian street. She crossed the street lamps one after another and from time to time, the crowded flow of people would bump into her shoulders.

Obscured and admiring sights would constantly fall on her. They were the complimenting gaze of the men passing by.

‘The recent outbreak of the anomalous mutated creatures’ upheaval on Cameron Star. According to the news from the latest Alliance expedition, the Science Department has preliminarily determined that there may be a hole in the void which caused the leak of Void Creatures. Such a leaking hole will usually shrink and disappear in two Mars-revolving-years. It is hoped that the people will not worry too much. The number of casualties are currently in the process of being tabulated, and it has not yet been determined…’

Looking up at the news on the big advertising screen.

A cold sarcasm was seen in the corner of Baylon’s mouth.

“What bullshit.”

She tugged her hands in her pockets and quickly accelerated forward in a light and quick motion.

No one knew the situation better than her. In the first wave of members who had come in contact with Cameron Star, her companion, White Winter, was involved.

Since the Energy Machinist Extinction, they had all joined the only Star Emperor force – Sawtooth King, who did not lay his hands on the Energy Machinists back then. They were now members of different positions in each army team.

This round of exterminating Scarlet Mourning Hall’s secret spot on Mars was the mission completed together by Clint and herself.

As for the rumor of their Regent-Level heritage, it was meaningless to Sawtooth King. Red King was defeated by him back then even though his power was twice as strong, and so he was not bothered at all.

On the contrary, he had a friendship with the Red King. This matter was a big problem for the general forces but it was a simple, trivial matter for Sawtooth King, who was one of the Nine Emperors of the human beings. As for White King, hardly anyone really knew about the matter of White King targeting Red Moon.

Baylon took a few steps forward and soon, a green coconut-like spaceship landed and hovered beside her.

The window opened to reveal a handsome looking face on the inside.

“Hey beauty, are you interested in going for a ride together?”

Chapter 1141: Dreamland 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Baylon was dressed in a white windbreaker and a pair of white jeans that outlined her muscle-toned legs. Her hair was tied back in a ponytail and her waist was dressed with a white metallic belt. A hundred over years had brought minor changes to her facial features and a cold alluring demeanor.

She threw an indifferent glance at the man as though she has never seen this person before. She went about her own business, giving him the cold shoulder.

“Hey, Colonel Baylon. Don’t be like this. Don’t be so cold, we are best friends, you know? Would it kill to ruin your ice princess status?” The man grinned mischievously as he navigated the vehicle to chase after Baylon.

“Looking at you is repulsive. Scram!” Baylon remarked straightly, hastening her speed.

The man was called Owen Lisbe. One of Baylon’s many suitors and the most prominent. He had an extraordinary background. His family connections ran all over the Human Nine Emperor Alliance. Baylon was a colleague from the same bureau.

Ever since Baylon was transferred to this special tactical bureau, it was love at first sight for him and followed by over sixty years of courtship. Other suitors came and went but only he remained.

He initially thought that with Baylon, a self-independent elite coming from a mediocre background would be hiding her glee being courted by him who was the second generation of the rich and official family although she looked unfazed. She would probably only be reserved in the beginning. He didn’t think that after all these years, she would never respond to it. However, Baylon’s reacting to it was the same.

There were so many beautiful women in the sea. Sixty over years of waiting and keeping watch had Owen Lisbe unsure what it was for. His family had pressured him but he brushed it off each time so they then let him be.

“Am I really a sadist? The more I’m tortured, the more excited I become?” Owen Lisbe grabbed his chin and put on his sunglasses. He glanced at his extremely cool and perfect reflection from the vehicle and nodded with satisfaction. He drove his vehicle to catch up.

He was not clear on Baylon’s background but no matter what, nobody would be a stronger candidate than he was. He couldn’t be bothered to put too much thought into it. It was all to his fancy.

“I have the latest news on the Scarlet Snow Sect, want to chat about it?” If cat-calling didn’t work, then he should use his trump card!

And indeed, right after these words were said, Baylon stopped stepping forward.

The lady turned around and the shroud of coldness in her eyes deepend.

“I’ll kill you if you’re joking!”

Owen Lisbe had cold sweats. He immediately nodded forcefully.

“How could I? Little ol’ me would not dare kid with Your Majesty,” he quickly ingratiated with a huge smile.

Baylon’s combat efficiently has broken through the horizon. If he, a regular Inherited Level were to raise his sword at her, he could be crippled at any given moment. No joke, two of the Soul Officials of the Scarlet Mourning Hall had died in her hands. Baylon, this young lady was famous for killing without batting an eyelash.

This was someone who once was coined Beowulf in the special bureau and could tear a large dragon with her bare hands!

Although the uncles in his family were more powerful than her, if he could get a girl with his familial connections then he would be more than a failure. Owen Lisbe wasn’t a dumb second generation.

Getting into the vehicle, Baylon did not say a word but stared intently at Owen Lisbe.

“Don’t be like this… It’s pressuring me…” Owen quickly spilled everything he knew.

“The people from the Scarlet Snow Sect are proved to be hiding out in a large underground cave in the south of Mars. The hall leader of the Scarlet Mourning Hall is already making his way there. The capabilities of both hall leader and deputy are unclear as nobody has seen them in battle as those that did, died. So it’s best you don’t act rashly!”

Baylon frowned.

“And?”

“And… And nothing else…” Owen laughed awkwardly. “This is the specific map,” he transferred the first-hand-obtained map over through wireless.

Baylon received the map and projected to her retina for a careful look.

“Thanks!” She flipped and leaped out of the vehicle and walked towards an outer lane.

“Sigh!” Owen stretched his arm out in hopes to persuade her to stay but alas, not a shadow in sight. He could only sigh helplessly.

“Always so mysterious, sigh…” He really didn’t know what else to say about this beautiful colleague of his. No matter well he treated her, she retained a distance from him. “Don’t tell me she’s prepared to be a spinster?” He was struck by this thought. He shook his head and navigated his flying vehicle away.

Once the vehicle left, Baylon’s face emerged from the alley.

Her gaze was quietly fixated at the leaving flying vehicle. A hint of guilt flickered in her eyes.

“I’m sorry, I do not wish to trouble you…” she muttered in a low voice.

With Chinande as a sworn enemy and White King as a foe, this kind of life has no future. They were battling with fate every moment of the day. What qualification did they possess to marry one and live a steady life?

She wasn’t stone cold. Anyone who was treated with sincerity for sixty years wouldn’t be heartless, but…

Baylon lowered her head to look at another intel in her hands. It was from White Winter.

“The Scarlet Mourning Hall may have sent someone out. Double-Headed Crab is the leader. It looks like it’s to probe on the news on the Scarlet Snow Sect. What’s the plan?”

“Are we able to get through to Scarlet Snow? How are they perceiving it?” Baylon ran a line on the paper and a row of words appeared.

“We managed to contact but they couldn’t be bothered. They are the last Energy Machinists. It’s not just those from Scarlet Snow, they took in other Energy Machinists. Their capabilities are unknown,” replied White Winter.

“Did you mention the name of my brother?” Baylon’s brows were in a knot.

“I did, but it didn’t change their attitude. They don’t seem to have heard of it?” White Winter was puzzled.

Baylon frowned.

Ever since the Scarlet Snow Sect retreated, they hid behind the scene for more than a hundred years. While they were recuperating and rebuilding. It was unknown how their development was but no matter what, it was not probable that they never heard of her brother’s name. He was, after all, one of the outstanding sect masters.

“Let’s continue this when I’m there!” Baylon responded and put away the paper. She took large strides into the alley and disappeared.

******

Too many things happened in a hundred and fifty years…

Scarlet Snow City in the core of Mars.

This huge city built deep in the crust of Mars was surrounded by lava torrents. The entire black city seemed to be encircled by a scarlet red ribbon. It looked exceptionally majestic.

In an old stone house in the city.

A middle-aged man coated with white hair was sitting with his legs crossed on a black stone bed.

The man opened his eyes and they reeked of coldness and solemnity.

“Cough cough cough…” He acutely barked. He extended his arm to obtain a tissue to cover his mouth. The white tissues were swiftly smeared with bloody red streaks.

“White Night, the acting sect master has something he needs you for,” an equally cold voice rang through the stone house. It was a female voice.

“What is it?” The middle-aged man on the bed asked.

“You would be happy to do so. Your brother, White Winter has been rescued but has been taken under Sawtooth King. The sect master wants you to take care of any possible appearance of ambush,” the female voice explained.

“White Winter is out?” White Night’s eyes widened slightly, “What Level is he?”

“It is unclear but it should be below the Inherited Level. It is said that he became an instructor of a team and is currently training a bunch of newbies.”

“Idiot!” White Night’s eyes popped open, “He forgot the about the family animosity! He forgot all he should bear. A Gideon Body type yet make no use to it!” A sense of violence rose from his body.

“You’re willing to devote to cultivation, doesn’t mean that others would,” the female voice did not say more and faded to the background.

Only the chilling aura of White Night’s growing rage remained within the range of a few hundred meters of the stone house and a layer of snow indistinctly condensed on the ground.

******

For all these years, the Scarlet Snow Sect had been in search of Garen’s whereabouts. Due to the Distortion Seeds, they firmly believed that Garen did not pass. In over hundred years of broadcast and assassinations of Mech Pilots, the old continued to sacrifice while the new kept emerging, replenishing the vacancies. In the Scarlet Snow Sect, apart from the high management, almost no one knew the real name of Garen, the previous sect master. Most of them only knew the name of Garen but not his real name.

On top of a bloody rock peaked on the mountaintop within the city of Scarlet Snow, was a red-clothed couple standing side by side, looking down at the city’s scenery in an arched cave.

The man was Dark Light, Dark Light Accord. After all these years, he had less of an arrogance and more of a maturity.

The woman leaning next to him was Alice from the Scarlet Snow Sect.

They looked intimate. It seemed they had bound in partnership.

“What path are you saying this Jared kid is taking again?” Dark Light narrowed his eyes. “The older he gets, the more I can’t get in his head. It was easy when he was young.”

“If you as a father can’t do it, do you think I can?” Alice rolled her eyes at him, “He’s only fooling around with Aloran’s girl all day. He’s such a baby even if he is over twenty. It’s your fault you did not educate him as a father.”

“Our Scarlet Snow as the head of the three major forces under Sawtooth King is only temporarily depending on him. I’m worried that Jared’s generation might be fused and assimilated by Sawtooth King,” Dark Light was concerned. “Garen must be still alive. With that character of his, there’ll surely be trouble once he’s back.”

“It’s been over a hundred years. What’s the point of fussing over it?” Alice wasn’t the least bit worried. “The acting sect master and Ice Demon General will be on it. Us, old folks should just live day by day. After years of killing sprees, it’s time for us to just enjoy our lives.

“That’s true, but…” Dark Light sighed, “I wonder how Liz and the rest are doing? When my father passed away last year, I only saw her once at the funeral and that was it.”

“You really think too much and complicate things. Our Scarlet Snow Alliance has extensive influence. We have thirteen just on our sect branches. We have grown more than ten folds compared to a hundred years ago. With the infusion of ninety percent energy essence from the Energy Machinists, apart from the Regent Levels, who would dare challenge us? Even if they were at Regent Level, they still have to be wary of Sawtooth King,” Alice was still unconcerned. “With this connection, it is enough for Liz to live comfortably.”

“Since King Cat was heading out, I asked for his help to investigate,” Dark Light was still at it. “We were friends after all.”

“I think you mean girlfriend,” Alice pinched him violently. The pain instantly had Dark Light’s brows in a tight knot.

Chapter 1142: Dreamland 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

White Royal Palace, Finite Nebula core.

A long robe hung loosely on White King as his white hair fluttered. His right hand calmly dabbed onto the dark golden void crystal.

Bam!!

The glass cracked then shattered with the sound of an explosion. Countless pieces of glass scattered and disseminated into sparkling white powder, firing in all directions with the pressure of the force field.

With a sound of a click, his palm penetrated sharply inside the crystal.

At the same time, a pure large resistance force blocked White King’s palm which instantly decreased the penetrating speed and halting it within the crystal.

“Mm?” White complicated line patterns emerged on the skin of White King’s right arm. On it were various symbolic characters with a scent of holiness. These white glowing symbolic lines seemed to have increased the strength of his palm.

The Distortive Power erupted from the palm of his hand and met head-on with the Confinement Power.

Two forces of power rules collided with no sight of an exaggerated explosion. The measure of their attribute concept was absolute and wouldn’t change based on its capacity. They didn’t have the concept of quantity but rather a form of an attribute.

The two forces of concept diminished all together and disappeared without a trace.

This was unpredicted whether by White King or Garen.

The attribute concept of Shadow Dragon and White were at the same height.

Clang!!

The palm of White King ricocheted out of the crystal. He took a step back and cradled his right hand. He was slightly surprised as he looked at the void crystal in front of him.

“What attribute is this?”

He instinctively felt that the concept of this attribute was no more inferior than his distortion and Regent Level that surpassed Perpetual Motioners in the concept of attributes. Without this, it would depend on the individual actual combat strength.

At this stage, the true telling of victory would be first to measure between attributes and second, at circumstances of equal attributes would be the actual killing power of the true form.

Seeing White King blocked successfully, Garen’s nerves simmered down.

“If your distortion is absolute to chaos then the confinement here is absolute to frozen stillness.”

White King frowned, extended his hand and pressed on the crystal once again.

This time, a large white ring appeared behind him. This ring seemed to be built by white jade. It looked sacred with carvings of complicated patterns and sculpture of flora and fauna.

“Crush space,” White King’s palm imprinted on the surface of the crystal and a distortive attribute different from before wildly surged.

This was purely the attribute of a distortive dimension without the accessorial distortion that aimed only at space. This sort of Distortive Power reached a terrifying level in a blink of an eye.

Buzz!!!

The contact this time burst open a slight distortive yet transparent force field between his palm and the crystal.

The surface of the crystal was sighted with strings of cracks but these cracks quickly disappeared.

Compared to the previous casual attempt, this was a demonstration of White King’s powers. The high density of the attribute concept did not destroy the dark golden crystal. It went without saying what this represented.

“Who would have thought…” The White King retrieved his hand and had a complicated look on his face, “Who would have thought that you’d use the attribute of foreign objects to bypass this checkpoint and covertly protect yourself.”

However, doubt still lingered in his face.

“But with this sort of absolute confinement, you have not grasped the attribute concept. Even if you succeed, you would lock yourself tighter in. What is the point of this?”

To him, Garen’s series of actions did not pose too big of a threat. For Garen to seal himself in, he had to avoid fated battle to the death, but wasn’t this equivalent to suicide?

“What do you think… Perhaps I am only begrudging…?” Garen’s voice started to shift on and off. The dark golden crystal repeated a round of extreme dark energy absorption. The confinement concept increased and even Garen’s voice could not be transmitted as it went on and off. Even if he grasped a part of the confinement attribute, he still received a severe interference.

“Begrudging?” White King stared coldly at Garen. It was a long pause.

The two of them exchanged glances without anyone giving in.

It was long until White King turned and left.

He built Garen a prison. He didn’t think that Garen would in turn, make the prison even more secure to the point that he as a creator could not even open it.

“A meaningless struggle. You are so, so are humans,” White King’s voice was heard from afar.

Garen’s lips pursed into a smile in the crystal.

“Is it really… meaning though?”

He stared at White King’s receding figure and knew that he finally retained his life from this world’s strongest existence.

The three strongest giant void beasts of the Endor civilization were the most mysterious Shadow Dragon who held the confinement attribute. Although it wasn’t him who personally yielded, it was enough to passively keep him alive.

“So the first stage of the plan is finally executed. On to the second stage… Since history has determined the new Red King to kill White King, the only thing I should do is…”

Garen looked at almost-collapsing Shadow Dragon boundary point. He slowly closed his eyes and fell into a deep sleep.

The confinement power of the void crystal increasingly built; getting more terrifying and heavier by the minute.

It was the third day since Garen closed his eyes.

With a clang from the crystal, its entirety emitted plain white cold air, spreading to the outside world.

The small half of White Royal Palace island territory was shadowed by the cold air. Although the Distortive Power was quick to vanquish, but since the ejection of cold air, the dark golden crystal had completely turned transparent. It embodied the finest of glass without a hint of impurity.

White King didn’t seem to be bothered by Garen’s series of actions. Too many things happened in over a hundred years and each of them were beyond his control.

The twelve Golden Merit Blue Princes each had their own ax to grind and was only suppressed by his authority and power. There seemed to be a new development in unison battle. This change brought about distance to the original general trend.

******

“Lon…”

“Lon…”

“It’s me… Lonnie…”

Calling after calling, a familiar voice lingered continuously by Baylon’s ear.

She saw herself standing in an empty city. A silvery-white city. Empty, still, cold. She could not see one soul in there. It was a dead city.

Right in front, walked a blurred figure of a man. He wore an outfit that she was familiar with. He lightly trod over, closing in and taking her hand.

The man’s face was a blur with an obscure dark fog.

He held her hand and made a turn, taking steps forward.

It was most peculiar as she saw her body from the neck down travel ahead with him. Her head remained where it was as she quietly watched her body leave with the man, further and further away.

“Lonnie…” The voice was heard again.

Baylon heard the voice again. A familiar voice.

She felt a pair of coarse hands wrapping around her head and then placed in one’s embrace.

“Who…?”

She opened her mouth to ask.

“You can see me,” a gentle voice of a man was heard.

Baylon struggled to lift her head, in an attempt to look at the person holding her head. Who was the owner of that voice?

Beep beep beep… Beep beep beep…

Suddenly, the sound of an ear-pearling alarm exploded in her ear.

Her eyes opened with a pop. Baylon got up from the bed. Her entire body was full of sweat.

Hu… Hu…

She gasped for air as she was short of breath. She lowered her head and held her face. That was when she realized her face was wet. She was unsure whether it was sweat or tears.

“What is this dream?”

She turned over and got down from bed. Her white pajamas were drenched all over. She walked to the washroom to strip off her clothes and turned on the heater valve, letting the hot water flushed over her from head to toe.

Ring…

Suddenly, her phone rang.

Baylon stretched her arm on the white-tiled wall and poked a few times. Instantly, a semi-transparent screen appeared in mid-air in front of her. On it was a projection of a blonde with two ponytails.

“Lin, where did you agree to meet with Clint?” A woman shouted without reserve.

“Oh, Duoduo. What are you asking this for?” Baylon casually rubbed her wet long mane and brushed it to the back of her head.

“Just tell me already. It’s fine if he doesn’t care about me, but his wife just had a newborn. Can’t he spend a little time with her?!” Duoduo was in rage. “He just runs around. He’s a grown up now yet he acts like a child!”

Duoduo was Clint’s wife. They both had a daughter. They had been married for thirty years. Between them, Clint was married while White Winter had a relationship but was hurt and now had turned into a decadent bearded uncle. He was an instructor at a rookie educational team.

It was only Baylon herself who kept away from the sentimental department.

“Relax, we’ll be back soon. You know how Clint is. It’s going to be alright,” she comforted. Duoduo wasn’t just Clint’s wife, she was also her best friend.

“I’m not opposed of you handling tasks but would it hurt to let me know prior to missions! What’s with leaving behind my back!?” Duoduo was still seeing red but could comprehend that the position Clint and the rest were in. Work task should always place first.

“The departing date is today. We’ll be back about twenty-five days later. Don’t worry, it will be as before, nothing major,” Baylon softly replied.

They were positioned at a special department and needed to be kept secret from family members as well so Duoduo was not aware of the dangers of their work. She thought that it was a gathering intel mission for some sort of safety task force. She wasn’t clear on the details.

“That’s fine then. He’s always like this. I have to look for you to learn what’s going on,” Duoduo vented. “Alright now, Ling is up. I have to take a look.”

“Alright, go ahead,” Baylon nodded and cut off communications.

With the splashing sounds of the shower, her thoughts drifted back to the earlier peculiar dream.

“Really… How long has it been since I last dreamed?” Shaking her head, she put aside the ridiculous thoughts. Intercepting the Scarlet Mourning Hall leader’s movement was happening in the afternoon.

The Scarlet Mourning Hall was a surly organization under Chinande. Perhaps she would be able to obtain news regarding Garen.